Chapter 513: Spoils

Han Li could only look on at Wyrm 3's departing figure with a wry smile.

He took some time to closely examine the map of the Black Wind Sea, and he discovered that not only was he currently very far away from Red Moon Island, he wasn't particularly close to any of the islands on the map.

Moments later, he stowed the map away, then set off in the direction of Dark Veil Island as a streak of azure light.

The wind blowing over the sea was carrying with it a slightly rank and salty smell, and after flying for tens of thousands of kilometers, Han Li removed the mask on his face and reverted back to his original appearance.

He then gently exhaled as he slowed down in his flight, inspecting his surroundings as he flew along at a leisurely pace, and it was a rare moment of serenity for him.

Even though the trip into the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor had been fraught with peril, his luck had been quite exceptional, and not only was he able to ultimately survive the ordeal completely unscathed, he had reaped many rewards to boot.

His cultivation base had reached the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, he had managed to manifest a large number of time law threads, and he had also attained a spirit domain. On top of that, his entire set of Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had undergone an incredible evolution, and even Jin Tong and his Essence Fire Raven had both become significantly more powerful than before.

Additionally, he also had the storage tools of Xiao Jinhan, Feng Tiandu, and Gongshu Jiu, and he was very much looking forward to going through the contents of those storage tools.

Close to an hour later, a three-colored island that was around 10 to 15 kilometers in size appeared in Han Li's field of view down below.

He immediately swept his spiritual sense over the island to find that it was completely devoid of human habitation, so he decided that this would be a good place to make a stop at.

As he descended toward the island, he was able to catch a clearer glimpse of it.

The eastern part of the island was filled with lush greenery, giving it a vibrant green color when viewed from afar, and the cries of apes and deers were ringing out incessantly from within. The central area of the island was slightly barren, with sections of yellow earth exposed, while the western side of the island was riddled with steep cliffs and mountain faces.

As soon as Han Li descended onto the island, a burst of loud rustling instantly rang out from within the dense forest, and a flock of seabirds rose up from the greenery before flying away from the island.

He found a patch of empty ground in the eastern part of the island where the sunlight filtered through the trees, and he sat down there with his legs crossed.

Immediately thereafter, a speck of golden light emerged from his body, then quickly expanded to form a spherical light barrier that encompassed the entire island.

He then flipped a hand over to produce a trio of storage bracelets, while a small white flag and a yellow badge also appeared on his lap.

The flag bore the image of a sea of clouds with both beveled silver text and golden seal text runes embroidered within them, while the words "Cloud Talisman" were inscribed onto the shaft of the flag, and that was presumably the name of the treasure.

This was a treasure of quite a high caliber, but there were no restrictions placed upon it, and Han Li was able to use it as he pleased after a brief stint of refinement.

He injected his immortal spiritual power into the flag, and it immediately swelled drastically in size, forming a huge flag that was close to 20 feet tall.

As he waved the flag through the air, a vast expanse of white mist that resembled a sea of clouds surged out from within, inundating the entire island in the blink of an eye.

All of the remaining birds and beasts on the island instantly erupted into a panicked frenzy with the sudden descent of this cloud of mist.

Fortunately for them, Han Li was only testing out what the flag could do, and he hadn't unleashed any of its abilities, so none of the living creatures on the island were harmed.

He discovered that this flag seemed to actually be an offensive treasure, but in a fit of panic, Gongshu Jiu had used it as a protective treasure earlier, so its true power was never revealed.

Having said that, the fact that an early-High Zenith cultivator had summoned it in such a perilous situation to protect himself indicated that the flag had to have some brilliant abilities, ones that Han Li was eager to explore in the future.

After stowing the flag away, he pulled out the yellow badge before conducting a close examination.

The badge was enshrouded within a layer of yellow light, within which some extremely obscure runes were flashing incessantly, and at the center of the badge was inscribed the words "Immortal Envoy" in golden seal text.

Han Li extended his spiritual sense toward the badge, but as soon as his spiritual sense came into contact with it, it immediately released a burst of yellow light that kept his spiritual sense at bay.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he attempted to channel his immortal spiritual power into the yellow badge as well.

All of a sudden, a string of runes abruptly erupted out of the badge before racing up into the heavens.

Han Li was greatly startled by this, and he immediately summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which released a wave of golden ripples that instantly encompassed the entire surrounding area.

The string of runes was only able to fly for about 1,000 feet before they were encompassed within the golden ripples, upon which they were instantly slowed down significantly, and Han Li made a grabbing motion with one hand to draw the runes back to himself.

The string of runes was struggling in his hand as if they were living creatures, and as soon as he tightened his grip around them, they were immediately scattered into specks of yellow light that quickly faded away.

Han Li presumed that these runes had been released by some type of concealed restriction in the badge, which would be activated as soon as someone outside of Gongshu Jiu tried to use the badge, and if those runes had been allowed to escape, then another immortal envoy from the Heavenly Court would most likely be on his trail soon.

Han Li gently exhaled as he stared at the yellow badge with a hesitant look on his face.

The badge had the potential to expose him, so his immediate thought was to destroy it right away. However, it was no ordinary object, and he couldn't shake the feeling that it would be somehow useful to him in the future, so it would be a real pity to have to destroy it.

After some hesitation, Han Li decided against destroying the badge. Instead, he placed some thorough seals on it before stowing it away.

After that, he picked up Xiao Jinhan's storage bracelet, and after briefly refining it, he released all of its contents, which took up the entire clearing that he was in.

Following a brief examination, Han Li discovered that there were over 30 treasures among the items, the most powerful ones of which were a set of two ice-attribute swords and a small blue flag, both of which were Acquired Immortal Treasures that were imbued with law powers.

Aside from that, there were also several dozen vials of different pills, only a small number of which Han Li was able to identify, while the rest were completely unfamiliar to him.

However, the medicinal auras emanating from all of these pills were far more formidable than the pills that he had regularly consumed to assist in his cultivation in the past, so it was clear that these were pills that were only fit for consumption for Golden Immortals.

Having reigned supreme over the Northern Glacial Immortal Region for so many years, Xiao Jinhan had accumulated a very impressive fortune, but all of it had now fallen into Han Li's hands.

Han Li briefly split up these pills into different categories, then stowed all of them away as well with a sweep of his sleeve.

His gaze then fell upon a white scroll that was around a foot tall, and he casually drew it into his own grasp before opening it.

As the scroll was slowly unfurled, Han Li caught a glimpse of several large characters running vertically down the right side of the scroll, and the characters read "Huanan Pill Scripture".

He hurriedly unrolled the entire scroll upon seeing this, then began to pore over its contents.

A short while later, he slowly rolled the scroll back up again, and a faint smile had appeared on his face.

There were only five pill recipes on the entire scroll, but all of them were for refining Golden Immortal Stage pills, so they were perfect for Han Li.

Furthermore, he could tell from the descriptions of the five pills that all of them were among the vials of pills that he had just stowed away.

Hence, he had both the pill recipes and some samples in his possession, and he would be able to refine more of these pills anytime that he pleased.

Han Li took a deep breath to suppress his elation before opening another scroll, and this one was filled with no fewer than 5,000 tiny ancient characters.

The characters had been inscribed in a very forceful fashion, to the point that the strokes had created deep indentations into the material of the scroll, and the text was giving off a cold and menacing aura.

Just the mere sight of the scroll was enough to make Han Li feel as if he were standing in a bone-chilling snowstorm.

This scroll contained the cultivation insights that Xiao Jinhan had gleaned over the course of his entire life pertaining to the laws of water.

Han Li wasn't cultivating the laws of water, but the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome being cultivated by his Earthly Deity Avatar was a water-attribute cultivation art, and he also regularly used heavy water himself, so he was quite familiar with concepts related to the laws of water. As such, he was able to determine that these insights were extremely valuable, and this scroll would be highly sought after among those cultivating the laws of water.

After stowing the two scrolls away, Han Li turned his gaze to all of the spirit medicines and materials that littered the ground.

A brief examination told him that all of these spirit medicines were very advanced in age, and they were most likely ingredients required to refine the Golden Immortal Stage pills from earlier.

As for the spirit materials, they were also all quite rare and precious, but most of them were ice-attribute materials that weren't very useful for Han Li.

Aside from those things, all that remained of Xiao Jinhan's belongings was a small mountain of Immortal Origin Stones, which were shimmering radiantly under the light of the sun.

He gleefully stowed all of these items away, then immediately moved onto the storage bracelet that had once belonged to Feng Tiandu.

A burst of azure light swept over the ground, and the entire clearing was once again filled with items of all descriptions, among which were three Acquired Immortal Treasures, namely a black bone saber that was around two feet in length, an inky-black rectangular inkstone, and a sheet of paper that had a jade-like quality to it.

After unraveling all of the restrictions placed upon them, Han Li refined all three treasures to an elementary extent.

On each side of the black bone saber was engraved a crescent-shaped indentation, out of which faint wisps of baleful qi were emanating incessantly.

In contrast with the bone saber, the rectangular inkstone appeared completely unremarkable in appearance. There was nothing inscribed upon it, and its only noteworthy feature was that its surface was riddled with irregular cracks. However, as soon as Han Li injected his immortal spiritual power into the inkstone, scorching black flames instantly surged out of those cracks.

As for the sheet of jade-like paper, a beastly lion-like head was engraved onto one end, and following an injection of immortal spiritual power from Han Li, the head rapidly swelled in size to form an icy mountain that resembled a resting lion, and it seemed to possess formidable restrictive powers.

Chapter 514: Treasured Case

After briefly observing the trio of Acquired Immortal Treasures, Han Li stowed them away, then made a beckoning motion toward a case on the ground that was about a foot in size, and it slowly drifted over to him.

On each side of the case was a sealed mechanism, upon which was plastered a silver talisman.

Han Li inspected the talismans briefly to find that they were a Azure Dragon Wood Trapping Talisman, a White Tiger Radiant Metal Talisman, a Vermilion Bird Fire Raising Talisman, and a Xuanwu Water Barring Talisman. Furthermore, all four of the talismans were of the highest possible quality.

Whatever's in this case had to have been held in extremely high regard by Feng Tiandu if he was willing to seal it with a Four Symbols Talismanic Array, Han Li thought to himself.

With that in mind, he made a hand seal and began unraveling the array.

The Four Symbols Talismanic Array was quite troublesome to deal with as the powers of the Four Symbols supported one another, so the talismans couldn't be removed one after another. Instead, all of them had to be removed at once. Otherwise, there was a very good chance that whatever was inside the case would be destroyed on the spot.

Hence, the best way to unravel such an array was to have four people with similar cultivation bases working together to remove all four talismans at the same time.

However, Han Li chose a much simpler and more direct approach, which was to encompass the case within the golden ripples released by his Mantra Treasured Axis, then remove all four talismans in rapid succession before they had a chance to react.

After successfully removing the four talismans, the mechanisms on the case instantly sprang open, and Han Li lifted its lid before setting it aside.

Even after the lid was removed, not even the slightest hint of spiritual power fluctuations emerged from within the case.

Han Li peered into the case to find that there was a waxy yellow scripture and a palm-sized black jade badge inside, placed around which were a series of black nails that were arranged in an orderly fashion.

The first thing that Han Li did was pull out the ancient scripture, and he discovered that it was quite smooth to the touch, indicating that it had been fashioned out of the hide of a certain type of beast.

On the cover of the ancient scripture was inscribed the words "Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture".

This title was rather familiar to Han Li, and after some contemplation, he realized where he had heard of it before.

Back when he was searching for a time-attribute cultivation art in the Transient Guild, someone had once mentioned to him there existed a time-attribute cultivation art in the Dawn Fall Sect, and it was precisely this Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture.

When it came to time-attribute cultivation arts, Han Li had only ever come into contact with the Mantra Axis Scripture, so he was unable to reference other cultivation arts of the same attribute to deepen his understanding of the laws of time.

Hence, this Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture could provide him with a valuable learning experience.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he hurriedly summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, then directed the gaze of his Eye of Truth upon the ancient scripture.

A beam of golden light shot out of the Eye of Truth before shining upon the yellow scripture, and a burst of golden light flashed momentarily over the surface of the scripture before immediately fading away again.

A hint of disappointment appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he stowed away both the scripture and his Mantra Treasured Axis.

Looks like this scripture is different from that stone plaque in the Blaze Dragon Dao. Both contain records of time-attribute cultivation arts, but this scripture doesn't appear to be imbued with any time law powers...

With his immense spiritual sense, it didn't take Han Li very long at all to read through the entirety of the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture, and he was very pleased to discover that even though this was also a time-attribute cultivation art, it was completely different from his Mantra Axis Scripture. In particular, it mentioned that once one attained an Illusory Dawn Sand Domain, they would be able to influence the power of time within a certain area.

However, it seemed that neither Feng Tiandu nor Qi Tianxiao had been able to make much progress in this cultivation art. At the very least, neither of them were able to use this cultivation art in battle.

Han Li wanted nothing more than to begin studying this cultivation art extensively right away, but doing so would require centuries, perhaps even millennia of seclusion, a luxury that he absolutely couldn't afford, given the current circumstances.

With that in mind, he could only suppress these urges and stow the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture away to be examined some other time.

After that, Han Li picked up the black badge from the case.

The badge was extremely smooth, and it appeared to have a transparent exterior, but its center was as dark as ink, resembling a drop of ink frozen in an ice crystal.

Just like an ink droplet, the black center of the badge was still able to flow slightly.

This appeared to be a badge that represented Feng Tiandu's status as the grand elder of the Dawn Fall Sect, and after the close call with Gongshu Jiu's badge, Han Li decided to set up a layer of restrictions, and only after that did he attempt to inject his immortal spiritual power into the badge.

However, no matter what he tried, the black badge remained completely unmoved, and it was as if it were truly nothing more than an ordinary badge.

In the end, Han Li wasn't able to uncover what purpose the badge could serve, and he could only give up on the endeavor.

With that, all that remained in the case were the black nails, of which there were quite a few, 81, to be exact.

Han Li picked out one of the nails at random and inspected it closely for a moment to find that it was riddled with all types of patterns, including some type of ancient beast and many peculiar runes, clearly indicating that this was no ordinary nail.

On top of that, there were wisps of black mist that resembled viscous ink swirling around the nail, further lending it a sense of mystique.

After picking up the black nail, Han Li noticed that there seemed to be a black metal slab embedded into the bottom of the case, and it was riddled with inscriptions of different depths.

Only after fishing the metal slab out of the box did he discover that it was an array plate that was riddled with spirit patterns, and on the lower left corner was a line of text that read: "Dawn Fall Heavenly Array."

Han Li was holding the array plate in one hand and the black jade badge in the other, and he took a glance down at the 81 black nails as he murmured to himself, "This seems to be some type of protective array..."

With that in mind, he stroked a finger over the array plate to find that there was an indentation on its back that was identical in shape and size to the black badge in his hand.

He immediately placed the badge into the indentation, and it fit inside perfectly with a faint crack.

A burst of black light instantly surged over the array plate, while the inky substance within the badge flew out from within before roaming over the surface of the badge.

Specks of dark golden light emerged over certain parts of the badge in the wake of the flowing ink, and an elated look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he hurriedly refined both the array plate and the badge together.

After that, he set them down onto the ground, then picked up one of the black nails before gently placing its tip down onto one of the specks of dark golden light.

As soon as the nail began to approach the array plate, the latter abruptly released a burst of powerful suction force that caused the nail to slip out of Han Li's hand before nailing itself into the speck of golden light.

Immediately thereafter, a thunderous rumbling sound rang out in the forest not far away, and Han Li turned to that direction to find that a black pillar of light that was several thousand feet tall had erupted out of the ground there.

There appeared to be a powerful beast coiled around the pillar of light, and it was constantly releasing bursts of faint black qi.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, and he continued to place more of the black nails down onto the array plate.

One nail after another was set down onto the array plate, while more and more pillars of black light rose up over the island.

After the final pillar of black light emerged, the black mist swirling around all of the pillars of light instantly spread outward to fuse together, quickly forming a black light barrier that encompassed the entire island.

Immediately thereafter, all of the pillars of black light that had appeared on the island gradually became more and more transparent, until they vanished out of sight entirely.

Before long, the light barrier encompassing the entire island also faded away, and it was as if nothing had ever happened.

However, a miniature version of the island had already appeared on the array plate in front of Han Li, indicating that it was under the protection of the array.

After observing the array plate for a moment, he rose to his feet, then flew out of the island.

As he passed through the light barrier, he clearly felt a burst of spiritual power fluctuations sweeping over his body, but as the one who had activated the array, the light barrier naturally posed no obstacle to him.

Looking into the island from the outside, it didn't appear to be any different, and it was impossible to tell that it was enshrouded within an array. No spiritual power fluctuations could be detected, but as soon as Han Li activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, the entire array instantly became as clear as day to him.

He flew all the way to around 10,000 feet away from the island, then clenched a hand into a tight fist and channeled his immortal spiritual power before throwing a punch at the island.

A resounding boom rang out as the entire space shuddered violently, and a giant fist projection hat was over 1,000 feet in size emerged before hurtling directly toward the island.

As soon as the fist projection came into contact with the light barrier, the latter was immediately revealed.

Radiant black light emerged over its surface as a series of inky-black dragons flew out of the 81 pillars of black light, drawing upon the power of the array as they converged toward the spot on the light barrier that had been struck by the fist projection.

An indentation that was several hundred feet deep was compressed into the black light barrier, and it looked as if it could collapse at any moment, but Han Li could sense that it was still far from reaching its limits.

Han Li gave a slight nod of approval upon seeing this.

Even though he hadn't unleashed that punch with his full power, it was still an extremely formidable blow, and the average True Immortal Stage protective array would've most likely already been completely razed to the ground at this point.

By Han Li's estimates, the defensive prowess of this array was slightly inferior to that of the array that the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace had set up in the Blaze Dragon Dao to trap Baili Yan.

Even so, this was already a very remarkable protective treasure.

Generally speaking, the protective array employed by a sect would always be set up in an area with an abundance of spiritual qi, and specially refined array plates and array flags also had to be set up to further bolster the array.

With those measures in place, the power of the array would be maximized, but it would also be permanently set in place without any possibility of being moved. It would be very difficult for someone on the outside to break the array, but the array could easily fall prey to internal sabotage.

In contrast, this array was a portable one that could be activated using just an array plate, so it was not only very convenient, but also quite difficult to damage.

With this array plate in his possession, setting up cave abodes was going to be far less of a hassle in the future.

Chapter 515: Incredible Wealth

After returning to the island, Han Li placed the array plate back into the treasured case, then stowed the case away into his storage bracelet before continuing to sort through Feng Tiandu's belongings.

In contrast with Xiao Jinhan, Feng Tiandu had far fewer pills and pill recipes in his possession, and what he did have were also of inferior quality, but he possessed far more spirit materials than Xiao Jinhan did.

Among them were as much as a quarter of a kilogram of Heavenly River Stardust, around a dozen palm-sized Vibrant Rainbow Crystals, and seven or eight vials of Serene Dark Water, all three of which were important spirit materials for refining Acquired Immortal Treasures, so they were always hotly contested during any major auctions that they appeared, even for the tiniest amount.

Aside from that, Feng Tiandu also had a pair of Silver Meridian Immortal Vines that were each around a foot in length and roughly the same thickness as an infant's arm. These vines were vastly renowned in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region as an exceptional puppet refinement material, and they were impossible to buy from virtually anywhere.

According to some unofficial historical records that Han Li had read on some scriptures, puppets refined using these vines possess bodies comparable to True Immortals in power, and they also develop a system of meridians in their bodies that allow them to channel immortal spiritual power and unleash immortal abilities.

After stowing all of these materials away, Han Li's gaze fell upon a bamboo cane that was as green as jade.

The cane was only around three feet in length and as thick as an adult human thumb. It was split up into nine sections, and each section was giving off a faint white glow. Even though it was without a root, it still seemed to be teeming with vitality, indicating that it was imbued with wood law powers.

Han Li was cultivating the laws of time, while his Earthly Deity Avatar was cultivating the laws of water, so he didn't know much about other types of law powers, he was still aware of just how precious these materials that were imbued with law powers were.

In particular, for those cultivating the laws of wood, this bamboo staff would be an extremely highly sought after treasure.

Han Li was going to require a large quantity of items that contained time law powers in order to manifest more time law threads in the future, so he could see if he could exchange these items for things that he needed.

Aside from that bamboo cane, none of the rest of Feng Tiandu's belongings caught Han Li's interest, not because there was nothing else of value, but simply because Han Li's standards had become almost absurdly high. Otherwise, the mountain of Immortal Origin Stones in Feng Tiandu's possession, which was even larger than Xiao Jinhan's collection, would be enough to leave the average Golden Immortal completely flabbergasted.

After sorting through all of Feng Tiandu's belongings, Han Li paused momentarily, then refined Gongshu Jiu's storage bracelet before also releasing all of its contents.

In the blink of an eye, a mountain of Immortal Origin Stones that exceeded even the combined wealth of Feng Tiandu and Xiao Jinhan appeared in the clearing. The Immortal Origin Stones on the top of the mountain slowly clattered down until they reached the edge of the clearing, while all of the other treasures were squished to the side.

Han Li's mouth gaped open slightly at the sight of the small mountain of Immortal Origin Stones, which was quite a bit taller than himself, and he was stunned beyond words.

I can't believe a High Zenith cultivator has so many Immortal Origin Stones...

In addition to the Immortal Origin Stones that he had taken from Qu Ling, Xiao Jinhan, Feng Tiandu, and the others, his current wealth exceeded two million Immortal Origin Stones, which was surely comparable to the entire wealth of a major sect.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li had become ridiculously wealthy, and it seemed that he had more money than he knew what to do with.

However, he then quickly regained his composure.

The path of cultivation was a long arduous one, and the amount of resources that he would have to go through was immeasurable. It was going to take a vast amount of resources just to secure more items that contained time law powers, and that wasn't even to mention all of the pill refinement resources that he required.

With that in mind, these two million Immortal Origin Stones were most likely nowhere near enough to even support his cultivation to the High Zenith Stage, and the elation in his heart immediately began to die down.

He made his way to the other end of the clearing, and from there, he continued to examine Gongshu Jiu's belongings.

The first thing that caught his attention was a massive wooden shelf with multiple tiers, one that was laden with over 1,000 Transient Guild masks of all types of different descriptions.

A stunned look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

Aside from the numbers on these masks, they also had a variety of different prefixes, including Wyrm, Raccoon, Dragon, Crow, and Fox.

Looking at this vast collection of masks, Han Li couldn't help but feel a sense of sorrow for these Transient Guild members that he had never met before. If he had perished by Gongshu Jiu's hands, then his masks would've been added to this collection as well.

"It looks like I'll never have to worry about running out of masks to use," Han Li chuckled as he swept a sleeve through the air to stow the entire wooden shelf away.

Due to how enormous Gongshu Jiu's collection was, Han Li had to sort through one type of items at a time, and the first category of items that he had chosen to examine were the pills.

Gongshu Jiu had a large number of pills in his collection, all of which were of an extremely high caliber, and most of them were unidentifiable to Han Li, but he presumed that they had to all be High Zenith Stage pills.

Having said that, Han Li was a Heavenly Pill Master, so he was able to determine from the aromas and other characteristics of these pills that most of them were for recovery and regenerative purposes, while there were only two types for cultivation enhancement.

It just so happened to be the case that there was golden slip plastered to each of the jade vials that contained these two types of pills, and the slips carried the names of these pills, namely Clear Jade Pills and Zenith Garden Pills.

However, what was rather disappointing to him was that there was only one of each pill left in the two jade vials.

As for the golden slips, their material was rather special, so he decided to give them a closer examination as well.

As soon as his hand came into contact with one of the golden slips, a series of golden characters emerged from within, denoting a series of medicinal ingredient names, such as Jade Yang Essence, Wind Spirit Seeds, Nine-leaf Silverberries...

Clearly, the golden slips contain the pill refinement recipes for these two pills.

Han Li examined the lists of ingredients while sorting through the spirit medicines in Gongshu Jiu's collection, and he discovered that Gongshu Jiu still had a spare supply of most of these ingredients, while only a few ones were missing,

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

After that, he picked up a black jade box, then tore off the golden talisman adhered to it before opening it.

As the lid of the box was removed, he was immediately greeted by a rich medicinal aroma.

There was a pill that was as fair as jade sitting in the jade box, and there were three golden lines on its surface, while faint wisps of mist were rising up from it to form a tiny white cloud around three inches above it.

Much to Han Li's astonishment and elation, this was a third-tier dao pill imbued with qi law powers!

A dao pill of such a high caliber was most definitely a priceless treasure, and Han Li couldn't help but examine it repeatedly with elation in his eyes, unable to bear the thought of putting it down.

Only after a long while did he close the jade box again before stowing it away.

After sorting through all of the pills, Han Li took a moment to compose himself before working through Gongshu Jiu's treasures.

To Han Li's surprise, there were only two Acquired Immortal Treasures in Gongshu Jiu's collection, and after some thought, he realized that perhaps High Zenith cultivators simply relied less on treasures than Golden Immortals.

One of the Acquired Immortal Treasures was a tiny, rusty bianzhong that was very shabby in appearance, looking as if it had just been unearthed long ago.

However, when Han Li tried to crush it with his immense strength, he discovered that he was unable to do so.

Aside from that, he discovered that no matter what he struck the bianzhong with, it didn't produce any sound.

Even after some extensive experimentation, he was unable to find out how to use the treasure.

As for the other immortal treasure, that was a strange-looking black bladed weapon that was around five feet in length, with the hilt and blade roughly equal in length, and its surface was riddled with lightning cloud designs.

Upon injecting his immortal spiritual power into the blade, Han Li discovered that it would tremble and buzz, and all of the lightning cloud designs on its surface would turn golden in color, while arcs of golden lightning sprang forth.

However, as he attempted to inject the power of the Lightning Bird and the Divine Devilbane Lightning in his body into the blade, it immediately began to tremble violently, clearly displaying intense rejection.

After some contemplation, Han Li summoned Daoist Xie, who only took a brief glance at all of the spoils that littered the entire clearing before withdrawing its gaze.

"I managed to reap some spoils during the earlier battle, and this blade is one of them. You're adept in using the power of lightning, so why don't you take a look to see if this is something that you can use?" Han Li proposed.

Daoist Xie remained silent as it swept its gaze over the blade, upon which its expression changed ever so slightly.

Han Li immediately noticed this minute change in Daoist Xie's expression, and he asked, "Is there something wrong?"

"If I'm not mistaken, the name of this blade is Thunderslash, and it's a vastly renowned weapon from the Black Soil Immortal Region," Daoist Xie replied.

"The Black Soil Immortal Region? It sounds like you've recovered quite a bit more of your memories, Brother Xie," Han Li remarked.

"Ever since we arrived in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, snippets of memories have been returning to me, and it's becoming more and more frequent an occurrence of late. Some memories that were previously incomprehensible to me have also been contextualized, so I have indeed recalled many things," Daoist Xie explained.

"It's fine, you don't have to explain anything to me. Seeing as you're able to identify the blade, I'm sure you'll be able to make good use of it, so you can have it," Han Li said with a smile.

Chapter 516: The Jade Pixiu

"I can't just accept such a precious gift for nothing," Daoist Xie said in an indifferent voice.

Han Li was familiar with Daoist Xie's personality, so he wasn't surprised by this response at all, and he said, "From the Spirit Realm to the Immortal Realm, you've assisted me greatly on many occasions. Even though you're contractually bound to do so, I still know better than to take you for granted.

“On top of that, I'll most likely be requiring your assistance from here onward as well. With this blade in your possession, your combat prowess will be significantly enhanced, and that'll only further benefit me."

After a brief moment of contemplation, Daoist Xie nodded in response. "I suppose you're right."

It then accepted the blade from Han Li and grabbed onto its hilt with both hands as a flash of golden lightning lit up in its eyes.

A loud crackling sound rang out as all of the lightning cloud designs on the entire blade began to radiate dazzling golden light, and the spiritual power fluctuations emanating from it were countless times more powerful than what Han Li had been able to manage.

After testing out the blade for a while longer, Daoist Xie stowed it away as it promised, "I'll be sure to repay you for this."

Han Li merely nodded in response with a smile on his face.

A curious look then appeared in his eyes as he wondered to himself, Could it be that Daoist Xie's former master came from this Black Soil Immortal Region?

This was clearly a question that Han Li didn't have an answer to, so he didn't ponder if for long before he continued to sort through his spoils.

This time, his gaze fell upon a tiny white jade Pixiu.

It seemed to be no different from an ornamental antique, and it was giving off a warm gleam under the light of the sun.

Han Li examined the Pixiu momentarily with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, then smiled as he asked, "Are you going to reveal yourself, or do you want me to beat you until you have to?"

The Pixiu remained laying on the ground in a completely still manner, as if it really were just an inanimate object.

"If you're going to force my hand, then don't blame me for what I'm about to do," Han Li said in a cold voice as his eyes narrowed slightly.

In the wake of Han Li's threat, the white Pixiu finally began to move, and it swelled rapidly to transform into a giant white beast the size of a house.

"To think that a mere Golden Immortal would dare to..."

The giant white Pixiu's voice abruptly cut off as its entire body stiffened.

As it turned out, three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had appeared around its neck, and all of them had their tips aimed directly at its throat.

The Pixiu had no doubt that if it were to step out of line, then those three swords would have it decapitated in an instant.

With that in mind, the Pixiu immediately shrunk down to the size of an average pet dof, and it laid down in front of Han Li in a submissive manner as it said in a feeble voice, "Don't be like that... Let's just have a nice and civilized chat."

The three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords continued to hover in the air around it, displaying no intention of letting it off the hook.

"You must be Gongshu Jiu's spirit pet, right? I can sense that you have quite a powerful aura. Why didn't you help him during his battle against us?" Han Li asked.

"Ptui! I'm a primordial true spirit, not a spirit pet! What right does he have to make me his spirit pet? I was only forced to follow him because he'd lived longer than me and possessed a superior cultivation base!" the Pixiu roared in a furious voice.

"Answer me! Why didn't you help him?" Han Li asked as a cold look appeared on his face.

"Because even if I had helped him, there's no way we would've been able to win," the Pixiu replied in a sheepish manner. "One of you had mastered the laws of time, while the other had mastery over the laws of reincarnation, and that's not even to mention that old monster... Gongshu Jiu was an idiot for picking a fight with you, I certainly wasn't going to go down with him!"

"Did he not have any way to force you to help him?" Han Li asked with a skeptical expression.

"He wishes he did! Unless he killed me on the spot, there was nothing he could do as long as I refused to sign a contract with him," the Pixius replied with a smug expression.

"So you're telling me he was unable to do anything to you? Is your current body not one that's been restricted by him using a secret technique? Otherwise, how could a true spirit like yourself have been turned into a little ornament that could be stowed away in a storage tool?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"That's... That's because..."

The Pixiu had no response for this.

"Tell me the truth! What abilities do you possess that convinced him not to place any more forceful restrictions upon you?" Han Li asked in a demanding voice.

"Fine, I'll come clean to you. I have an innate ability that allows me to gather wealth. Over the years, that old bastard, Gongshu Jiu, managed to accumulate a great deal of wealth with me by his side, and that's why he didn't want to kill me," the Pixiu conceded.

"If you keep lying and insisting on testing my patience, then I'll kill you right now. Your true spirit blood will be quite useful to me," Han Li mused as a hint of killing intent surfaced in his eyes.

"No, don't do that!" the Pixiu hurriedly implored in an urgent voice. "All of you humans are so sly and cunning! My innate ability isn't to gather wealth. Instead, it's to uncover certain hidden natural treasures, and as I become more powerful, this innate ability will also continue to improve."

"Alright, I suppose only time can tell whether you're being truthful to me. Now then, do you want to sign a contract with me or be slaughtered for your true spirit bloodline?" Han Li asked.

"What choice do I have? Having said that, I like the look of you a lot better than Gongshu Jiu," the Pixiu sighed in a pitiable voice as it took a glance at the three Azure Bamboo Coudswarm Swords and the time spirit domain around it.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he raised a hand before extending a finger toward the Pixiu's glabella.

After the contract was signed, the Pixiu said, "We're on the same boat now, Master, and my first piece of advice to you is to destroy that thing."

Han Li turned to the direction that it was pointing in to discover a shimmering golden disk, and he asked, "What's that?"

"It's the thing that Gongshu Jiu used to communicate with other immortal envoys and emissaries. As soon as the Heavenly Court learns that Gongshu Jiu has met his demise, they'll be sure to send people to track down that thing," the Pixiu explained.

Han Li reached out to make a grabbing motion, drawing the disk into his grasp for a closer examination.

A cold look then appeared on his face as he said, "If this thing is destroyed by force, the Heavenly Court will immediately be tipped off! Are you trying to get us both killed?"

"Of course that would be the outcome if you destroy it using conventional means, but if you give it to me, then I assure you that won't happen. Now that a contract has been established between us, our lives are interconnected, so what would I stand to gain from screwing you over?" the Pixiu grumbled.

Han Li raised an eyebrow with a skeptical look on his face, but he still handed the disk over to the Pixiu, upon which the latter immediately swallowed the disk whole.

"I was born with no anus, and there's an independent world in my belly, so nothing that goes in will be able to come out unless I allow it. Now that the communication disk is in my belly, it's completely cut off from this world, so no one will be able to track it down," the Pixiu explained with a proud expression.

"It sounds like you're the perfect thing to use to get rid of evidence after killing someone... This is your true innate ability, isn't it?" Han Li jibed.

The Pixiu immediately realized that it had revealed too much, and it protested in a disgruntled voice, "Don't even think about making me swallow anything dirty! I don't eat anything aside from treasures and spirit materials!"

An amused smile appeared on Han Li's face as he continued to sort through Gongshu Jiu's belongings.

The Pixiu seemed to know Gongshu Jiu's treasures like the back of its paw, and it proved to be a great help to Han Li as he sorted through the treasures.

After the treasures came the spirit materials and spirit medicines, of which there was a huge stash, and all of them were incredibly rare and precious pieces. There was also an incomplete map of the Immortal Realm, which denoted many of the areas in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

To Han Li's surprise and elation, he also discovered a pair of items that contained time law powers, one of which was a round fruit that was riddled with tiny golden spots, while the other was a broken dagger that was around a foot in length.

......

Before long, the sun set, and dusk was already beginning to transition into night.

It had taken Han Li the good part of an entire day to sort through all of his spoils, and he stretched lazily as he exhaled with a pleased smile on his face.

He then swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of golden light, and a little girl that appeared to be eight or nine years of age emerged.

She stumbled around a little before falling flat onto her backside, and Han Li hurriedly cast a concerned gaze toward her, only to find that was completely fine, but she was yawning non-stop with heavy-lidded eyes, looking as if she had just been woken up from a deep sleep.

"Why did you wake me up, Uncle?" Jin Tong complained in a displeased voice, displaying no intention of opening her eyes.

"Wake up, Jin Tong. It's time to eat," Han Li said with a smile.

Jin Tong finally forced her eyes open slightly upon hearing this, and she asked, "What is there to eat?"

"Take a look for yourself," Han Li replied as he swept a sleeve through the air, and close to 20 treasures that were giving off formidable spiritual power fluctuations instantly appeared in the clearing, including the white stone pillars that Jin Tong hadn't yet had a chance to finish.

"Woah, there's so much!" Jin Tong exclaimed as she snapped wide awake in an instant.

She then flew through the forest as a blurry golden shadow, arriving in front of the collection of treasures in the blink of an eye.

She then wrapped her arms around one of the white stone pillars with an ecstatic look on her face, but right at this moment, a thought suddenly occurred to her, and she turned to Han Li with her eyes narrowed slightly in suspicion and accusation.

Han Li immediately felt a chill run down his spine at the sight of her piercing gaze, and he asked, "What's wrong?"

Chapter 517: Verification

"You were counting treasures without me, weren't you, Uncle? These are just the things that you don't need, aren't they?" Jin Tong complained with her brows tightly furrowed in displeasure.

"You were sleeping really soundly after eating that cauldron, so I thought I'd let you sleep," Han Li replied in a sheepish manner.

Jin Tong immediately pouted with displeasure upon hearing this, clearly not very satisfied with Han Li's answer.

The jade Pixiu was looking back and forth at Han Li and Jin Tong upon seeing this, seemingly a little confused.

"This bracelet is for you. You can have everything inside it," Han Li said as he raised a hand to summon another storage bracelet, which he handed to Jin Tong.

The former owner of this storage bracelet was none other than Qi Tianxiao.

Jin Tong was still looking rather displeased as she accepted the storage bracelet, but as soon as she inspected its contents, a wide smile immediately appeared on her face.

"You're the best, Uncle!"

Jin Tong quickly put on the storage bracelet, then stowed all of the other treasures on the ground away as well, while Han Li looked on with a faint smile.

The jade Pixiu was feeling very indignant at the sight of this differential treatment, and it could only lay its head down onto the ground with a dejected expression.

Only then did Jin Tong notice the white Pixiu that was laying on the ground nearby, and she skipped over to its side before laying a hand down onto the top of its head.

"Where did you get this dog from, Uncle? Can I eat it?"

The jade Pixiu immediately sprang up onto its haunches upon hearing this, and it yelled, "What the hell are you saying, you little brat? I'll have you know that I'm a primordial true spirit!"

"Did you just call me a little brat?"

A cold look appeared in Jin Tong's eyes as she bared her teeth in a menacing fashion.

The jade Pixiu immediately felt a chill run down its spine, but there was no way that it would allow its honor to be trampled upon by a little girl, so it immediately swelled to the size of a house once again as it roared, "You asked for it!"

Jin Tong merely grinned as a burst of golden light appeared over her body.

An exasperated look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he turned and departed from the clearing.

......

A few minutes later, peace and quiet returned to the island.

"Let's go. We need to make a trip back to Dark Veil Island," Han Li said after erasing all traces of his visit from the island.

He then swept a sleeve through the air to summon the green jade flying carriage that once belonged to Gongshu Jiu before flying onto it.

"Alright, let's go!" Jin Tong yelled with an elated look on her face, and she was straddled atop the jade Pixiu, which looked as if it wanted to die.

"Hurry up, Xiao Bai!" Jin Tong urged as she gave it a slap on the head. [1]

The jade Pixiu gave a distraught wail before carrying Jin Tong onto the flying carriage, which then sped away into the distance, vanishing out of sight in the blink of an eye.

......

Several days later, a ball of green light appeared in the sky above an island as if by instantaneous teleportation, and it left a long trail of afterimages behind it.

The ball of green light faded to reveal a green jade flying carriage, atop which stood Han Li, who was looking down at the carriage with a pleased look on his face.

As expected of a flying immortal treasure used by a High Zenith cultivator, the flying carriage was several times faster than the azure flying boat that he had previously used.

However, due to how incredibly fast the flying carriage was, he was still yet to fully control it, so it was a little jarring whenever it drew to a halt.

At this moment, Jin Tong was laying on her back on the flying carriage, sleeping soundly with her little belly exposed, while the Pixiu was laying in a corner of the carriage in a dejected fashion.

Jin Tong had eaten a bunch of spirit treasures these past few days, and as a result, she had become quite drowsy. Her aura was also fluctuating unsteady while slowly growing more powerful, indicating that a breakthrough was imminent.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes as he detected Jin Tong's aura fluctuations.

Jin Tong was already extremely powerful at this point, and even Han Li wasn't confident in his ability to defeat her in a one-on-one battle without using his time law powers.

If she were to make another breakthrough, then she would naturally be an even more formidable ally.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face, following which he swept a hand through the air to release a burst of azure light that swept up Jin Tong before carrying her into a spirit beast pouch.

She didn't like staying in spirit beast pouches, but given that a breakthrough was imminent, it was safer for her to be in one.

The Pixiu immediately stood up upon seeing this, and before it had a chance to say anything, Han Li stowed it away into another spirit beast pouch, alongside some spirit treasures that were of no use to him.

"You can take a rest in this spirit beast pouch. Here are some spirit treasures that you can eat for your recovery."

After that, he cast his gaze toward the sea down below.

This region of the sea was previously a battleground between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island, but peace and quiet had since returned to the area.

In fact, over the past few days, Han Li hadn't spotted even a single Black Wind Island or Azure Feather Island cultivator on the islands that he had passed by.

After some brief thought, Han Li quickly realized why the conflict had suddenly subsided.

It had to have been the case that the conflict between the two islands was only serving as a smokescreen set up by the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace to throw off all of the other powers so that they wouldn't be able to find the entrance of the immortal manor.

Now that the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor had already come and gone, there was naturally no need for the conflict to continue.

This was good news for all of the islands in the Black Wind Sea, including Dark Veil Island.

Han Li remained on the spot for a moment longer, then made a hand seal, upon which the green flying carriage flew into the distance, vanishing out of sight in the blink of an eye.

Several more days passed by, and Dark Veil Island finally came into view on the distant horizon.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly stopped in his tracks, then cast his gaze to the left with a peculiar look on his face.

He then immediately flew in that direction, arriving on an island not long thereafter.

The island wasn't very large, far smaller than Dark Veil Island, and it was very long and thin, resembling a willow leaf. Vegetation on the island was quite sparse, and there were large patches of gray rock exposed everywhere.

An intrigued look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he inspected the island down below.

This was none other than the island inhabited by the Cold Crystal Race, and in the wake of Han Qiu's demise, the island was claimed by Dark Veil Island. At this moment, the entire island was enshrouded under a blue light barrier.

Han Li took a glance at his surroundings, and he recalled that the scene that he had witnessed back in the Moonlight Palace after being sucked into the wall of light by the Heaven Controlling Vial was precisely this exact setting.

However, even though this was the same island as the one he saw back then, there were still some differences between the two.

Could it be...

His eyes suddenly lit up slightly as he flew down into the sea near the island, then continued to descend through the water, quickly reaching the seabed.

At the same time, he released his spiritual sense outward, and he quickly tracked down a giant rock on the seabed before unleashing a streak of sword qi to strike it.

A huge hole was blasted into the rock, and Han Li reached into the hole to retrieve a green bracelet that was covered in mud.

"This is it!" he exclaimed with an elated smile on his face at the sight of the green bracelet.

This was the storage bracelet belonging to the Golden Immortal Stage nascent soul that Han Li had possessed during that vision.

This was proof that the vision had been real, and he really had possessed a nascent soul from the ancient past, back when the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace was destroyed.

With that in mind, he flipped a hand over to produce the Heaven Controlling Vial and began inspecting it in silence.

Its ability to drastically accelerate the aging of spirit plants was already quite astonishing, yet in addition to that, it had also developed the ability to send Han Li's soul into the past.

It seemed that the first vision that he had experienced, back when he had possessed Ling Yunzi, had also been a past event.

However, it was impossible to tell exactly what time period that was.

There was also the scene depicting the portly monk and his five disciples, and even to this day, that scene remained fresh in Han Li's mind. Having said that, he still had no idea who the portly monk was. However, one thing was certain: the monk's cultivation base had to have been far superior to his own. Otherwise, there was no way that he would've been able to make such significant strides in his cultivation just from hearing the monk's preaching.

After pondering the matter for a moment longer, Han Li stowed the Heavenly Controlling Vial away.

It was impossible for him to tell just how many secrets the Heaven Controlling Vial was harboring, but it was clear that it was even more profound than he had once imagined.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li released a burst of blue light that expelled all of the surrounding seawater, creating an empty bubble on the seabed.

He then released the contents of the storage bracelet, revealing some Immortal Origin Stones, spirit treasures, and pills, among other things.

He had briefly examined these things during the vision, but due to the time constraints, he wasn't able to inspect them very thoroughly, and now that he had a chance to do so, he was very pleased by what he saw.

There were around 50,000 to 60,000 Immortal Origin Stones on the ground, which was a trifling amount compared with his current wealth, but it was still quite a significant sum.

As for the spirit treasures, all of them were flying swords of high calibers, and there were as many as 60 to 70 of them.

With the exceptions of a few swords, all of them were a light blue color, and they were also identical in shape and design, clearly indicating that this was a set of flying swords.

After counting the swords thoroughly, Han Li discovered that there were 72 of them, just like his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and they were giving off bursts of faint starpower fluctuations.

Han Li only briefly examined these flying swords before looking away.

All of them were peak spirit treasures that were only one step away from becoming immortal treasures, but they were still far inferior to his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and therefore not worthy of his attention.

[1]. Xiao Bai is a very generic dog name in China, essentially equivalent to Fido or something like that.

[Back]

Chapter 518: Galactic Sword Array

Aside from the set of 72 flying swords, there were also three more longswords on the ground, one white, one black, and one green.

These three swords were all immortal treasures, and they were giving off bursts of law power fluctuations.

Han Li picked up the white sword to find that while it was very straight, the surface of the was rather bumpy and uneven, indicating that it had been refined using the leg bone of some type of demon beast.

With a slash of the sword, it instantly lit up, and gusts of white yin winds began to swirl around it, giving off a bone-chilling glacial aura.

Even with Han Li's immensely powerful physical constitution, he couldn't help but shudder slightly, but strangely enough, the surrounding seawater didn't freeze at all.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this. It seemed that the law powers imbued within this sword were only effective on physical bodies, so it would be a good weapon to use against other opponents with formidable physical constitutions.

After setting the white sword aside, Han Li picked up the black sword, which was inky-black in color and far shorter than the average sword, only around a foot in length.

Furthermore, its blade was very thin, and there were some dark green spirit patterns engraved onto it.

Han Li gently glided his finger over the blade of the sword, and a gash was sliced into his finger.

The gash was black in color, and the flesh around it began to rapidly necrose while spreading outward.

This is some extremely potent poison! Han Li thought to himself as a ball of golden light emerged over his fingertip, and the rate at which the poison was spreading was slowed down significantly, following which the wisp of poison law powers in the gash was slowly forced out.

The black gash quickly turned red again, then vanished altogether just a few seconds later, and Han Li's finger was restored to its original condition.

He set down the thin black sword before turning his attention to the final immortal sword.

The sword was dark green in color and longer than the average grown man was tall. Its blade had been crafted in the shape of undulating waves, and it was giving off a cold gleam.

This sword contained the most formidable spiritual power fluctuations out of all three of the immortal swords, and it wasn't inferior to any of the immortal treasures in the possession of Feng Tiandu and the others.

Han Li grabbed onto the hilt of the sword before lifting it, upon which his expression instantly changed slightly.

As it turned out, the sword was incredibly heavy, still far less so than his Heavy Water True Axis, but for a Golden Immortal who didn't focus on physical cultivation, the sword would be almost entirely impossible for them to lift.

Han Li swung the sword through the air, and it immediately released a vast expanse of green sword projections, which were imbued with the laws of destruction.

All of the sword projections then shrank down at Han Li's behest, converging to form a pillar of green light before crashing down onto the seabed.

The seabed was instantly torn apart like a frail rag, creating an enormous rift that was several dozen kilometers in length and hundreds of meters wide.

The entire seabed shuddered violently as if an earthquake had just taken place, and the willow-leaf-shaped island in the distance also trembled and swayed for quite some time before settling down again.

A hint of elation appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

He still hadn't refined the sword yet, nor had he swung it with his full power just now, yet it was already extremely formidable, and its destructive power was further enhanced by the destructive law powers that it contained.

If he had unleashed that strike with his full power just now, he would've been able to easily shatter the entire seabed within a radius of hundreds of kilometers, and even the island of the Cold Crystal Race would've been destroyed.

Right at this moment, a burst of spiritual sense erupted out of the island before sweeping through the surrounding area, and it belonged to the itinerant immortal that had been assigned to the island.

Han Li didn't want to meet them right now, so he raised a hand to summon an azure light barrier to conceal himself, as well as the damage inflicted by the sword just now.

The itinerant immortal's spiritual sense swept over the nearby area several times, but ultimately didn't discover anything amiss and faded away.

Even so, Han Li didn't withdraw his azure light barrier.

He took a glance at the dark green sword in his hand, then gave a nod of approval before stowing it away along with the other two immortal swords, following which he turned his attention to the pills on the ground.

After examining all of the pills, a faint smile appeared on Han Li's face.

These pills weren't inferior in the slightest compared with what he had found in the storage tools of Xiao Jinhan and Feng Tiandu, and most of them were recovery, regenerative, and antidotal pills, clearly collected in preparation for the adventure that he never had the chance to embark on.

After stowing the pills away as well, Han Li turned his gaze to the final few items, which consisted of two jade scriptures and a strange-looking silken handkerchief.

One of the jade scriptures was golden in color, while the other one was blue, and the latter was a lot thicker than the former.

He picked up the golden scripture first before quickly flipping through it.

It contained the Bright Moon Sword Arts, a very advanced sword cultivation art that was supposed to be able to support one's cultivation to the High Zenith Stage.

The sword intent cultivated using this cultivation art was very different from what Han Li was cultivating, but there were still some things in this cultivation that he could reference.

After setting the golden scripture down, he picked up the blue one, and this one contained all types of powerful sword techniques, of which there were close to 1,000 in total, and every single one of them was extremely profound.

These sword techniques weren't just designed for battle. Instead, there were also some that could allow one to slay inner demons and hone their mental fortitude, among other things.

Han Li previously thought that he was quite an expert in swordsmanship and sword techniques, but after seeing this blue scripture, he realized that he had been far too flattering in his self-appraisal.

The art of swordsmanship was one that was filled with vast complexities, and his knowledge in this field was still severely lacking.

With that in mind, Han Li sat down on the spot and began poring over the jade scripture in a completely enraptured fashion, and it didn't take long before he finished the first half of the scripture.

As soon as he moved onto the second half, his eyes immediately lit up. As it turned out, the second half of the scripture contained all types of sword arrays that were even more profound than the sword techniques that had come before them.

......

One profound sword array after another was laid out before Han Li, and they served all types of purposes, such as slaying enemies, trapping targets, defending the user, and there were even sword arrays that could stimulate one's acupoints and refine their physical bodies using sword qi.

It didn't take long before Han Li read through the entire scripture, and an intrigued look appeared on his face at the sight of the final sword array recorded in the scripture.

As time passed, the intrigue in his eyes steadily grew more pronounced before eventually transitioning into amazement and elation.

Only after a long time had passed did Han Li raise his head with a bright gleam in his eyes.

This sword array was called the Great Galactic Sword Array, and it was an extremely complex sword array that drew upon the power of the stars. It had been created by the Boundless Daoist over the course of 100,000 years after extensive observation of the stars in the night sky, and it was her supreme sword array of the Boundless Sword Sect, able to grant the user the power to slay enemies one or two cultivation ranks above them.

It could even be said that all of the sword techniques and sword arrays up to this point in the scripture had been created for this final sword array, which combined everything into one.

In order to unleash this sword array, 72 flying swords that were imbued with starpower were required, and they had to be of a very high caliber. Otherwise, they wouldn't be able to bear the enormous power of this sword array.

Once the sword array took shape, each of the flying swords would resonate with one of the stars in the sky, allowing them to draw upon their starpower. It would appear as if a dazzling galaxy of stars had appeared within the array, simulating the Great Dao of heaven and earth.

The array was extremely powerful, but it also had very stringent prerequisites that had to be fulfilled, requiring the user to be at least at the High Zenith Stage while also possessing immense spiritual sense.

There was also a simplified version of the array called the Minor Galactic Sword Array that could be unleashed using just 36 flying swords, and this array could be unleashed by late-Golden Immortal cultivators. Of course, it wouldn't be as powerful as the array's complete form, but it would definitely still allow one to sweep through all opponents of the same cultivation base.

Han Li slowly exhaled to suppress his excitement.

This Great Galactic Sword Array was extremely appealing to him.

Once one reached the High Zenith Stage, it would be virtually impossible to slay an enemy of a superior cultivation rank, unless they had extremely formidable immortal treasures or law powers to assist them.

Hence, it was very bold to proclaim that this Great Galactic Sword Array could allow one to slay an enemy one or two cultivation ranks above them.

Han Li turned his gaze to the 72 blue flying swords beside him, and he grabbed one of them before gently flicking its blade with his finger.

The sword immediately began to quiver like a blue spirit snake while emitting a pleasant ringing sound.

It was clear that these flying swords had been refined for the purpose of unleashing the Great Galactic Sword Array, but as they currently were, Han Li wasn't confident that they would be powerful enough to withstand the strains of the array.

There really was only one way to find out the answer to that question.

Even though the scripture stated that only after reaching the late-Golden Immortal Stage could one hope to unleash the Minor Galactic Sword Array, he possessed far more immortal spiritual power than the average mid-Golden Immortal cultivator, so there was a chance that he would be able to pull it off.

With that in mind, Han Li set down the flying sword in his hand as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

By his estimates, even if these swords could be used to unleash the Galactic Sword Array, they would only just barely be up to scratch.

If he wanted to unleash the Great Galactic Sword Array in its full glory, then he would have to refine another set of flying swords that were imbued with starpower.

His Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords also came in a set of 72, and they were far more powerful than these flying swords. Even though they didn't contain any starpower, it wasn't impossible to change that.

There were many profound sword nurturing techniques recorded in the scripture, and one of them was the Star Spirit Gathering Array, which allowed one to refine their flying swords using starpower.

This secret technique could draw upon starpower to eradicate the impurities within flying swords, thereby elevating their quality, and flying swords refined using this secret technique would slowly be infused with starpower.

Some annotations had been made in the scripture after this secret technique, so Han Li presumed that these flying swords had most likely been refined using this technique.

Having said that, he had no idea what effect this was going to have on his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

On top of that, following this trip into the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, he was currently only able to wield three of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at once, and it seemed that 36 swords was far out of reach, let alone 72.

With that in mind, Han Li shook his head with a wry smile.

Chapter 519: Arrangements

Han Li took a deep breath, then turned his gaze to the final silken handkerchief, which he drew into his grasp.

According to the vision that he experienced, this handkerchief carried a treasure map.

Back when he first experienced the vision, he had already briefly examined the handkerchief and noticed that it was no ordinary object.

With that in mind, he quickly summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, then gazed upon the silken handkerchief through his Eye of Truth.

A burst of rainbow light rippled over the silken handkerchief, and it spread outward from the center like a blot of ink, revealing a complex map.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as he carefully examined the map, following which his brows furrowed slightly.

The map didn't appear to be very complete. Instead, it seemed to be a portion of a complete map, and with the limited information that the map presented, he was unable to determine what location it depicted.

All of a sudden, Han Li's gaze fell upon a corner of the handkerchief, where there was a symbol of a round wheel, one that he had never seen before.

Moments later, he flipped a hand over to stow the silken handkerchief away.

According to the memories of that nascent soul, this map depicted an area in another immortal region, and following the passage of so many years, it was unclear whether the area depicted on the map still even existed, so there was no point in pondering the matter.

With that in mind, he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light to stow everything else away, then withdrew the surrounding azure light barrier.

After that, Han Li didn't linger here any longer, flying away toward Dark Veil Island as a streak of azure light.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li appeared in the sky above Dark Veil Island.

The island was still in a state of lockdown, and all of the members of the Luo Clan were cultivating in seclusion, while the mortals on the island led secure and peaceful lives. The island was very serene and peaceful, seemingly completely untouched by the conflicts that had ravaged the Black Wind Sea of late.

Han Li flew down from above before landing near a village that was surrounded by mountains on three sides.

At this moment, it was dusk, and plumes of smoke from cooking fires were rising up all over the village, forming a thin veil of smoke in the sky, which presented a dreamy and beautiful sight under the light of the dying sun.

The village was like a paradise from another world, completely free from the conflicts and troubles of this realm.

Han Li could hear the sound of livestock and playing children in the village, and an emotion that was rather difficult to identify welled up in his heart. Distant memories of his childhood began to surface in his mind, and he felt himself becoming immersed in these memories.

He quickly snapped back to his senses as a hint of bewilderment flashed through his eyes.

He had witnessed similar scenes on many past occasions without feeling anything, yet why was it that he was suddenly overcome with such strong emotions? Could it be that something had gone wrong with his cultivation?

With that in mind, Han Li hurriedly inspected his own internal condition, but there was nothing amiss.

His brows furrowed ever so slightly upon seeing this, but then quickly unfurrowed again.

The momentary immersion that he had experienced hadn't been detrimental to him at all. Instead, it had instilled within him a profound sense of relaxation.

He gently exhaled as he shook his head.

Perhaps it was because he had been wound up too tightly throughout the foray into the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, and now that he was witnessing such a serene and tranquil scene for the first time in such a long time, he was finally able to relax.

It seemed that it would perhaps be a good idea to visit the mortal world every once in a while as that seemed to have profound benefits on his mental cultivation.

Of course, this wasn't the time to do so. He knew that immense turmoil was going to be sweeping through the Northern Glacial Immortal Region in the near future, and that was most likely going to be followed by an extended period of chaos.

After taking one final glance at the village, Han Li quickly looked away, then flew away into the distance.

Moments later, he arrived in the Luo Clan, then descended silently in front of a large hall.

There was a layer of azure light that was gently swirling like a cloud over the gate of the hall, and it was clearly quite a profound restriction.

Of course, this restriction was nothing more than child's play in Han Li's eyes, and he flew through gates of the hall in a flash, while the azure restriction remained completely oblivious.

At the center of the hall sat Luo Feng atop a cushion with azure light swirling around his body.

Han Li appeared in front of Luo Feng in a stealthy manner, then gave a slight nod of approval as he observed Luo Feng's cultivation.

Luo Feng possessed decent aptitude, and he had made some progress in his cultivation since they last met, indicating that he had been working hard this entire time.

With that in mind, a burst of crimson light flashed over Han Li's body, and he reverted back to his original appearance.

Luo Feng seemed to have detected something, and he opened his eyes, upon which he hurriedly rose to his feet after spotting Han Li.

"Master Liu Shi!" Luo Feng greeted with a respectful salute.

"I came here today because I have some things to speak to you about," Han Li declared.

"Please go ahead," Luo Feng hurriedly prompted.

"I'm going to be leaving Dark Veil Island for some time soon. In my absence, continue to oversee the island as normal," Han Li instructed.

Luo Feng was very much taken aback to hear this, and he hurriedly asked, "How long will you be away for?"

Han Li had no concrete answer to this question, so he replied in a truthful manner, "I can't say for sure, but it'll most likely be a very long time."

Luo Feng's face instantly paled significantly upon hearing this, and he hurriedly said, "Right now, the conflict between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island is still ongoing. Our Dark Veil Island hasn't been swept up in it for now, but it's only a matter of time. Without your presence, there's no way we'll be able to withstand that ordeal on our own, and the allegiance of those itinerant immortals will most likely begin wavering again.

“If you're not receiving sufficient power of faith to satisfy you, then I can instruct the mortals on the island to be even more earnest in their worship..."

Han Li raised a hand to cut Luo Feng off, then said, "There's no need to be concerned. Right now, the conflict in the Black Wind Sea is beginning to die down, and the animosity between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island has also largely subsided. On top of that, even though I'm leaving, my avatar will still remain on the island, and it possesses sufficient power to keep those itinerant immortals in check so that they remain loyal to Dark Veil Island."

"Really?" Luo Feng asked in a slightly uneasy fashion, and it was unclear whether he was asking about the conflict between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island or about Han Li's Earthly Deity Avatar.

"Of course, so you can rest assured. Dark Veil Island is quite an important place to me, so there's no way I'll abandon it," Han Li assured.

Luo Feng was slightly reassured upon hearing this, and he immediately made a display of loyalty. "Thank you, Master Liu Shi. Rest assured, our Luo Clan will be your most loyal servants for all of eternity!"

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he flipped a hand over to produce a storage tool, which he handed to Luo Feng as he said, "There are some cultivation resources in here for you to use."

Luo Feng accepted the storage tool, and as soon as he injected his spiritual sense into it, he was instantly rooted to the spot.

There was an enormous array of spirit materials, pills, and spirit treasures within the storage tool, alongside countless spirit stones, and it was more than 1,000 times the Luo Clan's current wealth.

Such a vast volume of resources had been unimaginable to Luo Feng in the past, yet it had suddenly fallen onto his lap, and he couldn't help but feel stunned beyond belief.

"You can use these resources however you please, but don't use them without discretion. Make sure to nurture the brightest talents in your clan and the most prodigious cultivators on the island. Only by constantly bolstering the island's power will it be able to truly stand firm in the Black Wind Sea, understood?" Han Li instructed.

Given his current astronomical wealth, the resources that he had just given to Luo Feng were barely worth anything to him.

Luo Feng immediately snapped back to his senses upon hearing this, and he hurriedly replied in an excited manner, "I understand! Rest assured, Master Liu Shi, I'll be sure to put these resources to good use!"

With these resources at his disposal, he would definitely be able to develop a batch of high-grade cultivators in a short time, and a few of the elders on the island who were at the pinnacle of the Body Integration Stage would also have a chance of reaching the Grand Ascension Stage.

With a few more Grand Ascension cultivators on the island and the Earthly Deity Avatar leading the way, Luo Feng was confident that he would be able to protect Dark Veil Island.

However, at the same time, he was also rather perplexed. Such a vast volume of resources was something that not even Black Wind Island was guaranteed to be able to muster up all at once, so where had Liu Shi gotten all of this from?

"Good. I leave Dark Veil Island in your hands," Han Li said, then departed from the hall, vanishing into thin air in the blink of an eye.

"You can count on me, Master Liu Shi!" Luo Feng declared loudly.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li appeared in the sky above Dark Veil Island, then flew away from the island to arrive at the location where his Earthly Deity Avatar was in seclusion.

On the surface of the sea was a huge vortex that was swirling and rumbling incessantly, and it was much more formidable than before.

A hint of elation appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he plunged down into the sea, quickly arriving beside his Earthly Deity Avatar.

The Earthly Deity Avatar was seated with its legs crossed, and there was a huge cocoon of blue light around it, while a thin blue thread was hovering above its head, giving off a burst of formidable water law fluctuations.

Upon sensing Han Li's arrival, the Earthly Deity Avatar ceased in its cultivation before rising to its feet.

"You've made some good progress," Han Li remarked with a nod of approval at the sight of the blue thread above the Earthly Deity Avatar's head.

"Dark Veil Island and the other islands have been developing nicely over the years, and the populations on all of the islands have increased drastically. As a result, there are more worshipers, and therefore more power of faith directed to me, so I've been able to manifest law powers far faster than before," the Dark Veil Island explained.

"Good. At this rate, it won't take long until you fully recover your law powers," Han Li said.

Prior to this, Han Li had injected the Earthly Deity Avatar's water law thread into his Heavy Water True Axis, and he had been concerned that this would cause irreparable damage to the avatar's water law powers, but it seemed that his concerns were unnecessary.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li summoned a small blue flag and three blue flying swords, the latter of which appeared to form a set. On top of that, there was also a light blue storage ring.

"These two are both water-attribute immortal treasures, one for defense and one for offense, while this storage ring holds some things that should be useful to you, as well as some vessels to store heavy water. Take these things and protect the island while I'm away," Han Li instructed.

Dark Veil Island was the first place that he had arrived at during his second ascension to the Immortal Realm, so in some sense, this was his hometown in the Immortal Realm. Even though he had only become the ancestral god here by accident, the people here trusted him deeply and revered him as their deity, so he felt obligated to keep them safe.

The Earthly Deity Avatar accepted these items with a nod, and Han Li issued a few more instructions to it before departing.

Standing high up in the sky, Han Li heaved an internal sigh as he looked down at Dark Veil Island from above.

Following this departure, he didn't know when he would be back again.

He shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought, then flew away into the distance as a streak of azure light, vanishing into the distant sky in the blink of an eye.

Chapter 520: Sneaky Infiltration

Several days later, a streak of light descended outside Black Wind City, then faded to reveal Han Li in a disguised form.

He took a glance at the tall and wide city gate, then made his way into the throngs of people in the city.

The last time he tried to leave the Black Wind Sea, he had attempted to do so by crossing the Soul Stirring Winds, which had proven to be a very arduous experience. Even though his cultivation base had advanced significantly since then, he still had no intention of attempting the same thing again. Instead, he was planning to take the safer approach of using the teleportation array in the city.

After submitting the entrance fee, Han Li made his way into Black Wind City before making his way directly toward the island master's manor.

On the way there, he suddenly stopped in his tracks as he took a glance at the center of the city, then flew in that direction before landing in front of the teleportation plaza.

Bursts of white light were flashing over the teleportation pagoda on the plaza, and it was giving off bursts of tremendous spiritual power fluctuations interspersed with spatial fluctuations.

Han Li knew that this was a sign that the teleportation array had already been activated, and that teleportation was about to be initiated.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he raised a hand to stop a middle-aged Nascent Soul cultivator who was passing by beside him, then said, "Excuse me, Fellow Daoist, I heard that the Black Wind Island Master had declared that the teleportation array was going to be shut down for 1,000 years, so why is it suddenly running again?"

The man was just about to fly into a rage at being stopped by Han Li, but as soon as he detected Han Li's unfathomable aura, he hurriedly put on a fawning smile as he cupped his fist in a salute and replied, "You've must've only recently arrived at Black Wind City, right, Senior? The Black Wind Island Master suddenly declared that the teleportation array was going to be in use again just yesterday, and the teleportation will be initiated at noon today."

"I see. Would you happen to know why the island master suddenly changed his mind?" Han Li asked with a contemplative expression.

"That... I'm afraid not," the middle-aged man replied with a shake of his head.

"Thank you," Han Li replied with a nod, and the middle-aged man cupped his fist in a parting salute before quickly departing.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the teleportation pagoda with a contemplative look on his face, then raised his head to look up at the sun for a moment. All of a sudden, he abruptly vanished from the spot, flying toward the teleportation pagoda as a faint shadow before landing in front of the pagoda's entrance.

The gates of the pagoda were tightly shut, and there were two Black Wind Island cultivators standing guard on either side of them.

Han Li didn't pause even for a moment as he flew straight through the gates in a wraith-like manner. There were several layers of restrictions behind the gates, but none of them were triggered by his intrusion.

At this moment, there were as many as 80 to 90 people inside the pagoda, waiting for the teleportation to be initiated.

Han Li's gaze was immediately drawn to several blue-robed cultivators standing at the forefront of the crowd, and they were none other than Luo Qinghai and the Vast Flow Palace cultivators, while Island Master Lu Jun was standing beside them in a respectful manner.

It seemed that Luo Qinghai had left the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor before him, and he was also trying to leave the Black Wind Sea.

In the next instant, Han Li appeared behind everyone without attracting any attention, then tapped the back of a white-robed young man in front of him with his finger.

A glazed-over look instantly appeared in the young man's eyes, and he turned around before handing a blue talisman over to Han Li, then made his way to the side.

Aside from Luo Qinghai and a few others, no one else in the hall noticed what had just happened.

Luo Qinghai turned to examine Han Li, and a hint of befuddlement flashed through his eyes, but his expression remained completely unchanged.

Meanwhile, Han Li stood on the spot with a calm expression, not shying away from Luo Qinghai's scrutiny at all.

He wasn't hoping to avoid detection from Luo Qinghai and the others in the first place, and it didn't matter to him even if they did notice him.

With his understanding of Luo Qinghai's personality, he knew that he wouldn't make any rash moves in this situation.

Sure enough, Luo Qinghai only inspected Han Li briefly before looking away again, making no effort to expose Han Li.

However, right at this moment, Han Li suddenly turned to another direction, where a group of people were gathered, chatting quietly among themselves.

Han Li's brows furrowed ever so slightly.

Just now, he had detected someone scrutinizing him from that direction, but they had immediately looked away, so he was unable to tell who it was.

However, the fact that they had managed to detect what he had just done indicated that they were definitely also at the Golden Immortal Stage.

A hint of befuddlement flashed through Han Li's eyes upon arriving at this conclusion. Could it be Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni? Or was it someone else?

Before he had a chance to ponder the matter any further, a black-robed elderly man standing beside the teleportation array suddenly stepped forward as he declared, "Sorry to keep you waiting, fellow daoists. It's time, please enter the array."

Everyone that was holding a blue talisman filed into the teleportation array one after another, while the white-robed young man remained rooted to the spot with a dazed look on his face.

Lu Jun's gaze flashed over Han Li momentarily upon seeing this, but he didn't say anything.

The black-robed elderly man flipped a hand over to produce a white array plate, then made a quick string of hand seals, upon which the array plate instantly began to glow with radiant white light.

The teleportation array also began to glow bright, and the dazzling white spiritual light inundated everyone inside the array, following which all of them vanished without a trace.

A hint of relief appeared on Lu Jun's face upon seeing this.

In the instant that everyone was teleported away, the clarity returned to the white-robed young man's eyes, and a panicked look appeared on his face as he exclaimed, "What just happened? Why am I standing here?"

"Get him out of here and return his spirit stones to him," Lu Jun instructed with a dismissive wave of his hand.

A pair of Black Wind Island cultivators instantly heeded his call, escorting the white-robed young man out of the teleportation pagoda.

The black-robed elderly man made his way over to Lu Jun's side as he sighed, "Thank heavens they're finally gone, Island Master!"

"I'm afraid we may not be out of the woods yet," Lu Jun replied with a grim expression.

The black-robed elderly man faltered slightly upon hearing this, while Lu Jun elaborated, "It wasn't just the Vast Flow Palace that entered the immortal manor, yet they're the only ones who have appeared here. What does that entail? To this day, the Immortal Palace cultivators are still nowhere to be found, and on top of that, everyone from the Dawn Fall Sect and the Blaze Dragon Dao has also seemingly vanished into thin air.

“I'm sure something must've happened in the immortal manor. Luo Qinghai claims that he knows nothing, but I highly doubt that. Regardless of what happened, it happened in our Black Wind Sea, so there could still be much more trouble to come."

"I thought that they must've already left the Black Wind Sea through some other avenues. After all, those people are all extremely powerful, and some of them didn't arrive in our Black Wind Sea through the teleportation array in the first place," the black-robed elderly man said in a hesitant manner.

"You're referring to the Soul Stirring Winds, right? We can only pray that they've already left our Black Wind Sea through the Soul Stirring Winds," Lu Jun mused with a wry smile.

"By the way, have you received any news about Young Mistress Yuqing from the people of the Vast Flow Palace?" the black-robed elderly man asked.

"I'm afraid not, but I don't know if they really didn't know anything, or if they were just hiding what they knew from me," Lu Jun replied with a hint of concern in his eyes.

"Young Mistress Yuqing's Origin Soul Lamp is still lit, so she's definitely still alive. Perhaps she's merely trapped somewhere at the moment, and she could be back soon, so don't be too concerned, Island Master," the black-robed elderly man consoled,

Lu Jun offered no response to this, merely heaving a forlorn sigh with tightly furrowed brows.

The black-robed elderly man didn't know what else he could say, so he could only remain silent as well.

Lu Jun stood beside the teleportation array for a moment longer, then heaved another long sigh before turning to depart, but right as he did so, he suddenly spotted a white jade slip on the ground beside the array.

His brows furrowed slightly as he drew the jade slip into his hand, then injected his spiritual sense into it, and he found a short message inside:

"Fellow Daoist Lu Yuqing has encountered an opportunity in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, and she's perfectly safe, so do not be concerned."

An ecstatic look immediately appeared on Lu Jun's face upon seeing this, and all of the concern in his eyes was erased.

He stowed the jade slip away, then extended a deep bow toward the teleportation array, while the black-robed elderly man looked on with a perplexed expression.

......

Han Li's entire field of view was filled with white radiance, and the entire world spun around him in a blur.

Some time later, his vision was restored, and he appeared in another white hall.

Han Li took a glance at his surroundings, and he identified this place to the teleportation hall in Wave View City.

At this moment, there was another group of people standing in a corner of the hall, and they were clearly waiting to be teleported into the Black Wind Sea.

Han Li filed out of the teleportation array with everyone else, then quickly exited the teleportation pagoda.

After that, he promptly departed, quickly vanishing into the crowd on the street outside.

Luo Qinghai and the other Vast Flow Palace cultivators were gathered in a nearby pavilion, and all of them were looking in the direction where Han Li had just faded into the cloud.

"Do you know who he is, Palace Master?" the fair-skinned scholar asked as he withdrew his gaze.

A contemplative look appeared on Luo Qinghai's face as he replied, "I'm not sure, but judging from what he managed to pull off earlier, he has to be a Golden Immortal. I presume that he's currently using a disguise conjured up by a Transient Guild mask, so that's not his true appearance. Were you able to identify him, Meng'er?"

Nan Kemeng was still looking a little weary and frail, and he merely shook his head in response to the question.

"If he's using a Transient Guild mask, then perhaps a member of the Reincarnation Palace," one of the Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals speculated.

"Perhaps, but he could also be from the Blaze Dragon Dao, the Dawn Fall Sect, or some other power. Quite a few cultivators entered the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor on this occasion, and we weren't able to meet all of them," Luo Qinghai said.

"If he's a Golden Immortal, then why is he sneaking around like this? I'm concerned that he may be harboring some ill intentions. Should I send someone to investigate him?" another Golden Immortal asked.

"There's no need to do that. We've already completed our objective for this trip, so it doesn't matter who that man is and what his intentions are. In the wake of everything that had happened here, the Northern Glacial Immortal Region is sure to undergo a period of turmoil, so we have to return to the Vast Flow Palace and make some preparations," Luo Qinghai replied with a shake of his head.

The Golden Immortal was rather disappointed to hear this, but he still nodded in response.

With that, the group continued onward, and Nan Kemeng followed them for a few steps before a layer of peculiar blue light suddenly appeared over his face, then transformed into a thin layer of blue ice crystals.

He immediately swayed momentarily before tipping over, and Luo Qinghai hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of blue light to catch him, while everyone else gathered around to see what had happened.

Chapter 521: Followed

A grim look appeared on Luo Qinghai's face as he made a hand seal, and the ball of white light that had lifted up Nan Kemeng split up into five before entering different parts of his body.

The layer of blue ice crystals on his face quickly faded away, and his trembling also ceased.

"Palace Master, what is wrong with Martial Nephew Nan?" the fair-skinned scholar asked.

"This is not the place to talk. Let's find somewhere to settle down first," Luo Qinghai replied with a grim expression, and the Vast Flow Palace cultivators quickly made their way into Wave View City before taking up residence in a quiet inn.

"Meng'er sustained some severe injuries during the prior battle, and in his injured state, he forcibly activated the Frost Crystal Plaque, resulting in the glacial qi within the plaque entering his meridians. If this isn't addressed in a timely fashion, it could harm his cultivation foundation. I have to immediately use a secret technique to treat his condition.

“I'm sure all of you must be tired after that ordeal in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, so you can all go and rest," Luo Qinghai said to the other Vast Flow Palace cultivators, then made his way into an independent small courtyard behind the inn with Nan Kemeng.

Moments later, a light barrier rose up from within to encompass the entire courtyard.

"Martial Nephew Nan is in good hands with our palace master treating him, so there's no need to be concerned. Let's all go and take a rest," the fair-skinned scholar as he made his way into a nearby courtyard, while the other Vast Flow Palace True Immortals each picked out a courtyard of their own.

However, one of the Golden Immortals among their ranks, an elderly man with a black beard, remained still on the spot for a moment, then made his way into the courtyard that the fair-skinned scholar was staying in.

The fair-skinned scholar was rather surprised to see him, and he asked, "Why aren't you resting, Palace Master Tie?"

"With our cultivation bases, I'm sure that trip was nowhere near enough to tire us out. I came here because I have something to discuss with you, Palace Master Qiu," the elderly man explained as he swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a light barrier.

The fair-skinned scholar's expression remained unchanged upon seeing this, and he prompted, "Go ahead, Palace Master Tie."

"Pardon my intrusion, but may I ask what rewards you've managed to reap from the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace?" the elderly man asked as he lowered his voice slightly.

"Why do you ask this, Palace Master Tie?" the fair-skinned scholar asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"For the sake of reaching the High Zenith Palace as soon as possible, none of us were able to gather many treasures or resources on the way there. To make matters worse, we've expended many treasures, so overall, I would say it was a net loss for all of us. Are you willing to return to the sect like this, Palace Master Qiu?

“Out of the Five Extreme Palaces, we are the only two palace masters to have accompanied Grand Palace Master Luo into the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace. The other three haven't said anything, but I'm sure they're not very pleased. Given Grand Palace Master Luo's personality, if another good opportunity arises in the future, he definitely won't call upon the two of us again," the elderly man said in an indignant manner.

"If you have something to say, then please be more direct about it, Palace Master Tie," the fair-skinned scholar urged in an indifferent voice.

"In that case, I'll keep it concise. Even though we haven't reaped many spoils on this trip, that doesn't mean that others haven't," the elderly man said in a meaningful voice as he pointed outside.

"You're referring to that man from earlier?" the fair-skinned scholar asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"That's right. Seeing as he just came out of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, he must be carrying plenty of precious treasures and resources with him. Even if his luck in the immortal manor was quite lackluster, the entire wealth of a Golden Immortal is still enough to cover our losses," the elderly man said.

A contemplative look appeared on the fair-skinned scholar's face upon hearing this, but he then immediately shook his head as he said, "No, we can't do that. We don't know who that man is, and Grand Palace Master Luo has already told us to leave him be."

"This may come across as a little disrespectful, but of course Grand Palace Master Luo is unwilling to get involved in this matter, considering he's already achieved his objective of securing a High Zenith Pill. In contrast, we're still both completely empty-handed!" the elderly man said.

"How could you say that about Grand Palace Master Luo? Everything that he's doing is for the sake of our Vast Flow Palace's future!" the fair-skinned scholar said in a cold voice.

The elderly man gave a cold harrumph in response. "I have no intention of slandering Grand Palace Master Luo. That man left in quite a hurry after spotting us, so he's definitely not an ally of ours. In that case, he could be an enemy of our sect, so why shouldn't we take advantage of this opportunity to eliminate him?"

"I suppose you're right. The problem is that his cultivation base is unclear, so even if we join forces, we may not be guaranteed to be able to take him down," the fair-skinned scholar mused with a hesitant expression.

An elated look immediately appeared on the elderly man's face upon hearing this, and he said, "Not to worry, Palace Master Qiu."

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, and two bursts of yellow light shot out of his hand, then transformed into a pair of earthy yellow puppets that were giving off formidable auras intermingled with hints of law power fluctuations.

However, both puppets were quite severely damaged, and the auras that were emanating from them were also fluctuating in a rather unsteady fashion.

"These are Golden Immortal Stage puppets!" the fair-skinned scholar exclaimed as a hint of greed flashed through his eyes.

"With these two puppets on our side, I'm sure you'll have no further qualms, right, Palace Master Qiu?" the elderly man chuckled.

"I didn't think you would have such formidable puppets in your possession. With these two puppets on our side, we'll surely be able to take him down," the fair-skinned scholar replied as a decisive look appeared on his face.

Moments later, the two of them slipped silently out of the inn, then flew away into the distance.

......

Han Li emerged from a materials shop, holding a jade box with a pleased look on his face.

Inside the jade box were some Nightlight Herb seeds, a type of spirit plant that was only found on the Primordial Wave Continent.

The Nightlight Herb was the final ingredient that he was missing for refining Infernal Azure Pills, a Golden Immortal Stage pill in the Huanan Pill Scripture.

Nightlight Herbs were quite rare on the Primordial Wave Continent, so he wasn't actually very confident that he would be able to find seeds of this spirit plant here, and this discovery had come as a very pleasant surprise. Even though he had only managed to secure some seeds, as opposed to actual specimens of the spirit plant, it made virtually no difference to him.

After stowing the jade box away, Han Li quickly left Wave View City, flying away as a streak of azure light and vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

Not long after his departure, two faint shadows also flew out of the city, trailing along some distance behind him.

Han Li didn't immediately summon the green jade flying carriage. The flying carriage once belonged to Gongshu Jiu, and even though there was most likely no one in Wave View City who recognized it, it was still better to take a more cautious approach and only summon the carriage once he was a bit further away from the city.

As he flew through the air, he flipped a hand over to summon the white jade slip that had been given to him by Wyrm 3, which contained the route that he could take to leave the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

According to the jade slip, the starting point of the route was a location somewhere in the southwest of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face as he traced his finger over the jade slip in an absentminded manner.

Even though Wyrm 3 had told him two routes through which he could leave the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, it was clearly not feasible for him to leave through the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace's interregion gate.

Even though his Reincarnation Palace mask still hadn't been exposed yet, the Reincarnation Palace was a sworn enemy of the Heavenly Court, so there was no guarantee that the Heavenly Court didn't have any ways to see through Reincarnation Palace masks.

Hence, the only option available to him was to cross the primordial land.

However, he naturally wasn't going to blindly trust Wyrm 3, so he had to verify through some other avenues that this was indeed a feasible route to take.

Aside from that, he also had to make a trip to the Ancient Cloud Continent prior to his departure.

All of a sudden, Han Li swept his gaze across the surrounding area. He discovered that he was already very far away from Wave View City, and he immediately swung around as he yelled, "Who's there? Come out and face me!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, a masked elderly man appeared ahead of him amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the masked elderly man, and he said, "I don't believe we've met before. Why have you followed me all this way?"

Even though the elderly man's entire body was enshrouded within a burst of invisible force, Han Li was struck by a sense of familiarity at the sight of him.

The masked elderly offered no response as he made a hand seal, and nine streaks of golden light shot out of his sleeve, then transformed into nine golden flying swords.

There were countless white runes swirling around the flying swords like radiant white flames, and they swelled rapidly to over 1,000 feet in length each, then arranged themselves into a line to form a formidable sword dragon that swooped down toward Han Li with tremendous power.

Even before the white sword dragon descended upon Han Li, a burst of incredible sharp law powers erupted out of its body, causing the surrounding space to tremble and warp.

However, Han Li was completely unfazed by this, and a mocking sneer appeared on his face as he made a hand seal.

A burst of golden light flashed over his body, and a layer of thick golden fur emerged over his skin as he transformed into a giant golden ape that was several thousand feet tall in the blink of an eye.

The giant ape made a grabbing motion with one hand, and a dark green sword instantly appeared in its grasp. This was none other than one of the three immortal swords that he had just obtained from the storage bracelet that he had dug up from the seabed.

As soon as the green sword was summoned, all of the spirit patterns on its surface instantly lit up, and it swelled to over 1,000 feet in size while giving off a burst of tremendous law power fluctuations.

The golden ape then let loose a thunderous roar as it swung its giant green sword into the white sword dragon, and the two bursts of opposing law powers clashed with an earth-shattering boom.

The white light around the white sword dragon was instantly destroyed, as were the law power fluctuations that it was releasing, following which the entire sword dragon itself was sent flying like a ragdoll.

As the sword dragon tumbled through the air, it split back up into nine golden flying swords, every single one of which had dimmed significantly, clearly indicating that their spiritual nature had been severely damaged.

A stunned look flashed through the masked elderly man's eyes upon seeing this, but right at this moment, a vast expanse of black mist surged out of the nearby space in a frenzy, and it instantly encompassed the entire surrounding area in a radius of several dozen kilometers.

An elated look appeared on the elderly man's face upon seeing this, and he immediately vanished into the black mist.

Enshrouded within the cloud of black mist, Han Li found himself trapped in a turbulent black sea, immediately following which a series of black sea beasts came pouncing at him from all directions.

All of these sea beasts were as enormous as mountains, and their auras indicated that they were all at the Golden Immortal Stage!

Chapter 522: Joyful Reunion

The giant ape didn't panic in the slightest upon seeing this, and it harrumphed coldly, "Are you really expecting to fool me with such a weak illusion?"

It then slashed its giant green sword horizontally through the air, instantly unleashing a burst of tremendous force that swept outward in all directions.

The surrounding illusion was unable to put up any resistance as it was instantly eradicated, and the original setting re-emerged.

However, at this point, a pair of yellow puppets had appeared on either side of the golden ape, and they were no more than 100 feet away. Both of the puppets were glowing with radiant yellow light that was interspersed with bursts of formidable law power fluctuations.

The two puppets swung their arms through the air, and two balls of yellow light flew out of their bodies, transforming into a pair of yellow dragons that were thousands of feet in length.

The two yellow dragons wrapped themselves around the golden ape's arms in the blink of an eye, binding them into place like a pair of chains.

Right at this moment, the masked elderly man reappeared in front of the golden ape, while another white-robed masked figure emerged behind it.

As soon as the masked elderly man appeared, he immediately made a hand seal, and the nine golden flying swords shot forth once again, fusing as one mid-flight to form an enormous golden sword that was over 1,000 feet in length.

The huge white sword swept through the air in an arc, forming an enormous white sword wheel as it hurtled toward the golden ape while giving off a burst of law power fluctuations that were even more formidable than those of the white sword dragon from before.

At the same time, a burst of dark azure light flew out of his body before transforming into a massive hammer.

Balls of dark azure flames emerged over the hammer, and they were giving off a glacial aura as the hammer swept toward the golden ape.

Meanwhile, the white-robed man swept a sleeve through the air to release an inky-black wooden ruler, which swelled to over 1,000 feet in length in the blink of an eye before crashing down toward the golden ape with tremendous force.

A cloud of black mist was swirling around the giant black ruler, and it came crashing down like an enormous mountain, causing the nearby space to warp and buzz incessantly.

At the same time, the man opened his mouth to release a string of around a dozen purple beads, all of which were giving off an astonishingly fearsome lightning aura.

The golden ape was completely unfazed by all of this, and bright purplish-golden light erupted out of its body as a layer of purplish-golden scales emerged over its fur. At the same time, a pair of heads and two pairs of arms appeared on its shoulders and beneath its ribs, respectively, instantly transforming it into a purplish-golden devilish deity with three heads and six arms.

The devilish deity grabbed onto the pair of yellow dragons that were wrapped around its arm with its four free hands, then made a violent wrenching motion.

A burst of indescribably tremendous power erupted out of its body, causing the nearby space to ripple and compress to an extreme degree.

A resounding boom rang out as the pair of yellow dragons were torn apart as if they were made of tofu, then disintegrated into a vast cloud of yellow mist.

Immediately thereafter, all of the spirit patterns on the devilish deity's body lit up, and the immortal spiritual power in its body surged into the giant green sword in its hand like a turbulent sea, causing the silver runes on the surface of the sword to glow several times brighter than before.

As the sword was swung through the air, it released a burst of mountainous interspersed with law power fluctuations in all directions, threatening to tear the very space apart.

A string of thunderous booms rang out as the two puppets, the white sword wheel, the dark azure hammer, and the giant black ruler were all sent flying like weightless feathers as soon as they came into contact with the almighty green sword.

As for the purple lightning beads, all of them exploded into vast balls of purple light upon contact with the giant green sword, and they were giving off bursts of formidable lightning law fluctuations.

However, these purple balls of light were then instantly inundated and swept away by a wave of dark green swordlight.

The masked elderly man and the white-robed man shuddered violently as they were also sent flying back through the air, and they stumbled back for several thousand feet before finally managing to steady themselves.

Both of them had blood flowing down the corners of their lips, and they were utterly astonished by the unfathomable power of their opponent.

The white-robed man gave the masked elderly man a vicious glare, then immediately turned and fled into the distance, doing so in such a hurry that he was even leaving his black ruler behind.

The masked elderly also immediately fled the scene upon seeing this, but the devilish deity wasn't about to let them get away, and it chuckled coldly, "Why don't you stay and keep me company?"

Immediately thereafter, the Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind it, releasing waves of golden ripples that instantly spread through the surrounding area in a radius of over 10,000 feet, encompassing both the masked elderly man and the white-robed man within them.

The white-robed man's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and a look of immense horror and regret appeared in his eyes as he exclaimed, "You're Li..."

Before he had a chance to finish his sentence, his voice was abruptly cut off as the time-slowing effect of the Mantra Treasured Axis took hold, and the masked elderly man was also completely rooted to the spot.

Meanwhile, the devilish deity looked down at the giant green sword in its hand as it gave a pleased nod.

The enormous weight of the sword and the immense destructive law powers that it contained made it an ideal weapon to use in this form.

Han Li made a hand seal, quickly reverting back to his human form, and the giant green sword also returned to its original size.

He then stowed the sword away before turning his gaze to the pair of immobilized figures within the nearby golden ripples.

He made his way over to white-robed man, then tore off his mask to reveal none other than the fair-skinned scholar from the Vast Flow Palace.

He raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, then strode over to the masked elderly man before removing his mask as well, and he was able to identify the elderly man as another one of the Vast Flow Palace's Golden Immortals.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as grabbed onto the elderly man's head, and bursts of black light emerged over his fingertips before vanishing into the elderly man's head.

Golden Immortal Stage nascent souls were extremely resilient, so under normal circumstances, soul search techniques were very difficult to execute, but the task was made far easier by the time-slowing effect of the Mantra Treasured Axis.

Moments later, Han Li removed his hand from the elderly man's head, and by then, he had already determined their motive for coming after him.

The elderly man's eyes had bulged slightly outward, but the light within them hadn't faded.

Han Li was just about to destroy both of their nascent souls when he suddenly stopped what he was doing, and a contemplative look appeared on his face.

"I suppose it's your lucky day," Han Li harrumphed coldly as he flicked a finger through the air, releasing a pair of crimson fireballs that landed upon his two assailants, quickly incinerating their bodies into ashes, leaving only a pair of storage tools and a pair of nascent souls behind.

Han Li then swept a sleeve through the to release a burst of azure light that drew the pair of nascent souls into his grasp, following which he plastered a purple talisman to each of their heads.

A series of purple runes instantly emerged over the pair of talismans to restrict the two nascent souls, and only then did he stow them away.

After that, he seized their storage tools, the surrounding immortal treasures, as well as the pair of yellow puppets, then withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis.

All of the surrounding golden ripples faded away in a flash, and Han Li took a glance at Wave View City before quickly withdrawing his gaze.

Right as he was about to depart, the sound of applause suddenly rang out.

"As expected of one of the paramount laws. That was truly a formidable display!"

"Who's there?"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he cast his gaze toward a certain spot, and a pair of figures immediately appeared there.

Much to Han Li's elation, they were none other than Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni, and he made his way over to them as he said, "I'm glad to see you're both safe and well, fellow daoists!"

"I can see that you're also doing just fine, Fellow Daoist Li," Daoist Hu Yan chuckled.

"When did you two get here?" Han Li asked.

"We only just got here, and we arrived just in time to see that impressive display! The five Golden Immortal Stage palace masters of the Five Extreme Vast Flow Palaces are all vastly renowned figures in the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, yet they couldn't even put up any resistance against you!" Daoist Hu Yan praised.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Hu Yan. They were simply oblivious to my identity and caught off guard. If they had known who I was from the beginning, then it wouldn't have been so easy for me to defeat them," Han Li replied in a modest manner.

"Sorry for leaving you behind on your own to face Gongshu Jiu and Mo Yu," Daoist Hu Yan said with a hint of apology in his eyes.

Yun Ni didn't say anything, but she also extended an apologetic curtsey toward Han Li with a guilty look on her face.

"Don't worry about it. The situation at the time demanded for such measures to be taken. We're all alive and well now, so there's no need to apologize for such trivial things. You've always been a really straightforward man, since when were you the type to get hung up over these things, Fellow Daoist Hu Yan?" Han Li jibed.

"Well, you've certainly become a lot more carefree than before!" Daoist Hu Yan chuckled, while a smile also appeared on Yun Ni's face, and with that, they were once again just a trio of old friends enjoying each other's company.

"We almost died on quite a few occasions back in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, and the fact that we've survived is very much worthy of celebration. Let's have a drink! Yun Ni doesn't like drinking much, and it's been really boring drinking on my own," Daoist Hu Yan said as he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a table and some chairs in mid-air.

"So you're saying that you don't enjoy my company?" Yun Ni asked as her expression darkened slightly.

"Of course not!" Daoist Hu Yan hurriedly replied. "What I'm saying is that I don't enjoy drinking on my own. Of course I love having you around!"

Yun Ni gave a displeased harrumph and turned away to ignore Daoist Hu Yan.

An amused smile appeared on Han Li's face at the sight of their lovers' quarrel, and he sat down onto one of the chairs as he declared, "I agree that a celebration is in order. Let's all have a drink!"

"Fantastic! No matter what happens from here, whether that be the entire immortal region being swept up into turmoil, or the Vast Flow Palace reigning supreme as the only dominant force, none of that matters here and now. Today, all we're going to focus on is drinking to our hearts' content!" Daoist Hu Yan agreed as he also eagerly sat down.

"Seeing as Fellow Daoist Li is with us, I'll let you off the hook for now. Otherwise..."

Yun Ni's voice trailed off as she gave Daoist Hu Yan a cold glare, following which she also sat down.

"You really saved my skin there, Brother. I owe you one!" Daoist Hu Yan said to Han Li in a grateful voice through voice transmission, while Han Li merely smiled in response.

Chapter 523: A Drink with Old Friends

Daoist Hu Yan swept a sleeve through the air, and a burst of red light flashed over the table, upon which an orange wine jar appeared. The jar was around a foot in height, and judging from the antiquated patterns engraved onto its surface, it was clearly a very old jar of wine.

Even before the jar was opened, it was already releasing a mesmerizing aroma throughout the surrounding area.

Having discussed wine on so many past occasions with Daoist Hu Yan, Han Li had accumulated a great deal of knowledge on the subject, and he immediately exclaimed, "This is exceptional wine! Judging from its fragrance, this must be Seasonal Dream, right?"

"Precisely! This jar of Seasonal Dream was brewed using Cloudborn Fruits as the main ingredient, and I had to spend countless years brewing it," Daoist Hu Yan said as he removed the stopper from the jar, then conjured up three pristine white cups, all of which he filled with wine.

The wine was as clear and pure as a mirror, and it had a light red hue that was further accentuated by the white cup that it had been poured into.

Han Li took a sip, and his eyes instantly lit up as he praised, "This is indeed exceptional wine!"

As soon as the wine flowed into his mouth, it immediately transformed into a burst of heat that was as mellow as a cloud, filling his entire body with a sense of warm comfort.

On top of that, the wine also contained immense immortal spiritual power, instantly replenishing the immortal spiritual power that he had expended during his battle against the two palace masters.

"Of course! My cultivation aptitude can only be described as decent at best, but when it comes to brewing wine, just this jar of Seasonal Dream alone is sufficient testament to prove that I'm unmatched in the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region!" Daoist Hu Yan replied in a proud manner.

"As soon as you have a bit to drink, you immediately start bragging like a fool!" Yun Ni scolded with a displeased expression, but she also took a small sip of wine from her cup.

The three of them exchanged some small talk, then began to talk about what had happened after they had parted ways in the immortal manor.

As it turned out, following Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni's departure, they immediately hid somewhere secluded, but not long thereafter, they were teleported out of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor and ended up in the Black Wind Sea.

After some discussion, the two of them decided not to brave the Soul Stirring Winds again. Instead, they had the same idea of leaving the Black Wind Sea through the teleportation array. However, they encountered the Vast Flow Palace's cultivators there, so they disguised themselves before entering the teleportation pagoda.

"I knew it! Prior to stepping into the array, I detected two familiar auras nearby. That was you two, right?" Han Li chuckled.

"Indeed. I didn't think you would have the courage to blatantly steal a teleportation spot right under the noses of the Vast Flow Palace cultivators! I have to say, I was really impressed at the time," Daoist Hu Yan also chuckled in response.

"By the time I got to Black Wind City, it was already right on the cusp of the scheduled teleportation, so I didn't have much of a choice," Han Li explained with a smile.

"How did you fare against Gongshu Jiu after we left, Fellow Daoist Li?" Yun Ni suddenly asked, and a serious look appeared on Daoist Hu Yan's face upon hearing this.

"Gongshu Jiu is already dead," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice as he took another sip of wine.

Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni had already guessed that this would be the outcome, considering Han Li was alive and well, but they were still very much taken aback by this answer.

"Your powers are truly unfathomable, Fellow Daoist Li. To think that even a High Zenith cultivator is no longer a match for you. Your cultivation aptitude is truly unmatched!" Yun Ni said as she raised her cup with a hint of admiration in her eyes.

"Even back in the Blaze Dragon Dao, I knew that there was something special about you, but never in my wildest dreams could I have imagined that you would come so far in just a few centuries!" Daoist Hu Yan chuckled as he also raised his cup.

"You're far too kind, fellow daoists. Gongshu Jiu died by the hand of multiple people, and I only made a very minor contribution," Han Li said in a modest manner.

"Then what about that Gray Immortal?" Daoist Hu Yan asked.

"The Gray Immortal immediately left following Gongshu Jiu's demise, and he didn't target me. After that, I left the High Zenith Palace, but I was also suddenly teleported out of the immortal manor shortly thereafter. There was still supposed to be some time left until the closing of the immortal manor, so I presume someone was pulling strings behind the scenes," Han Li replied, refraining from telling the two about Mo Yu and Lu Yuqing.

"Indeed, there's a very good chance that the Gray Immortal was controlling everything from the very beginning. I've heard that he has some ties with the Infernal Frost Immortal Lord, and he was also clearly very familiar with all of the restrictions in the High Zenith Palace. It's a good thing that he's not a bloodthirsty individual. Otherwise, even if we managed to kill Gongshu Jiu, there's no way we would've been able to escape from him," Daoist Hu Yan mused.

"We were indeed very fortunate. While it's true that he's a Gray Immortal, his personality seems to be different from what Gray Immortals are said to be like," Han Li remarked.

"The death of an immortal envoy is a very important matter, and I'm almost certain that there will be a new immortal envoy sent to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region soon to investigate this matter. All of those immortal envoys are skilled in secret techniques that allow them to identify members of the Reincarnation Palace, so do be careful," Daoist Hu Yan cautioned with a serious expression.

"Thank you for the warning, Fellow Daoist Hu Yan. I'll be sure to keep myself well-concealed from here onward," Han Li replied.

"With your powers, as long as you remain on your guard, you should be fine. If you can't stay in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, then just leave," Daoist Hu Yan advised.

"Do you know of a way to leave the Northern Glacial Immortal Region?" Han Li asked with an intrigued expression.

"I heard from Dao Lord Baili that there exists an interregion gate in the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace that leads to other immortal regions. However, apparently, each teleportation expends an enormous amount of resources, so even the palace master may not be able to use it whenever he pleases. Hence, that's most likely out of the question.

“Even if we manage to force our way to the interregion gate, we'll most likely be confronted by immortal envoys sent by the Heavenly Court before we manage to figure out how to activate the gate," Daoist Hu Yan replied.

"I've also heard about this. If this is an unfeasible route to take, then are there any alternatives?" Han Li asked.

"The alternative option would be to cross the primordial land between immortal regions. However, I've heard that such a journey is no less perilous than forcing our way into the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, and even a High Zenith cultivator isn't guaranteed to be able to make the journey safely. Having said that, it's said that the Reincarnation Palace has carved out a relatively safe passageway through primordial land, but I don't know where this route is," Daoist Hu Yan replied.

Han Li nodded in response.

It seemed that Wyrm 3 had been telling him the truth.

"Fellow Daoist Li, the perils of the primordial land come primarily from how unchartered and unexplored it is. Many cultivators have tried to cross through it in the past, but most of them haven't lived to tell the tale, so I advise you not to pursue that path unless it's absolutely necessary," Yun Ni cautioned.

"Thank you for the advice, fellow daoists. I'll be sure to consider this matter carefully. May I ask what your plans are from here onward? Now that your identities have been exposed, I'm sure the Heavenly Court will be coming after you as well," Han Li said.

"We'll be sure to be on our guard as well, so there's no need for you to worry about us. To tell you the truth, Dao Lord Baili has already taken the High Zenith Pill, and a breakthrough to the High Zenith Stage is imminent for him. Once that time comes, we won't have to fear any immortal envoys!" Daoist Hu Yan replied.

"In that case, I'll be offering my congratulations to Dao Lord Baili in advance," Han Li said with a smile.

"At the moment, Dao Lord Baili is working on refining the High Zenith Pill, so he won't be able to come out of seclusion to see you. However, he's also very interested in you, so if we get a chance to meet again in the future, let's all share a drink together!" Daoist Hu Yan said with a wide smile.

"That sounds great to me," Han Li replied with a smile.

After that, the three of them began to discuss the state of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region and what the future likely held, following which the conversation shifted to sharing cultivation insights and experiences.

The jar of wine was quickly finished, but Daoist Hu Yan had a virtually endless stash of fine wines, and he immediately brought out a new jar.

The time flew by in a flash, and before long, day had already transitioned into night.

The three of them were thoroughly enjoying one another's company, and they were reluctant to part ways, but it was time to say their goodbyes.

"It's about time that we left, Fellow Daoist Li. Look after yourself!" Daoist Hu Yan declared as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

"Same to you, fellow daoists," Han Li replied with a nod.

Daoist Hu Yan stowed the table and chairs away, then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of fiery red light that encompassed both himself and Yun Ni.

The two of them then rose up into the sky before flying toward the setting sun in the distance, quickly fading out of sight.

Han Li stood with his hands clasped behind his back while his robes flapped audibly around him in the wind, remaining as still as a statue as he looked on at the setting sun.

A short while later, he swept a sleeve through the air to summon the green jade flying carriage, then sped away in another direction.

Chapter 524: Visiting a Place of Old

Heavenly Cloud City, Ancient Cloud Continent.

It was the end of another year. For cultivators, this was just another insignificant moment in their long and busy lives, but for mortals, this was the most important time of the year.

Light snow was falling from the sky, and aside from some inns and taverns inhabited by cultivators, the rest of the city was completely covered in a blanket of snow. In accordance with an old tradition passed down from time immemorial, newly cut-down peach tree branches were stuck into the snow between the window frames, while vibrant and colorful couplets had been stuck onto the door frames.

The sun had already set, and dusk was transitioning into night.

On a street to the east of Heavenly Cloud City, all of the shops had put up large red lanterns, illuminating the entire street with a festive red glow.

There was steam rising up all over the street as all types of hot foods were being sold, and all of the merchants were loudly advertising their wares, giving the street a lively and bustling atmosphere.

A petite and beautiful young woman wearing a red cloak was currently slowly walking along the street with a delectable tanghulu in her hand.

Her entire face was concealed within the large hood of her cloak, and there was a lonesome look on her face.

"Big Brother and the others aren't here, and Master Li is still gone... I'm all alone..." she sighed to herself in a dejected voice before taking a bite out of her tanghulu.

Right at this moment, she suddenly raised her head, and she spotted a tall azure-robed man at the end of the street, approaching her with a smile on his face.

Her eyes instantly sprang wide open with incredulity, and she hurriedly swallowed the mouthful of tanghulu before hurriedly rushing over to him.

Only when she had almost reached him did she notice that there was an adorable little girl by his side, grabbing onto his robe with both hands as she looked around with a curious expression.

"Master Li!"

The young woman immediately removed her hood upon reaching the azure-robed man, then extended a respectful curtsey.

The man was none other than Han Li, who had traveled all the way here from the Primordial Wave Continent, while the woman was Meng Qianqian.

"No need for formalities. I entered the city through the eastern gate, and I just so happened to sense your aura, so I came to pay you a visit," Han Li said with a smile.

Jin Tong's gaze had been drawn to all of the food being sold along the street, but she turned her attention to Meng Qianqian before pursing her lips slightly in disdain as she asked, "Who's this, Uncle? Her cultivation base is so low, and her aptitude is also terrible!"

An exasperated look appeared on Han Li's face as he scolded, "Don't be so rude! She's your junior martial sister!"

Meng Qianqian lowered her head in a slightly embarrassed manner, then said, "It's a pleasure to meet you, Senior Martial Sister."

"I have a junior martial sister now!" Jin Tong immediately exclaimed in delight, then summoned a vial of pills before tossing them at Meng Qianqian. "Here, this is for you."

None of the mortals dared to stop and stare at Han Li's trio, but Han Li could tell that they were all sneaking furtive glances their way, so he said, "Let's get back to the Moonview Forest first. I have some things to tell you."

"Yes, Master Li!" Meng Qianqian hurriedly replied.

"It smells so good here! I want to eat first before we go," Jin Tong protested as she caught a whiff of the fragrant aroma wafting out of a nearby restaurant.

Han Li naturally didn't dare to leave her here on her own. If she were left unchecked, she could easily eat the entire city!

Hence, he had no choice but to comply with her demands. "Alright, let's have some food then. It's been a long time since I've had mortal food myself."

"Which shop has the best food?" Jin Tong asked in an eager voice, and she was barely able to contain her own salivation.

"Are there any larger restaurants nearby?" Han Li asked as he turned to Meng Qianqian, who hurriedly nodded in response.

"There are two large restaurants nearby. I can take you to them right away."

He had explored the city quite extensively during her time here, so she was very familiar with the food being sold here, and she immediately led Han Li and Jin Tong to the nearest large restaurant.

However, Jin Tong was already unable to wait any longer, and she was drawn to a steamed bun stall on the side of the street.

"The steamed lamb buns here are quite popular. We can have some of them first," Meng Qianqian suggested.

Han Li nodded in response, and the three of them sat down at the stall.

The stall waiter could tell that these three were no ordinary customers, and he hurriedly rushed over to them with a warm smile as he asked, "What would you like to order? Our steamed lamb buns are the best in the city!"

"We'll have three steamers of lamb buns and three bowls of lamb offal soup," Meng Qianqian ordered as she pulled out a silver ingot.

"Coming right up!" the waiter declared before departing, and it didn't take long before the order was brought to the table.

Jin Tong was already at her limit, and she grabbed into a steamed lamb bun, which was even larger than both of her hands combined, then sank her teeth into it.

The soft and sumptuous steamed bun instantly split open, and the golden soup inside spilled into her mouth, bringing with it a delectably meaty aroma.

A blissful look appeared on her face as she began to munch down the steamed bun at an incredible speed.

The waiter was very alarmed to see this, fearing that she would burn herself on the piping hot steamed buns, but before he had a chance to say anything, the first bun was already finished, and Jin Tong wiped the oil from her lips before stuffing a second bun into her mouth.

As she ate, her movements became faster and faster, and by the end, it as as if the steamed buns were being zapped out of existence, vanishing into thin air one after another.

All the while, the waiter gawked on with his mouth agape.

"These steamed lamb buns are incredible, Uncle! Get me 100, no, 1,000 steamers of these!" Jin Tong yelled with an ecstatic expression.

Not only was the waiter completely rooted to the spot, even the other diners had all turned to look at her.

"Are they really that good?" Han Li chuckled.

"They are!" Jin Tong insisted as she smacked her lips.

"How many more steamed buns do you have? We'll take them all," Han Li said as he turned to the waiter with a smile.

The waiter was still reeling from what he had seen, so he didn't reply right away.

Han Li thought that the waiter was concerned that he wouldn't have enough money to pay for the meal, and he was just about to pull out some silver when he realized that he didn't have a single tael of silver on him, only a mountain of Immortal Origin Stones.

Ironically, he was too rich to afford food in this city!

Meng Qianqian immediately came to his rescue, flipping a hand over to place a mid-grade spirit stone onto the table.

Compared with the mortals of the Spirit Realm and the Mortal Realm, those of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region generally lived longer and were healthier. Even though the most commonly used forms of currency among them were still silver and gold, they were not unfamiliar with immortal currencies like spirit stones.

Spirit stones contained the world's origin qi, so even though a mortal couldn't directly absorb spiritual power from them, they could still carry spirit stones around to extend their lifespans and improve their health.

Hence, spirit stones were a type of premium currency that was extremely sought after among the upper class.

However, the spirit stone that Meng Qianqian had just pulled out was of a far better quality than normal spirit stones, making it a very rare sight in the mortal world, and it instantly attracted everyone's attention.

Thankfully, the female boss of the stall had also had her attention drawn to Han Li's table by all the commotion, and after taking a glance at the mid-grade spirit stone on the table, she knew that it was her lucky day.

She immediately hurried over to the table with a wide smile as she said, "I'm extremely honored that you think so highly of my steamed buns, esteemed customers, but this spirit stone is far too precious for me."

Despite what she was saying, she had already silently slipped the spirit stone into her pocket.

After that, she declared that her stall was closed for business, then respectfully urged everyone to return the next day. All of the other customers could also tell that Han Li's trio were no ordinary people, so they duly obliged. Only as they turned their attention back to their own tables did they realize that all of their steamed buns had already disappeared.

"This stuff tastes much better than treasures!" Jin Tong exclaimed with an ecstatic expression.

"Senior Martial Sister, you... you normally eat treasures?" Meng Qianqian asked with a stunned expression.

"Of course," Jin Tong replied as if it were the most normal thing in the world. "What other good stuff is there to eat?"

"There's a ton of delicious food being sold on this street," Meng Qianqian hurriedly replied, then began to rattle off a list of available foods, while Jin Tong listened with a pair of enraptured eyes.

"I don't know what any of those things are, but they all sound really delicious! Let's finish up here, then take me to the next shop!" she urged as she wiped away the drool that was threatening to dribble down her chin.

Right at this moment, the waiter arrived at the table with 10 more steamers of buns, all of which were sucked into Jin Tong's belly in an instant.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he took a sip of his lamb offal soup.

The soup was a little murky, and it was very flavorful, and it filled his stomach with a sense of gentle warmth.

This was something that he hadn't experienced in a very log time.

Han Li had already forgotten the last time he had enjoyed such mortal delicacies, and that sip of soup instantly sent him on a trip down memory lane, evoking memories of the small village in the Mortal Realm that had been his first home.

He looked around at the lively and bustling street, and he couldn't help but heave an internal sigh.

Having spent all his time cultivating, a change of scenery was quite a pleasant experience.

Chapter 525: Bottomless Pit

It was all hands on deck in the kitchen of the steamed bun shop as steamer after steamer of freshly cooked steamed lamb buns were brought to Han Li's table one after another.

Jin Tong was eating non-stop, and it didn't take long before she had gobbled down 70 steamers of buns, while a small crowd of astonished onlookers had gathered nearby.

Han Li didn't want to attract excessive attention, so even though Jin Tong was still eager for more, he dragged her away to the next shop, this one a shaobing shop.

The shop was run by only two people, an elderly man who was close to 80 years of age and his grandson. As a result, they were unable to churn out shaobing as quickly as the steamed bun shop, and it didn't take long before they ran out of food to serve Jin Tong.

Shaobing was one of the most commonplace food items in the mortal world, but the elderly man had over 60 years of experience in cooking shaobing, and during that time, he had made many innovations to the simple dish, setting his shaobing apart from the rest.

Jin Tong was thoroughly impressed, and she immediately declared that the elderly man had to be rewarded, a request that Meng Qianqian happily obliged.

This was the first time that the elderly man had sold so many shaobing in one night, and he could tell Jin Tong truly loved his food, so he was also extremely pleased, praising Jin Tong for her voracious appetite.

After the bill was paid, Meng Qianqian took Jin Tong to eat glutinous rice balls cooked in fermented wine.

Thankfully, the shopkeeper of the stall had already prepared a large pot full of rice balls with all types of fillings, and the entire pot of rice balls was purchased by Han Li.

It didn't take long before news of Jin Tong's extraordinary feats of consumption spread across the entire street.

As a result, all of the shopkeepers were urging their chefs to cook up as much food as humanly possible in anticipation for Jin Tong's visit.

They had even set up tables on the street outside, and whatever food that was churned out was immediately carried out of the kitchen and onto the tables.

Jin Tong was ecstatic to see this, and she swept through the street like a hurricane, eating everything in her wake while Meng Qianqian footed the bill.

Deep into the night, all of the shops that had been visited by Jin Tong had already run out of food and closed for the night, while the rest of the shops that she was still yet to visit were still open,and there were many shopkeepers standing on the street outside, eagerly awaiting her arrival.

It was said that not only did Jin Tong possess an extraordinary appetite, she was also extremely generous, and anyone who could serve up food that was to her liking would be rewarded. Furthermore, as opposed to silver, her rewards were issued in the form of mid-grade spirit stones, with some shops even receiving high-grade spirit stones, which were extremely sought after even among cultivators!

Meng Qianqian didn't have much savings to begin with, and it didn't take long before she ran out of money. Before she even had a chance to say anything, Han Li casually tossed a storage pouch at her.

As soon as she inspected the pouch's contents with her spiritual sense, she was instantly rooted to the spot.

The pouch was filled with over 10,000 top-grade spirit stones!

Han Li had taken the storage pouch from one of the Golden Immortals that he had slain in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, and in this rare moment of relaxation, he was more than happy to spend some money so that Jin Tong could enjoy a good time.

Finally, the three of them arrived at one of the large restaurants that Meng Qianqian mentioned, and the shopkeeper was a short man dressed in a silken robe.

As soon as Han Li's trio arrived at the entrance of the restaurant, he immediately rushed out before greeting them with a wide smile.

Han Li noticed that the shopkeeper was a late-Foundation Establishment cultivator, and he asked, "Do you have any vacant seats upstairs?"

"Certainly! Please come with me, esteemed customers," the shopkeeper immediately replied before leading the way up the stairs.

Upon reaching the upper floor, Han Li discovered that it was still brightly lit, but there weren't any other customers inside, perhaps because it was too late at night, or perhaps the entire floor had been vacated by the shopkeeper in anticipation for Jin Tong's visit.

The three of them took a seat by a window-side table, following which Meng Qianqian instructed, "Fill all of these tables with your finest dishes and wine."

The shopkeeper was ecstatic to hear this, and he immediately gave an affirmative response before rushing downstairs.

Meanwhile, Jin Tong was still holding a large cake in her hands, and for some reason, she was only taking small bites out of it at a time with a blissful look on her little face.

"Why are you the only one here? Where is your brother?" Han Li suddenly asked as he turned to Meng Qianqian.

Meng Qianqian's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this, and she hurriedly replied, "My apologies, Master Li, I completely forgot about that. My brother has returned to the Late Age Nation with everyone else."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he felt like this name was rather familiar.

Meng Qianqian was feeling a little uneasy at the sight of Han Li's furrowed brows.

"The Late Age Nation is where you and your brother originally came from, right?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. After Brother Sun progressed to the Deity Transformation Stage, he wanted to return to the Late Age Nation to avenge his clan. My brother couldn't dissuade him, so he decided to go with him," Meng Qianqian replied.

As the two of them were speaking, all manners of dishes and wine were being brought to the surrounding tables, and there were also waiters standing beside each table, introducing the dishes on their respective tables.

Jin Tong was the only one eating, while Han Li and Meng Qianqian remained seated at their table.

Meng Qianqian was feeling a little uneasy at Han Li's silence, and she said, "Master Li, their intention was never to disobey your orders. It's just that... we didn't know how to contact you, so please don't be displeased with them. Brother Sun always acts like he doesn't have a care in the world, but in reality, this has been weighing on his heart this entire time. Otherwise, with his personality, he wouldn't have worked so hard in his cultivation all this time."

"It's fine. I never forbade you to go and seek vengeance, it's just that you have to ensure that you possess sufficient power before you attempt to do so. I only came back to Heavenly Cloud City this time as I have some things to tell you and the others," Han Li said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

Meng Qianqian's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and she prompted, "Please go ahead, Master Li."

"It's nothing major. It's just that I'm going to be leaving the Northern Glacial Immortal Region soon, and I don't know how long it'll be before I return. All of us were brought together by fate, so it wouldn't feel right to leave without making some arrangements for all of you," Han Li explained.

"You're leaving, Master Li? Why don't you take us with you? We may not be very useful, but at the very least, we'll be able to perform some servant duties for you during your travels," Meng Qianqian hurriedly said.

"It's going to be a very perilous trip, so I can't take all of you with me. I've already prepared some pills, treasures, and cultivation arts for you and the others, and they're all here in this storage bracelet. Seeing as they're not here at the moment, I'll get you to pass these onto them when they get back," Han Li said.

Meng Qianqian was slightly dejected upon hearing this, but didn't say anything further.

"Additionally, there are 30 masks in this storage bracelet, all of which are exceptional aura concealment tools, and they've been specially treated to alter some of the restrictions within them. There's a jade slip inside that tells you how to use the masks, and you can bring out these masks in your times of need to alter your appearances and auras for concealment purposes," Han Li continued.

He flipped a hand over as he spoke, summoning a white storage bracelet that he handed to Meng Qianqian, who accepted the bracelet as she said, "Thank you for making such thorough preparations for us, Master Li."

"The entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region is going to have to endure a period of turmoil soon, and a storm is coming. Once Yungui and the others get back, all of you must set off for Dark Veil Island in the Black Wind Sea right away. I've already arranged for someone to meet you there," Han Li said.

"Yes, Master Li," Meng Qianqian immediately replied.

The two of them paused momentarily to take a look around, at which point they discovered that all of the surrounding tables had already been cleared out by Jin Tong.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he flipped a hand over to produce a flagon of wine that had been given to him by Daoist Hu Yan, and he poured a cup of wine each for himself and Meng Qianqian, then raised his own cup to take a sip.

Meng Qianqian hurriedly accepted her cup with both hands, then took a gentle whiff of the wine's aroma, but she refrained from drinking the wine as she stared at Han Li, who was looking out the window.

It was getting quite deep into the night, and a veil of moonlight was draped over the roof of the restaurant, giving it a rather cold appearance.

Han Li was looking up at the moon in the sky as he pondered the journey that he was about to embark upon.

Right at this moment, his brows suddenly furrowed slightly, and he spotted a shadow plummeting into the city.

Immediately thereafter, Meng Qianqian also sensed something, and her expression instantly changed slightly.

"Let's go," Han Li immediately said.

Meng Qianqian hurriedly nodded in response, then summoned a spirit stone before placing it onto the table.

Han Li immediately grabbed into Jin Tong, who was still munching on a pair of pig trotters, then grabbed onto Meng Qianqian's shoulder with his other hand, and the three of them instantly vanished into thin air.

Immediately thereafter, they appeared in the Moon View Forest.

There were many restrictions littered throughout the forest, but they completely failed to register their intrusion.

After entering a courtyard in Area A, Han Li spotted the figure that had just plummeted out of the sky. It was a large azure bird with its entire body riddled with wounds.

The bird seemed to have spotted Han Li's trio as well, and its eyes immediately lit up as it began squawking at them in a feeble voice.

"Featheryearn!" Meng Qianqian exclaimed as she hurriedly flew over to the large bird, while Han Li set down Jin Tong before making his way toward the bird as well.

Jin Tong was naturally very displeased to have suddenly been dragged here in the middle of her meal, and she was just about to complain when she spotted the injured bird.

She immediately gobbled down the rest of her greasy pig trotters, then rubbed her hands together as a sinister smile appeared on her face.

Featheryearn seemed to have detected her gaze, and it immediately pressed itself more tightly against Meng Qianqian in a fearful manner.

Chapter 526: Revenge

"What happened?" Han Li asked.

"They told me not to come with them, but I was worried about them, so I sent Featheryearn to accompany them. At this point, it's already at the Grand Ascension Stage, so I thought they would definitely be safe, but something must've happened to them," Meng Qianqian murmured with a distressed expression.

Han Li cast his gaze toward Featheryearn, then communicated with it momentarily using his spiritual sense before declaring, "Yungui and the others have been trapped in a restricted area of the Late Age Nation's imperial palace, and Featheryearn fled back here to inform you of this."

Meng Qianqian's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, following which she implored, "Master Li, please allow me to go and save my brother."

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this, and he asked, "Why aren't you asking me to help you save them?"

"I may not not be very smart, but I know that your departure from the Northern Glacial Immortal Region cannot be delayed. I'm already extremely grateful that you went out of your way to come and see us, and it would be far too greedy of me to delay your departure any longer," Meng Qianqian hurriedly replied.

"If Featheryearn was so severely injured even after reaching the Grand Ascension Stage, then you're surely no match for these enemies, how can you expect to save them? Also, the Late Age Nation is quite far away, so how do you know that they'll be able to last until you get to them?" Han Li asked.

"I..." Meng Qianqian had no response to this.

"Let's go. It won't take much time," Han Li said.

Before Meng Qianqian had a chance to reply, Jin Tong had already approached them, and there was still some oil on her lips as she assured, "You can count on me to look after this injured bird, Uncle."

All of the feathers on Featheryearn's entire body instantly stood up on end at the sight of the approaching Jin Tong, and it desperately tried to get away, but it was too severely injured to do so.

"You're not planning to eat it, are you?" Han Li asked with an exasperated expression.

"Of course not! I'm going to treat its injuries! I've been reading all of the scriptures in the storage bracelet that you gave me," Jin Tong immediately complained with an indignant expression.

"I didn't think you would be interested in reading. I thought you were only interested in eating," Han Li chuckled with an amused expression.

"Don't look down on me, Uncle! While I was reading the scriptures, I discovered that I already knew some of the things outlined inside. That must mean that I have talent!" Jin Tong protested in an indignant manner.

"Alright, then how are you going to look after Featheryearn?" Han Li asked.

"That's simple!" Jin Tong replied with a proud expression, then summoned a pill before stuffing it into Featheryearn's beak.

Featheryearn swallowed the pill, but it was still staring at Jin Tong with an alert and fearful expression.

Jin Tong pursed her lips in disdain as she scoffed, "You're so weak and frail, unlike my Xiao Bai. Xiao Bai, where are you? Are you slacking off again?"

Her gaze fell upon the miniature white jade Pixiu hanging from Han Li's waist as she spoke.

"Leave me alone," the Pixiu groaned.

"I'm calling you so you can come and eat with me, you ungrateful little bastard!" Jin Tong scolded.

"I have no interest in mortal food," the Pixiu replied.

"You'd better not regret this!" Jin Tong threatened in a grumpy manner, to which the Pixiu gave no response.

With that brief interlude, the tense atmosphere instantly lightened up significantly., and Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a few more pills, then instructed Meng Qianqian to feed them to Featheryearn.

"I already know the location. Stay here and rest," Han Li said to Featheryearn, then swept a sleeve through the air to summon the green jade flying carriage.

After that, he swept his other sleeve through the air to carry Meng Qianqian and Jin Tong on the carriage, following which he sped away into the night sky, quickly vanishing into the distance.

......

Late Age Nation.

The gates of the capital city, Bright Cloud City, had been tightly shut for many days, and all of the city's residents had also been prohibited from leaving their homes.

At the moment, it was very late at night, and the streets in the city were very peaceful. There weren't even many lit houses, and if it weren't for some of the armor-clad soldiers littered throughout the streets and alleys, one could easily mistake the city as one that was deserted.

In contrast with the deathly silence inside the city, the imperial palace situated in the southern part of the city was brightly lit and constantly being patrolled by imperial guards, while the imperial garden at the back of the palace had been surrounded by multiple protective encirclements.

The encirclements were formed by hundreds of people, all of whom were cultivators.

They were led by a tall and thin purple-robed elderly man, whose aura indicated that he was a mid-Spatial Tempering cultivator.

He was the patriarch of the Xu Clan, the cultivating clan that was currently controlling the Late Age Nation from the shadows.

At this moment, his brows were tightly furrowed, and he was clearly not very pleased.

Half a month ago, a descendant of the Late Age Nation's former imperial clan had stormed into the imperial palace with some members of the Yun Clan, and they had collaborated with some officials of the past imperial court to stage a surprise coup.

By the time he made an emergency exit from seclusion, over half of the Xu Clan's cultivators had been killed or wounded. On top of that, the puppet emperor that they were supporting had been constantly indulging himself in wine, extravagant food, and debauchery, and he had been so frightened that he had died from a heart attack.

After settling the unrest in his clan, he had immediately come to the imperial palace to face the intruders in battle.

However, the intruders were both using cultivation arts of a far higher caliber than his, and they also had a seemingly endless supply of treasures at their disposal, so he was unable to defeat them, even though his cultivation base far surpassed theirs.

What was even more astonishing to him was that they were accompanied by a Grand Ascension Stage bird, which had almost killed him on the spot. If it weren't for the timely arrival of his backers, he would already be dead by now.

"Esteemed patriarch, those scoundrels have already been hiding in this dried well for two days. We've been chipping away this entire time at the restrictions that they've set up, and we should be able to break through them in just four more hours," a middle-aged man with a black mole on his face reported to the elderly man in a respectful manner.

"The Yun Clan was a very formidable force in our Late Age Nation for many years, and those restrictions are not to be underestimated. Make sure to be on your guard at all times and ensure that they don't make it out of here alive," Xu Shou instructed with a dark expression.

"If our savior hadn't gone to pursue that demon beast, he could've easily broken those restrictions," the middle-aged man complained.

Xu Shou was just about to scold him for his untoward remarks when he suddenly looked up into the night sky, where a streak of yellow light flashed through the air before landing beside the dried well.

Xu Shou and the others immediately extended respectful bows as they greeted in unison, "Welcome back, esteemed savior."

The yellow light faded to reveal a yellow-robed young man with a set of unremarkable features, and he took a glance at the middle-aged man who was knelt down beside Xu Shou, following which a cold gleam flashed through his eyes as he decapitated the man with a casual sweep of his hand.

Xu Shou's entire body was splattered with the man's blood, but he only flinched slightly and didn't dare to move even a single inch.

The young man drew the middle-aged man's nascent soul into his hand, then casually crushed it in his hand.

Earlier, he had set off to pursue that strange azure bird, but it was even faster than a late-Grand Ascension cultivator, so he was unable to catch it, and that had left him in a very foul mood.

He was looking for someone to vent his fury on, and the middle-aged man had made those careless remarks at the worst possible time.

"How are things going?" the young man asked.

"The restrictions will be broken in just four more hours," Xu Shou hurriedly replied.

"I don't have time for that. After I take care of things here, I have to get back to the sect. From this day forth, the annual offerings that your Xu Clan must submit to our Stone Ditch Palace will be doubled," the young man said, and Xu Shou's heart immediately sank upon hearing this.

The Xu Clan had taken over the Late Age Nation as there was a Sunray Sand mine here, and most of the profits made from that mine had to be submitted to the Stone Ditch Palace. Now that the mandatory offerings had been doubled, there was no profit for them to be made at all.

"Is there a problem?" the young man asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Not at all, esteemed savior," Xu Shou hurriedly replied.

The young man paid no further heed to him as he swept a hand through the air, and a yellow paper talisman appeared on each of his fingers.

After chanting a brief incantation, the five talismans erupted into flames, then shot forth toward the opening of the well as five bursts of flames of different colors.

A burst of yellow light flashed over the entrance of the well, and an array that had been set up around the well was activated, working with the five bursts of flames to attack the opening of the well.

A resounding boom rang out as a golden light barrier appeared over the opening of the well, only to then explode an instant later.

Immediately thereafter, seven or eight streaks of light of different colors shot out of the well, then rose up into the sky like fireworks before flying away in different directions.

However, before they had a chance to disperse, a giant five-colored umbrella descended out of the sky, revolving on the spot while releasing a burst of invisible suction force to reel in all of the streaks of light, revealing them to be a group of cultivators.

The cultivators of the Xu Clan immediately surrounded the group of cultivators, and all of them were holding weapons with sinister grins on their faces.

Standing beside the well was an azure-robed young man with a crescent-shaped jade pendant hanging from his waist. Beside him was another young man who appeared to be of similar age and was built like a brick wall.

These two were none other than Meng Yungui and Sun Buzheng, while the ones around them were Meng Xiong and the others, and all of them were severely injured.

Chapter 527: Disappeared?

Sun Buzheng was quite severely wounded, and his face was deathly pale. His voice was rather unsteady as he said, "I owe you for getting us into this mess, Yungui, but it looks like I won't be able to repay you this lifetime. Let's be brothers again in our next lives!"

Meng Yungui heaved a concerned sigh upon hearing this. "How is Qianqian going to be able to fare on her own?"

The guilt on Sun Buzheng's face became even more pronounced upon hearing this, and he gritted his teeth tightly.

The young man withdrew his five-colored umbrella, then pointed his thumb at himself as he declared, "Don't be in such a hurry to decide your own fate. Whether you live or die is up to me."

"If you're going to kill us, then do it! Stop wasting time!" Sun Buzheng yelled in a furious voice.

"Tell me where you came from. How did you obtain all of those powerful treasures, and what's the deal with that bird? If you answer these questions truthfully, perhaps I'll find it in the kindness of my heart to spare one of you," the young man said.

Sun Buzheng's expression changed slightly upon hearing this. If possible, he wanted Meng Yungui to survive.

"So you want to kill us, but you're afraid of our backers, and you want to know who they are before you kill us and get rid of the evidence, right? Save your energy, we're not going to say anything!" Meng Yungui declared in a resilient voice.

"I gave you a chance, but you didn't want it, so you can't blame me," the young man said with a sinister smile, then tossed his five-colored umbrella up into the air with a flick of his wrist, and it rose up into the sky to encompass everyone from above.

The runes on the umbrella were flashing incessantly, while countless bursts of five-colored light emerged over the umbrella's frame, then shot down toward Meng Yungui and the others like a storm of five-colored needles.

Meng Yungui was calmly prepared to face his death, and his final thought was still of his sister.

Right as everyone thought that everything was about to come to an end, the five-colored umbrella hanging in the sky suddenly shuddered violently, following which it was forcibly closed, shutting in all of the five-colored needles of light before the umbrella was sent flying even higher up into the sky.

Immediately thereafter, a hand reached out to grab onto the umbrella, and with just a casual swipe, its connection to its former owner was completely erased.

The young man gave a muffled groan as he looked up into the sky with shock and horror in his eyes.

A green jade flying carriage had appeared in the night sky up above, atop which stood three figures.

"Master Li! Qianqian!" Meng Yungui immediately exclaimed in an ecstatic voice.

Sun Buzheng and the others were also ecstatic, and tears were beginning to well up in Meng Xiong's eyes.

"We pay our respects to Master Li!" all of them declared in unison as they fell to their knees.

"You did very well, Yungui," Han Li said with a nod of approval.

Meng Yungui didn't know what Han Li was referring to, and a perplexed look appeared on his face, but Sun Buzheng knew that he was being praised for refusing to reveal his own identity even in the face of death.

With that in mind, a hint of lingering fear welled up in his heart. If he had let slip even a single word of information earlier, then they would've most likely all been left here to die.

"Big Brother!" Meng Qianqian called out as she flew down from the carriage before descending by Meng Yungui's side, then pulled a white jade vial that had been given to her by Han Li and tipped a few yellow pills from within before handing them out to everyone.

Just a moment ago, the young man had been confident and assured, but now, there was a fearful look on his face, and Xu Shou and the others were so terrified that they didn't even dare to breathe too loudly.

"You're from the Stone Ditch Palace, is that right?" Han Li asked as he glanced at the young man's attire.

The young man forcibly composed himself, then replied, "Yes, Senior, my name is Luo Hua, and I am an outer sect disciple of the Stone Ditch Palace."

Even though he was only at the pinnacle of the Grand Ascension Stage, he had seen extremely powerful figures during his time in the Stone Ditch Palace, and he knew that there was no way he could contend against this man, so he didn't even try to put up any resistance.

To his surprise, Han Li suddenly asked, "Do you know Gao Sheng?"

Luo Hua faltered slightly upon hearing this, then asked, "Are you referring to Elder Gao Sheng, who once served in the Immortal Palace?"

"All I know is that he once served at an Ascension Platform," Han Li replied.

"That's him. Elder Gao Sheng disappeared several hundred years ago, and our sect has expended a huge amount of resources to try and find him, but to no avail so far," Luo Hua explained in a fearful manner.

"He disappeared? How?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"I'm but a mere outer sect disciple, so my knowledge of the circumstances surrounding Elder Gao Sheng's disappearance is very limited. Please forgive me, Senior," Luo Hua replied in an uneasy manner.

Han Li was unconvinced, and he reached out with one hand before making a grabbing motion, upon which Luo Hua was forcibly wrenched up from the ground.

Han Li caught him by the throat, and he struggled violently with a horrified look on his face as he pleaded, "Please spare me, Senior!"

Han Li extended a finger forward in an expressionless manner, and a burst of light emerged over his fingertip as he tapped it against Luo Hua's glabella to employ a soul search technique.

He then raised an eyebrow as he discovered that there was a restriction in Luo Hua's consciousness that was impeding his spiritual sense.

Of course, this posed no obstacle to him, and as soon as he channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, the restriction in Luo Hua's mind instantly faded away.

After searching through Luo Hua's memories for a moment, a furious look appeared on Han Li's face, and the light glowing from his fingertip became even brighter.

Initially, there had been a horrified look on Luo Hua's face, but his eyes quickly rolled over into the back of his head, and he began drooling in a slack-jawed manner. His expressions became stranger and stranger until finally, he fainted altogether.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, then slapped him with such tremendous force that his body was completely embedded into his ground. Not only had he been reduced to a pile of mincemeat, even his nascent soul, which had already been stripped of its spiritual nature by Han Li's Spirit Refinement Technique, was completely shattered as well.

Xu Shou and the others were astonished to see this.

In their eyes, Luo Hua had been an almighty deity, yet it was clear that this dark-skinned young man was countless times more powerful than he was, and they couldn't and didn't even dare to imagine just how lofty his cultivation base was.

At this moment, all of them were knelt down onto the ground, and they were trembling uncontrollably as cold sweat poured down their faces.

Han Li had become so incensed because Luo Hua had been blatantly lying to his face.

He wasn't just some ordinary outer sect disciple, as he proclaimed. Instead, he was one of the disciples of the Stone Ditch Palace specifically assigned with the task of gathering intelligence, and he had only come to the Late Age Nation during the course of his investigation of Gao Sheng's disappearance.

After that, he discovered that there was a Sunray Sand mine here, and in order to claim it for himself, he assisted the Xu Clan in replacing the Yun Clan and destroying the Sun Clan to take over the nation.

As for Gao Sheng, he was a direct disciple to the Stone Ditch Palace's grand elder, and his disappearance had created a massive stir in the sect. The circumstances surrounding his disappearance were indeed quite murky. All that the sect knew was that it had to do with a certain mysterious person, and there were portraits of that person circulating throughout the sect.

That mysterious person was naturally none other than Han Li.

There were many more intelligence-gathering disciples like Luo Hua, and they had been sent out several centuries ago to search for Gao Sheng.

Hence, he had instantly identified Han Li as the mysterious figure depicted in the portraits.

After killing Luo Hua, a hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face as he pondered whether he should make a trip to the Stone Ditch Palace to see if he could find any news about Gao Sheng. After all, the events that had unfolded several centuries ago were still a mystery to him.

However, ultimately, he decided not to make such a detour. It had already been some time since he had left the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, and it most likely wasn't going to be long before the Heavenly Court made its move.

His top priority right now was to leave this immortal region as soon as possible.

With that in mind, Han Li pointed a finger at Xu Shou, releasing a burst of azure light that instantly bound him to the spot.

"I'm going to the mountain outside the city. You only have an hour," he declared, following which the green jade flying carriage vanished into thin air.

"Thank you, Master Li!" Sun Buzheng yelled as he knelt down in gratitude toward Han Li.

Shortly thereafter, the sound of blood-curdling howls rang out as a slaughter ensued.

......

On the mountain outside Bright Cloud City, Han Li was seated in a pavilion on the mountain summit, resting with his eyes closed.

Jin Tong was seated on the ground with her legs crossed beside him, and she was holding a white longsword in her hands, which she was breaking up into pieces before eating. As she did this, her gaze was constantly roaming over her surroundings, and it seemed that she was quite interested in this area.

Han Li opened his eyes, then flipped a hand over to produce a disk treasure.

A hint of befuddlement appeared on his face at the sight of the peculiar patterns on the disk.

Just now, as he was channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique, the disk had suddenly reacted.

After some contemplation, Han Li channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique once again, and a cloud of white mist instantly rose up over the disk to encompass its entire surface.

At the same time, a speck of pulsing red light emerged on the disk.

Han Li withdrew his Spirit Refinement Technique, and the speck of red light gradually faded.

After repeating this experiment several times, it became apparent to Han Li that this disk was capable of detecting those using the Spirit Refinement Technique nearby.

He didn't know how large its sensory range was, but the fact that it came from a High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal like Gongshu Jiu meant that it had to be quite a powerful treasure. In the future, he had to be careful when using the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Han Li exhaled as he stowed the disk away, and he suddenly heard the sound of gentle snoring ringing out from beside him.

He turned to discover that Jin Tong had already fallen asleep while laying on the bench under the pavilion, and there was a faint smile on her face.

Chapter 528: Come Out to See Me

Han Li tried to rouse Jin Tong from her slumber through their spiritual connection, but she displayed no signs of waking up, so he could only put her back into his spirit beast pouch.

The breeze blowing over the mountain was very cool and refreshing, and the sun was already beginning to rise in the distance.

A short while later, Meng Yungui and the others arrived on the mountain summit to meet Han Li.

He told them the same thing that he had already informed Meng Qianqian of earlier, then departed on his own without lingering any longer, leaving Meng Qianqian to look on with a sullen expression.

"Master Li's cultivation base seems to have advanced even further. I think he's become even more powerful than the Golden Immortal Stage Dao Lords of the Blaze Dragon Dao," Sun Buzheng murmured unadulterated admiration in his eyes.

"That's why we need to work even harder in our cultivation. We may not be able to help him in the future, but we definitely can't weigh him down," Meng Qianqian said.

"Qianqian's right. We definitely can't put ourselves in a position where Master Li has to come and save us again. Once everything is settled in Bright Cloud City, let's follow Master Li's instructions and travel to the Black Wind Sea right away," Meng Yungui said.

......

A month later.

In the sky above a boundless blue sea, a streak of azure light was racing through the clouds, doing so at such an incredible speed that it was impossible to track with the naked eye.

However, after flying for some time, the carriage drew to an abrupt halt.

Han Li was standing atop the carriage in his usual azure robe, holding a shimmering golden spirit beast pouch.

A surprised look flashed through his eyes as he opened the spirit beast pouch, and a mountainous golden beetle instantly emerged from within.

It was none other than Jin Tong in her true form, and her entire body was glowing with radiant golden light.

Furthermore, he entire body was riddled with countless peculiar patterns that were giving off a terrifying aura.

However, Han Li noticed that the beetle's eyes were still closed, indicating that it was still sleeping.

Through raising Gold Devouring Beetles back in the Spirit Realm, he learned that they evolved by devouring one another, but it seemed that Jin Tong was currently on the cusp of a breakthrough after devouring a large number of treasures.

No wonder her aura's been fluctuating unsteadily ever since she ate that cauldon... Han Li thought to himself, and the concern in his heart faded away as he sensed Jin Tong's steadily rising aura.

Right as he was about to set up an array to conceal the signs of Jin Tong's breakthrough, its eyes abruptly sprang open, and a thunderous burp rang out.

A pillar of translucent light that was over 1,000 feet in length then erupted out of its mouth, covering a distance of several hundred kilometers in the blink of an eye.

The sea down below was completely parted by the pillar of light, to the extent that the entire seabed was revealed.

Immediately thereafter, the golden light radiating from Jin Tong's body rapidly faded, and it quickly reverted back to a little girl.

The little girl stretched lazily with a bleary look in her eyes, seemingly having only just woken up.

Han Li was left feeling rather speechless upon seeing this.

At this moment, her aura indicated that she was already at the late-Golden Immortal Stage. She had made a breakthrough just by eating some things and taking a nap.

He knew that the key to Jin Tong's breakthrough had to have been that pill cauldron from the High Zenith Palace, while the other treasures that she devoured thereafter only had a secondary effect.

It appeared that she had easily made this breakthrough, but in reality, she had devoured so many resources in the process that even the average High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal may not be able to support her.

As Jin Tong finally woke up, her tummy began to grumble, and she asked, "Is there anything to eat, Uncle?"

"Of course!"

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a giant ax that was riddled with runes before handing it over to Jin Tong, and she grabbed onto the ax with both hands before sinking her teeth into it.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he dragged Jin Tong back onto the carriage, then flipped a hand over to produce a white jade slip.

Everything in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region had already been taken care of, so it was time for him to leave, but before that, there was one more place that he had to visit.

With that in mind, he made a hand seal, and the green jade flying carriage quickly vanished into the distance as a streak of light.

......

The Upper Arr Continent was situated to the south of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and in contrast with the Ancient Cloud Continent and the Infernal Frost Continent, the climate here was very warm, so it was a continent that was thriving with vitality. There were countless lush forests and swamps that were teeming with snakes and ferocious beasts, making it unfit for mortal habitation.

Hence, despite the continent's fertile lands and abundant resources, it only had a tiny population of mortals, far below that of the northern continents. Due to the abundance of spirit veins here, the continent was teeming with spiritual qi and all types of spirit plants and precious beasts, so there were many cultivating sects here. As the number one spirit mountain range of the Upper Arr Continent, the Ancient Point Mountain Range was vastly renowned across the entire continent.

However, what was even more renowned was the Vast Flow Palace within the Ancient Point Mountain Range, while Grand Palace Master Luo Qinghai was an almighty immortal who ranked alongside the likes of Baili Yan of the Blaze Dragon Dao and Feng Tiandu of the Dawn Fall Sect.

The five extreme palace masters were also all Golden Immortals, and they presided over the five Vast Flow Extreme Palaces that were littered all over the continent.

Aside from them, there were many more vastly renowned figures in the sect, but the Vast Flow Palace had always liked to keep a low profile. Most of its members spent the majority of their time cultivating in seclusion, and they very rarely left the sect, so not much was known about the sect to outsiders.

At this moment, a tall man with a thick beard was currently standing in the sky near the Ancient Point Mountain Range. It was none other than Han Li in disguise.

As he inspected the mountain range up ahead, he was recalling the information that he had gathered pertaining to the Vast Flow Palace.

From his perspective, the Ancient Point Mountain Range was enshrouded in a mysterious veil of cloud and mist.

The mountain range was filled with abundant spiritual qi, particularly that of the water attribute.

A short while later, Han Li continued onward, and not long after he entered the Ancient Point Mountain Range, a streak of blue light instantly flew out from within to greet him. It was a blue spirit boat shaped like a fish, and there were several Vast Flow Palace disciples standing on it. led by a square-faced young man who appeared to be in his twenties.

Judging from their attire, they appeared to be patrolling disciples of the Vast Flow Palace, and all of them were at the Deity Transformation Stage, while their leader was a Spatial Tempering cultivator.

The square-faced young man was observing Han Li with a wary look in his eyes, but he still extended a respectful salute as he said, "I am Attendant Li Ang of the outer place. May I ask your name and the purpose for your visit, Senior?"

Han Li wore a cold expression, and he didn't even take a single glance at these people before a burst of tremendous spiritual pressure erupted out of his body without any warning.

The blue spirit boat was instantly sent flying like a leaf in a tornado, and all of the Vast Flow Palace disciples on it threw up mouthfuls of blood before falling unconscious on the spot.

Han Li continued onward without pause, but Li Ang was able to remain conscious, and he swept a sleeve through the air to send a burst of blue light erupting into the heavens as he yelled, "We're under enemy attack!"

A resounding boom rang out as the burst of blue light exploded in the sky before spreading outward in all directions.

Han Li made no attempt to stop what he was doing. In fact, he didn't even bother to take a glance at Li Ang as he continued to fly onward.

Immediately thereafter, countless streaks of light erupted out of all parts of the mountain range to stand in Han Li's path.

These were all Vast Flow Palace cultivators who possessed far superior cultivation bases to Li Ang, and they were led by a group of early and mid-True Immortal cultivators.

"Stop! Who dares to encroach upon our Vast Flow Palace?" an elderly man yelled in a furious voice.

"Get Luo Qinghai to come out and see me," Han Li declared in an expressionless manner, following which a vast wave of azure light erupted out of his body, sending all of the surrounding cultivators flying through the air.

Right at this moment, an extremely deep and resonant voice rang out. "Welcome, Fellow Daoist. Please forgive these juniors for their rudeness. May I ask your name?"

At the same time, a gentle breeze blew past, instantly scattering the wave of azure light.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he stopped in his tracks.

Immediately thereafter, a blue-robed elderly man appeared not far in front of him.

The man was quite tall, with a long beard that trailed all the way down to his chest, but his skin was dark green in color, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

The vast aura emanating from his body indicated that he was a Golden Immortal.

Han Li took a glance at the elderly man, but offered no response.

The elderly man wasn't bothered by this, and he cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "I don't think we've ever met before, Fellow Daoist. What is the purpose of your visit?"

"Get Luo Qinghai to come out and see me," Han Li repeated.

"I'm afraid you haven't come at a good time, Fellow Daoist. Palace Master Luo left the sect a very long time ago, and he still hasn't returned yet. If you have something important to discuss with him, you can leave a message with me, and I'll be sure to pass on the message once he returns."

"The Infernal Frost Immortal Palace has already closed, and I ran into Grand Palace Master Luo in Black Wind City some time ago. Back then, he had already set off back to the Vast Flow Palace. Surely you're not telling me that he still hasn't returned?" Han Li asked with a mocking sneer.

The elderly man's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this.

"It's fine if Luo Qinghai doesn't want to meet me, but in that case, I'll have to advise your Vast Flow Palace to select two more extreme palace masters," Han Li continued with a cold smile.

The elderly man's expression changed drastically upon hearing this. "What did you just say?"

Meanwhile, everyone else was exchanging befuddled glances with one another.

Chapter 529: Visit

"I'll handle this, all of you can go now," the elderly man instructed.

Everyone else was quite curious to see what was going to happen next, but they didn't dare to disobey the elderly man, and all of them promptly departed.

"Please come with me, Fellow Daoist," the elderly man said, then flew toward the Ancient Point Mountain Range.

Han Li seemed to have already anticipated this response, and he followed along as a streak of azure light.

It didn't take long before the two of them were deep in the mountain range, and at this point, the dense mist surrounding the mountains had vanished, revealing the mountain range in its full glory.

There were countless mountains stretching as far as the eyes could see in all directions, and some buildings and restrictions were beginning to come into view.

"We just passed through the outskirts of the Ancient Point Mountain Range, only now have we entered the mountain range's inner sanctum, and this is where our Vast Flow Palace is located," the elderly man said as he continued to fly onward.

Han Li casually took a glance at his surroundings in a completely expressionless manner, and the elderly man was left feeling a little deflated by his reaction.

After flying for a while longer, Han Li suddenly spotted an enormous mountain up ahead that towered over all of its neighbors.

It stretched all the way up into the heavens, and all of the mountains around it were made to resemble tiny hills.

Han Li had witnessed quite a few majestic mountains in the past, but none that could compare with this one.

The world's origin qi near the mountain was far more abundant than it was elsewhere, and there were countless palaces and pavilions constructed on the mountain, packed tightly together to resemble the interior of a beehive.

The mountain summit was enshrouded within a huge white light barrier, and it was impossible to see into the light barrier or pass one's spiritual sense through it.

"I've heard that there are 19 enormous mountains referred to as the 19 Holy Peaks in the Vast Flow Palace, and they are the places where the spirit veins of the Ancient Point Mountain Range converge.

“The first grand palace master of the Vast Flow Palace used the spiritual power of the 19 Holy Peaks as a foundation to create a secret area on each mountain summit, collectively known as the 19 Holy Areas. Which one of the 19 Holy Peaks is this one?" Han Li suddenly asked.

"You're certainly very knowledgeable, Fellow Daoist," the elderly man remarked with a surprised expression. "This is the Light Conception Peak."

Han Li nodded in response.

Beside the Light Conception Peak was an extremely wide river that was flowing into the distance.

The water in the river had a vibrant blue color and was giving off extremely abundant water-attribute spiritual power, indicating that it was some type of true water, rather than normal water.

Through the scriptures that he had read back in the Blaze Dragon Dao and the soul search technique that he had performed on the elderly man, Han Li had learned many things about the Vast Flow Palace.

Beside each of the 19 Holy Peaks was a large river, and these rivers were referred to as the 19 True Rivers.

These weren't just ordinary rivers. Instead, the water within them had been converted into true water by the spirit veins in the Ancient Point Mountain Range, and the true water in each of the 19 True Rivers possessed different properties from one another.

The past cultivators of the Vast Flow Palace had created countless water-attribute cultivation arts and abilities based on these 19 True Rivers, and they were an extremely important asset to the sect.

As the two of them continued onward, they passed by several more holy peaks and true rivers, and Han Li could tell that all of the true rivers were converging to a single place.

Close to an hour later, the elderly man suddenly stopped, and Han Li cast his gaze forward, upon which a surprised look appeared on his face.

There was an enormous round crater in the ground up ahead, and it was tens of thousands of kilometers in size, resembling a vast pit that led all the way to the underworld.

This was where the 19 True Rivers converged, and all of them were flowing into the crater as 19 breathtaking waterfalls, presenting a marvelous spectacle to behold.

The green-faced elderly man paused by the crater for a moment, as if he were intentionally showing Han Li the astonishing scenery here, and only after that did he begin to embark on a descent.

Han Li withdrew his gaze and followed along, and it didn't take long before the two of them reached the bottom of the crater.

At the bottom of the crater was a vast body of blue water.

Even though there were 19 massive waterfalls pouring into the crater, the surface of the water was extremely calm without even the slightest wave to be seen, resembling an enormous blue gemstone.

A blue palace was hovering in the air above the water, and the entire palace had been constructed out of some type of blue crystal. There were no visible seams or connective points on the entire palace, as if it had been carved out of a single vast crystal.

The entire palace was riddled with spirit patterns that were glowing radiantly, and hanging directly above the entrance of the palace was a huge plaque that read "Vast Flow Palace".

The elderly man descended in front of the Vast Flow Palace with Han Li, and at this moment, there were already six or seven other Golden Immortals gathered there, with Luo Qinghai present among them, and all of them were looking at Han Li with some degree of animosity in their eyes.

In particular, there was a brawny man with a single blue horn on his forehead, and he was glowering at Han Li with a menacing expression.

At the same time, all of them were exerting pressure upon Han Li by releasing their auras, clearly trying to intimidate him.

"I believe we had a brief encounter back in Wave View City, Fellow Daoist. Please forgive me for not coming out to greet you sooner," Luo Qinghai said as he approached Han LI with a smile.

It appeared that all of the Vast Flow Palace's Golden Immortal cultivators were present, and this formidable lineup was a strong testament to the Vast Flow Palace's power as one of the top sects of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

If none of the Vast Flow Palace's Golden Immortals had perished in the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace, then the number of Golden Immortals in the sect wouldn't have been inferior in the slightest to that of the Blaze Dragon Dao during its heyday, and three of the people present were at the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, while Luo Qinghai was at the late-Golden Immortal Stage.

The elderly man who had led Han Li was one of those mid-Golden Immortal cultivators, while the other two consisted of a blue-robed young woman and that brawny man with the horn on his head.

In particular, the horned man's aura indicated that he had already reached the pinnacle of the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, so he was only a step away from joining Luo Qinghai at the late-Golden Immortal Stage.

Their collective auras formed a crushing wave of spiritual pressure that surged directly toward Han Li, but having already faced Gongshu Jiu in direct battle, this amount of spiritual pressure was certainly not enough to intimidate him.

"It sure is difficult trying to request an audience with you, Grand Palace Master Luo," Han Li said in an indifferent voice.

It was clear that Han Li was completely unfazed by the surrounding spiritual pressure, and Luo Qinghai's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this, but his amicable smile remained unchanged as he explained, "I was cultivating in seclusion in the sect, so I informed everyone that I wasn't going to meet with any visitors. Of course, you're an exception to that, Fellow Daoist."

Han Li merely smiled and offered no reply.

"Please come in and take a seat, Fellow Daoist," Luo Qinghai said as he turned around to lead the way.

Han Li paid no heed to the other Golden Immortals present as he entered the blue palace without any hesitation.

All of the other Golden Immortals exchanged a few glances, then entered the palace as well.

Inside the palace was a guest hall that was around 300 to 400 feet in size.

The layout of the hall was very simple, with around a dozen blue jade pillars inside, every single one of which had a rhomboid crystal embedded into it. These crystals were emitting a faint blue light that illuminated the entire hall, and there were two rows of large blue chairs placed in between these pillars.

Luo Qinghai sat down onto the main chair, then made an inviting hand gesture as he said, "Take a seat, Fellow Daoist."

Han Li duly obliged, and everyone else quickly sat down as well.

Luo Qinghai introduced everyone in the hall to Han Li, then said, "This is our second meeting, yet I'm embarrassed to say that I still don't know your name. May I ask where you've come from, Fellow Daoist?"

"My surname is Liu. As for where I came from, that's not something for you to be concerned about. I'm not from the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, so even if I told you my place of origin, you wouldn't know of it anyway," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice.

"Welcome, Fellow Daoist Liu. May I ask what your intentions are?" Luo Qinghai asked with a smile.

"I should be asking you that. After leaving the Black Wind Sea, I was planning to return to my sect, but I was ambushed by two Golden Immortals from your Vast Flow Palace near Wave View City. Thankfully, I was able to defeat them. Otherwise, I would already be dead by now. Were you the one who instructed them to come after me?"

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a pair of blue badges as he spoke, then slapped them forcefully down onto the tea table beside him.

These were the identification badges of the two Golden Immortals that he had found within their storage tools, and all of the Vast Flow Palace cultivators' expressions instantly changed slightly upon seeing this.

Luo Qinghai's pupils also contracted slightly, but he didn't say anything.

A cold sneer appeared on the horned man's face, and he cast a provocative gaze toward Han Li as he said, "Surely there's been a misunderstanding. Palace Master Tie and Palace Master Qiu both disappeared back in Wave View City, and they most likely fell prey to enemies of our sect. We've been desperately searching for them as well, yet you proclaim that they ambushed you? I'm afraid we're all very confused."

The horned man's name was Feng Hai, and he was the Southern Extreme Palace Master of the five extreme palaces.

"So you're saying that I'm framing them for something that they didn't do?" Han Li asked as he turned to Feng Hai.

"Do you expect us to just take your word for it? If you're going to claim that they ambushed you, then you need to provide evidence. Otherwise, we're not going to accept any culpability," Feng Hai said in a cold voice.

"I came here today to demand an explanation, but seeing as you don't believe me, then I suppose there's no point in continuing this conversation any further. Two of my juniors just so happen to be missing a pair of Golden Soul Pills anyway," Han Li said as he rose to his feet, then turned to leave the hall.

All of the Vast Flow Palace cultivators' expressions changed slightly upon hearing this, and Feng Hai appeared in front of Han Li in the blink of an eye to block his path.

"What do you take our Vast Flow Palace for? An inn that you can check and check out of as you please? You can leave if you want, but you'll have to leave the nascent souls of Palace Master Tie and Palace Master Qiu behind!"

Chapter 530: Negotiation

"Who do you think you are? Get out of my way!"

A cold look appeared on Han Li's face, and golden light flashed over his body as one of his arms abruptly swelled drastically in size as he threw a punch at Feng Hai.

His arm instantly took on a radiant golden hue, looking as if it had been crafted out of pure gold, and it was also covered in countless strands of needle-like golden fur.

The space in the wake of the golden fist screeched and warped violently, as if it were about to be torn apart, and even before the fist arrived, a burst of terrifying force had already descended upon Feng Hai.

In response to Han Li's attack, Feng Hai took a step backward, and a layer of bright blue light surfaced over his body, while his hands transformed into a pair of formidable dragon claws.

He then let loose a thunderous roar as he thrust his claws forward, and a pair of millstone-sized blue dragon claw projections appeared in front of him.

Countless runes were pulsing incessantly on the pair of projections, while rippling waves of blue light were surging incessantly over their surface.

The two dragon claw projections were layered on top of one another to oppose Han Li's fist, and a resounding boom rang out as the golden first crashed into the claw projections, upon which the latter was instantly shattered into countless specks of blue light.

Not only that, but a radiant golden fist projection had erupted out of Han Li's fist, and it was crashing toward Feng Hai with unstoppable force.

Feng Hai was greatly alarmed to see this, and he hurriedly swept both hands through the air, releasing a pair of small triangular blue shields.

The shields transformed into a pair of translucent walls of blue light in front of him, and they had only just taken shape before they were struck by the golden fist projection.

A thunderous boom rang out as the golden fist projection exploded into a burst of powerful golden shockwaves, which completely inundated the two walls of light.

In the face of these golden shockwaves, the walls of blue light were unable to pose any resistance, instantly disintegrating under the pressure.

A burst of tremendous force exploded outward in all directions, causing the entire palace to shudder violently, and Feng Hai was forced to stumble back close to 20 steps before finally managing to steady himself.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and by the end of the sequence, Han Li had ended up where Feng Hai had been standing just a moment ago. The two triangular shields were held in his hands, and they had already been shattered into pieces.

Han Li closed his hands around the ruined shields, instantly reducing them to powder that slipped through his fingers before being blown away by a gentle breath.

Feng Hai's expression had darkened significantly upon seeing this, and all of the other Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals had also sprung to their feet with astonished looks on their faces.

Even though Feng Hai was only at the pinnacle of the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, he possessed a Qiulong bloodline that granted him incredible physical prowess and a body that was comparable to a Profound Immortal's True Extreme Physique. However, he had just been comprehensively beaten in a clash of strength, and it seemed like his opponent wasn't even going all-out.

Han Li slowly withdrew his hands, then continued onward without even bothering to spare a glance at Feng Hai.

All of the Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals instantly appeared in front of Han Li to block his path, and it seemed that a battle was imminent.

"So this is how the Vast Flow Palace treats its guests? This is certainly some exceptional hospitality!" Han Li chuckled as bright golden light erupted out of his body, and a layer of golden fur emerged over his skin.

In the blink of an eye, he transformed into a giant golden ape that was over 100 feet tall, and his aura also swelled drastically to the late-Golden Immortal Stage. Furthermore, it was an aura that was filled with an astonishing degree of malice and violence, and it was sweeping through the air in all directions.

All of the Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals were very much taken aback by this abrupt elevation in Han Li's aura, and right at this moment, Luo Qinghai appeared between them and Han Li as he yelled, "Stop!"

"Do you want to have some fun as well, Grand Palace Master Luo?" the giant golden ape asked with a cold smile, displaying no fear at all.

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Liu, I have no such intentions. All of you, go back to abodes and repent on your transgressions! None of you are to come out of seclusion without my permission! Fellow Daoist Liu is an esteemed guest of our Vast Flow Palace, and he must be treated as such!" Luo Qinghai scolded with a stern expression.

The Golden Immortals didn't dare to raise any objections, and they flew out of the palace in quick succession.

Feng Hai gave Han Li a vicious glare before also departing.

In the wake of their departure, Han Li reverted back to his human form, and with that, he and Luo Qinghai were the only ones left in the palace.

"I'll be honest with you, Fellow Daoist Liu. Our Vast Flow Palace suffered severe losses in the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace, and our woes were compounded even further by the unexplained disappearance of Palace Master Tie and Palace Master Qiu, so everyone is quite tense and on-edge right now. I hope you can understand," Luo Qinghai said with a friendly smile.

"Unexplained disappearance? Did I not just explain to you how they disappeared? It sounds like you also think I'm slandering them. In that case, there's no point in continuing this conversation," Han Li said with a cold smile.

"Let's not rush here, Fellow Daoist Liu. At our cultivation base, we're rarely ever overcome by our emotions. Everything that we do is for the sake of personal interest, so I'm assuming you didn't just come to our Vast Flow Palace to demand an explanation, is that correct?" Luo Qinghai asked with a faint smile.

Han Li offered no response to this.

"Palace Master Tie and Palace Master Qiu's Origin Soul Lamps haven't been snuffed out, so you must've spared them out of the kindness of your heart. Please allow me to apologize in their stead," Luo Qinghai said with a serious expression as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li.

"Don't misconstrue my actions, Grand Palace Master Luo. I only spared them because I didn't want to grant them a swift and painless death," Han Li said in a cold voice.

"Let's be calm and civilized now, Fellow Daoist Liu. I don't know why Palace Master Tie and Palace Master Qiu decided to go after you, but as long as you're willing to return their nascent souls to us safe and sound, our Vast Flow Palace is willing to offer you satisfactory compensation," Luo Qinghai said.

"You sound very confident that I'll agree to your proposal," Han Li remarked as he raised an eyebrow.

"I'm a firm believer in the notion that everything has a price. As long as the reward is sufficiently alluring, even sworn enemies can become friends," Luo Qinghai said.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then said, "In that case, I don't have much use for their nascent souls anyway, so I can return them to you."

Luo Qinghai was very relieved and elated to hear this, and he hurriedly cupped his fist in a grateful salute as he said, "Thank you, Fellow Daoist Liu. What would you like in return? Our sect has always been rather lacking in resources compared with the likes of the Dawn Fall Sect and the Blaze Dragon Dao, but I'll do my best to satisfy you."

"There's not much that can catch my eye in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, but back in the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace, I heard from Fellow Daoist Gongshu that your Vast Flow Palace has a cultivation art by the name of the Water Divination Time Arts, and that it's related to the laws of time. Is that correct?" Han Li asked as he sat down onto one of the chairs in the hall.

"That is indeed true," Luo Qinghai confirmed as a peculiar look appeared on his face. "By the way, by Fellow Daoist Gongshu, are you referring to Immortal Envoy Gongshu Jiu?"

"That's right," Han Li replied with a nod.

"It sounds like you also entered the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, but I don't recall seeing you there. Could it be that you entered the immortal manor together with Immortal Envoy Gongshu?" Luo Qinghai asked.

"I don't believe that's any of your business, Grand Palace Master Luo," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Forgive me. Please continue, Fellow Daoist Liu," Luo Qinghai said with an apologetic smile.

"There's not much else to be said. Give me the Water Divination Time Arts, and I'll return the nascent souls to you," Han Li replied in a direct and concise fashion.

"The Water Divination Time Arts is the premier cultivation art of our Vast Flow Palace. Even within our sect, we can only access the cultivation art after securing majority approval from the panel of elders, so I'm afraid this may be a little too much to ask. Is there anything else I can do for you, Fellow Daoist Liu?" Luo Qinghai asked.

"That's the only condition that I have, it's up to you whether you want to accept it or not. I'm only going to wait two hours here. If I don't see the Water Divination Time Arts in two hours, then I'll just have to refine those nascent souls into Golden Soul Pills," Han Li said as he casually flipped a hand over to produce an object.

Han Li had summoned a white crystal ball, sealed within which was a blue nascent soul in the appearance of the fair-skinned scholar, and Luo Qinghai's pupils instantly contracted slightly upon seeing this.

The nascent soul was ecstatic to see Luo Qinghai, but it was completely immobilized, and it wasn't able to communicate with Luo Qinghai through voice transmission, either.

Luo Qinghai shifted his gaze from the white crystal ball to Han Li, then said, "Please wait here for a moment, Fellow Daoist Liu, I have to discuss this matter with the others."

After that, Luo Qinghai promptly departed, leaving Han Li on his own in the hall.

......

Luo Qinghai emerged from the hall with his brows tightly furrowed in indecision.

After a brief pause, he quickly made his way into a side hall, where all of the other Golden Immortals were already waiting for him, and they immediately rose to their feet as he entered the room.

"How did it go, Grand Palace Master?" the green-faced elderly man asked.

Luo Qinghai gave everyone a brief recount of his conversation with Han Li.

"He wants the Water Divination Time Arts? He must be delusional!" Feng Hai harrumphed coldly.

"The Water Divination Time Arts is the most prized treasure of our Vast Flow Palace. How can we give it to an outsider?" the blue-robed woman chimed in.

"The problem is that this is the only condition that he's stated. If we turn him down, what's going to happen to Palace Master Tie and Palace Master Qiu?" the green-faced elderly man asked with tightly furrowed brows.

The blue-robed woman fell silent upon hearing this.

"He may be a formidable opponent, but if all of us attack him at once with the restrictions in the Vast Flow Palace on our side, surely we'll be able to bring him down! Once he's dead, we'll be able to save Palace Master Tie and Palace Master Qiu's nascent souls," Feng Hai suggested as a hint of killing intent flashed through his eyes.

Everyone else was also quite tempted by this proposal.

Chapter 531: The Third Cultivation Art

"That man has a very peculiar aura, and I've never seen such fierce baleful qi in anyone, so he's definitely no ordinary Golden Immortal. On top of that, I can sense that there's some type of extremely formidable power that he still hasn't displayed yet. Additionally, he seems to be an acquaintance of Gongshu Jiu's, so he may be a very important figure in the Heavenly Court.

“Regardless of whether we can take him down or not, attempting to do so will result in severe trouble for our sect, so that's an option that we cannot explore," Luo Qinghai replied with a shake of his head.

"How are you so sure of that, Grand Palace Master?" Feng Hai asked.

"Back when the immortal manor first opened, only seven Infernal Frost Scenic Paintings appeared, and I saw all of the cultivators in possession of those seven paintings, but none of them possessed the same appearance or aura as that man.

“Hence, he must've entered the immortal manor together with Gongshu Jiu using the eighth Infernal Frost Scenic Painting, which indicates that they had to have been quite close with one another," Luo Qinghai replied.

Everyone nodded in response upon hearing this.

"What do we do then? Are we really just going to hand the Water Divination Time Arts over to him?" Feng Hai asked in an indignant manner.

The other Golden Immortals all fell silent upon hearing this.

"You've always been the best decision-maker out of all of us, Grand Palace Master, so I think you should decide on how we should proceed," the green-faced elderly man said.

"I'm not exaggerating when I say that this has been the most tumultuous period in the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace in the past hundreds of thousands of years. The Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, the Dawn Fall Sect, and the Blaze Dragon Dao have all fallen from their pedestals, while only our Vast Flow Palace remains relatively intact.

“In times of crisis, countless opportunities present themselves, and this is the ideal time for our Vast Flow Palace to expand its forces. If we can take full advantage of this opportunity, it's very much possible for us to crush the Dawn Fall Sect and the Blaze Dragon Dao to become the number one sect in the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace," Luo Qinghai said.

Excited looks appeared on everyone's faces upon hearing this.

Even though the Vast Flow Palace was one of the top three sects of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, it had always been inferior to the Dawn Fall Sect and the Blaze Dragon Dao.

If they could surpass those two sects, not only would they be able to reap tremendous benefits, just the honor to be gained was already extremely appealing to them.

"What do you suggest we do, Grand Palace Master?" Feng Hai asked.

"If we want to achieve that objective, then Palace Master Tie and Palace Master Qiu are indispensable to us. Hence, I think we should recover their nascent souls in exchange for the Water Divination Time Arts," Luo Qinghai said.

"I agree. Ensuring the bright future of our Vast Flow Palace is far more important than the Water Divination Time Arts," the green-faced elderly man declared.

"Indeed. On top of that, the cultivation art is extremely profound and difficult to understand. Throughout the entire history of our Vast Flow Palace, barely anyone has been able to make any progress in this cultivation art, and even the exceptional prodigies who managed to make some inroads progressed far too slowly and were quickly outstripped by their peers who were cultivating other law powers, so it really is just a waste of time."

"I also agree. The cultivation art is a small price to pay in exchange for two Golden Immortal Stage elders!"

Everyone else quickly nodded in agreement as well.

Feng Hai was still a little reluctant, but seeing as everyone else had already expressed the approval of the proposal, he didn't raise any further objections.

"In that case, please go fetch the Water Divination Time Arts, Elder Qnig Fu," Luo Qinghai said to the green-faced elderly man, who promptly departed from the hall.

......

Han Li was sitting on his own while playing with the white crystal ball in his hand when the sound of footsteps rang out from outside, and Luo Qinghai and the green-faced elderly man entered the room.

"How did your discussion go, Grand Palace Master Luo?" Han Li asked.

"Sorry to keep you waiting, Fellow Daoist Liu. This is the Water Divination Time Arts," Luo Qinghai said as he flipped a hand over to produce a blue jade slip before placing it onto the tea table beside Han Li.

"You're a smart man, Grand Palace Master Luo," Han Li said as he also flipped a hand over to produce another white crystal ball, this one containing the elderly man's nascent soul.

He tossed both of the crystal balls to Luo Qinghai, then reached out to grab the blue jade slip.

Luo Qinghai caught the pair of crystal balls, then injected a burst of blue light into each of them, upon which an elated look appeared on his face.

The two nascent souls inside had only been restricted but not harmed, so they could possess new bodies just fine.

Meanwhile, Han Li injected his spiritual sense into the jade slip for a moment, then quickly withdrew his spiritual sense as a surprised look appeared on his face.

Luo Qinghai had already stowed the pair of crystal balls away, and upon noticing Han Li's expression, he asked, "Is there something wrong?"

"No. Now that the exchange is done, I'll be taking my leave," Han Li replied as he stowed the jade slip away, then turned to depart.

An urgent look appeared in Luo Qinghai's face upon hearing this, and he hurriedly said, "There's no hurry to leave, Fellow Daoist Liu. Why don't you stay at our Vast Flow Palace for a few days so I can show you some hospitality?"

"There's no need for that. I don't know anything about Fellow Daoist Gongshu or what happened in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, so there's no need to waste your time on me, Grand Palace Master Luo," Han Li said.

Luo Qinghai's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this, but it then quickly returned to normal as he turned to the green-faced elderly man as he said, "In that case, I won't keep you any longer. Qing Fu, please escort Fellow Daoist Liu out of the sect for me."

"Yes, Grand Palace Master. Please come with me, Fellow Daoist Liu," the green-faced elderly man replied, then led Han Li out of the hall before flying away into the distance.

Luo Qinghai watched as the two of them departed, and he remained standing at the entrance of the hall for a moment before also departing himself.

......

Close to a day later, a streak of azure light flew out of the Ancient Point Mountain Range, then descended onto a small hill to reveal Han Li.

He turned back to the Ancient Point Mountain Range, and a faint smile appeared on his face.

At the same time, Jin Tong emerged beside him amid a flash of golden light.

"It's a good thing you were with me, Jin Tong. Otherwise, that wouldn't have gone so smoothly," Han Li said.

Back in the Vast Flow Palace, he had completely concealed his own aura while adopting his Giant Mountain Ape form, while Jin Tong had released her late-Golden Immortal Stage aura, thereby resulting in the illusion that Han Li possessed her aura, ultimately intimidating Luo Qinghai into complying to his demands.

"I can't believe you gave those nascent souls to them instead of feeding them to me!" Jin Tong said with a displeased expression.

Han Li smiled as he flipped a hand over to summon another pair of Golden Immortal Stage nascent souls, and the displeasure on Jin Tong's face was instantly replaced with elation as he grabbed the pair of nascent souls from him.

These two nascent souls had been a part of a Gongshu Jiu's collection, of which there were five or six left. Perhaps he had secured these nascent souls from the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, or perhaps he had sourced them from elsewhere.

Han Li pulled out the jade slip that contained the Water Divination Time Arts, and a faint smile appeared on his face.

Even though he was still yet to completely grasp the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture that he had obtained from the Dawn Fall Sect, it had reminded him of the Vast Flow Palace's Water Divination Time Arts.

He was going to be leaving the Northern Glacial Immortal Region anyway, so he may as well claim all three of the immortal region's time-attribute cultivation arts, hence his decision to visit the Vast Flow Palace.

At first glance, the Water Divination Time Arts was different from both the Mantra Axis Scripture and the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture in that it was a cultivation art that manifested time law powers using the power of water.

However, what was quite surprising to Han Li was that all three of them had certain similarities.

Could it be that the three time-attribute cultivation arts of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region are somehow connected with one another?

Han Li only considered this notion briefly before shaking his head and stowing the jade slip away again.

His top priority at the moment was to leave the Northern Glacial Immortal Region as soon as possible, so he would just have to study the cultivation art another time.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the green jade flying carriage appeared, and he released a burst of azure light to sweep up Jin Tong before flying onto the carriage.

Immediately thereafter, the carriage shot forth toward the entrance to the primordial land as a ball of green light.

......

In a certain space countless kilometers away from the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

The sky here was a radiant blue color with giant white clouds drifting lazily through the air, while a series of spirit birds flew through them.

Everything here seemed to be particularly bright, as if there weren't any darkness or shadows here.

Above the white immortal clouds was a vast world that consisted of countless giant mountains hovering in the sky, stretching as far as the eyes could see.

These mountains all varied in size, with some only tens of thousands of feet tall, while the largest ones stood at a staggering tens of millions of feet in size. Each mountain carried one or multiple majestic buildings, and these buildings were all of different styles, but they shared one similarity, which was that they were all radiating dazzling golden light.

The mountains were connected by bridges of rainbow light, presenting a spectacular sight to behold.

There was one mountain that was several million feet tall, hovering in mid-air, and it was riddled with radiant golden spirit patterns.

Around a dozen smaller mountains were hovering around it, much like stars around a moon.

On the summit of the mountain stood a golden palace that was glowing radiantly like everything else here.

The palace was around 1,000 feet tall and constructed from some type of unknown golden jade material, and it was extremely opulent and spectacular.

Above the entrance of the palace hung a silver plaque that read "Dawn Void Palace".

There were also many buildings littered across the smaller mountains around the giant golden peak, some of which were medicine gardens, while others were pill refinement chambers.

The nearest one of the smaller mountains had a large estate on its summit, within which numerous immortals were being kept, and it was looked after by several young servants.

Right at this moment, a streak of white light shot forth from afar, then flashed over the estate before hurtling toward the summit of the giant golden mountain.

The streak of white light was releasing a burst of tremendous spiritual pressure, and a giant azure light barrier quickly surfaced around the estate to keep the immense spiritual pressure at bay, but some of it was still able to force its way through.

All of the immortal beasts in the estate immediately became anxious and restless, while all of the servants' complexions paled significantly as they collapsed to the ground.

Only after the spiritual pressure had completely faded did they return unsteadily to their feet with looks of admiration and longing on their faces.

Chapter 532: Arriving at the Primordial Land

"Who was that? Their aura was incredible!" a tall and thin young man asked as he cast his gaze toward the summit of the giant golden peak with an excited expression.

"You were only just assigned to the Dawn Void Palace, so it's no surprise that you don't know of him. That was Xu Yunping, the fifth disciple of the Dawn Void Immortal Lord," one of the older servants replied.

"Master Xu seems to become more powerful everytime I see him," another servant with a pair of bushy eyebrows mused.

"I heard that Master Xu has been cultivating in seclusion for a long time, attempting to break through the mid-High Zenith Stage bottleneck. Now that he's come out of seclusion, I presume he's already made the breakthrough. However, he doesn't seem to have consolidated his cultivation base yet. Otherwise, there would be no spillage of spiritual pressure," the older servant said.

"I heard that Master Xu has only been a disciple of the Dawn Void Immortal Lord for several hundred thousand years, yet he's already reached the mid-High Zenith Stage. If we had even a hundredth of his aptitude, we wouldn't be stuck here," the servant with the bushy eyebrows sighed.

"Master Xu ascended from a lower realm, so it's no surprise that he possesses exceptional aptitude. Even among the Dawn Void Immortal Lord's disciples, he ranks near the top in terms of aptitude, so he's certainly far beyond us," the older servant sighed with a self-deprecating expression.

After that, they began busying themselves with their respective duties again.

Meanwhile, the streak of white light descended in front of the palace on the summit of the giant golden mountain, then faded to reveal a golden-robed young man.

He possessed a pair of handsome features, most notably of which were a pair of bright eyes and sharp brows, and there was an aura of sharpness about him.

On either side of the palace stood a guard clad in golden armor, and the skin on their faces was giving off a metallic sheen.

"Is my master inside?" the golden-robed young man asked.

"He is," one of the armored guards replied.

The golden-robed young man nodded in response, then made his way into the palace and passed through a few corridors to appear in a side hall.

The hall was completely empty with the exception of a silver raised platform, upon which stood a golden chair.

A purple-robed middle-aged man was seated on the chair with his legs crossed. He had a dark complexion, and there was a powerful air of authority about him.

At this moment, his eyes were tightly shut, and bursts of purple light were emanating from his body, which was enshrouded within a cloud of faint purple mist.

The entire hall was also enveloped within a burst of strange power, and as the man breathed, the purple mist pulsed rhythmically, while the space within the hall trembled and buzzed, as if everything in the hall were in his control.

A hesitant look appeared on the golden-robed young man's face, but he still gritted his teeth to muster up his courage as he declared, "Disciple Xu Yunping pays his respects to his master."

The purple-robed man's eyelids fluttered slightly before springing open, and he cast a bright and piercing gaze toward the golden-robed young man, who shuddered involuntarily as his complexion paled slightly.

The bright gleam in the purple-robed man's eyes quickly faded, and his aura also became restrained as he asked, "Is there something you need from me, Yunping?"

"Master, I just received news from the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, informing me that Palace Master Xiao Jinhan had ventured into the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, but they suffered extremely severe losses, with Xiao Jinhan and several Golden Immortal Stage elders perishing in the immortal manor," Xu Yunping reported.

The purple-robed man's expression remained completely unchanged as he asked, "Oh? If I recall correctly, Xiao Jinhan was at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage. How did he die?"

"After receiving this news, I immediately sent out people to investigate, but only a small handful of the Immortal Palace's cultivators managed to return from the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor alive, and none of them knew exactly what had happened.

“However, Xiao Jinhan had been attempting to unite the Northern Glacial Immortal Region for a long time, and as a result, a lot of tension had arisen between him and the other major powers of the immortal region, so I presume his demise must've had something to do with them," Xu Yunping replied.

"I've heard about what Xiao Jinhan had been doing recently. While it's true that he was a little too aggressive, he was still a representative of our Heavenly Court, and his death cannot be tolerated! Send someone to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region to investigate this matter right away.

“Find all of the people who contributed to his demise and have them all killed! The authority of the Heavenly Court is not to be challenged!" the purple-robed man declared as a cold look appeared in his eyes.

"I've already sent people to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region to investigate this matter, and I'm sure an outcome will arise soon," Xu Yunping replied.

"Good. Make sure to get to the bottom of this," the purple-robed man said.

"I'll do my best, Master. Also, I have something else to report to you," Xu Yunping said.

"What is it?" the purple-robed man asked.

"I heard that Immortal Envoy Gongshu of the Immortal Prison also entered the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor to pursue some members of the Reincarnation Palace, but he also seemed to have met his demise in there," Xu Yunping said.

"Gongshu? Are you referring to Gongshu Jiu from the Gongshu Clan?" the purple-robed man asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"That's right," Xu Yunping replied.

"Gongshu Jiu wasn't particularly powerful among immortal envoys, but he was still a High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal, so there shouldn't have been anyone in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region capable of killing him. Is the Reincarnation Palace behind this?" the purple-robed man asked as he rose to his feet.

"At this point, those details are still unclear, but we would've surely found out had the Reincarnation Palace sent a High Zenith cultivators into the Northern Glacial Immortal Region. Should I send out some people to investigate this matter as well?" Xu Yunping asked.

"There's no need for that. The Immortal Prison has always acted as an independent entity, so they'll be sure to send someone to investigate this matter, and there's no need for us to get involved," the purple-robed man said.

"Yes, Master," Xu Yunping replied.

"You did very well in taking care of this matter. The Northern Glacial Immortal Region is under my jurisdiction, so it must not be allowed to descend into chaos. Go and arrange for a new palace master to be selected as soon as possible," the purple-robed man said.

Xu Yunping promptly departed after extending a parting salute, while the purple-robed man paced slowly back and forth in the hall with a contemplative look on his face.

Moments later, he suddenly stopped in his tracks, then vanished from the hall amid a flash of purple light.

......

Across the sea to the southwest of the Upper Arr Continent was an even larger continent called the Primordial Edge Continent.

The eastern region of the continent was riddled with countless mountains, littered throughout which were innumerable dense forests and other perilous terrains, with very cities present.

Close to 100,000 kilometers inland from the east coast was a cliff that was over 10,000 feet tall and stretched for millions of kilometers, acting as a natural wall that sprawled over the continent from its north to its south.

It was still the same continent, yet it was as if the land had been sliced into two here. Above the cliff was a vast oasis, yet below it was a boundless desert.

Atop the cliff was a city that stretched for tens of thousands of kilometers like a resting black dragon, and there were passes that were filled with restrictions and beacon towers positioned strategically along the city.

Even with all these passes and beacon towers, there was only one city on the border, and it was called "Primordial Origin City".

Close to nightfall, the sun in the sky had already set below the city wall, but its warm radiance could still be seen extending over the horizon, basking the cold, black city walls in a layer of gentle warmth.

In the vast desert at the foot of the cliff to the west of the city, the sand was glowing gold under the light of dusk, and aside from the sound of the gentle breeze blowing through the area, there were no other sounds to be heard.

In stark contrast, on the other side of the city wall stood a massive city that was hundreds of kilometers in size. The city was filled with streets and alleys, as well as buildings of different description, and even though it still wasn't nighttime yet, the city was already brightly lit.

Due to how enormous the city was, aside from the central region of the city, which was relatively well planned-out and organized, the rest of the city sprawled out toward the east in a completely disorganized and haphazard fashion.

At this moment, there were two figures, one tall and one short, slowly walking alongside one another on the ancient path leading toward the outskirts of the city.

The shorter of the two figures was a little girl who appeared to be eight or nine years old, wearing a festive little red coat with embroidered golden edges. She was holding three tanghulus as she walked beside a tall man dressed in an azure robe.

The man was none other than Han Li, while the little girl was Jin Tong.

The first stop on the map that Wyrm 3 had given him was the same location that Daoist Hu Yan pointed out to him, and after arriving in Primordial Origin City, Han Li decided to gather more information before he made a decision on how he was embark on this journey through the primordial land.

"Why do I have to conceal my cultivation base, Uncle?" Jin Tong asked with a puzzled expression while munching on a tanghulu.

"Your late-Golden Immortal Stage aura will attract too much attention here," Han Li replied as he cast his gaze toward the edge of the city.

"Isn't that what we want? It would be great if we could lure a few Golden Immortals into attacking us, and after we kill them all, I'll have more snacks to eat! I've constantly been feeling hungry recently," Jin Tong said in an excited manner.

"Our top priority right now is to leave the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, so you're not allowed to cause any trouble. Otherwise, I'll wear you on my finger as a ring instead of allowing you to follow me in your human form," Han Li warned with a serious expression.

"Don't do that! Fine, fine, I'll behave," Jin Tong sighed in a reluctant voice.

As the two of them were speaking, they had already arrived in the outer city of Primordial Origin City.

Chapter 533: Primordial Origin City

The streets in the outer city were lined with mud and short brick and tile buildings, most of which had rectangular tables in front of them, upon which were placed all types of merchandise. The majority of the merchandise catered toward mortals, so they were of no interest to Han Li.

As they approached the inner city, the streets became wider and much more uniform, and the buildings that lined the streets also became taller and more extravagant. However, in contrast with the other continents in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, there was a clear disparity in the style in which the buildings were constructed.

There were very few cylindrical pillars incorporated into the buildings here, nor any intricate engravings that were commonplace elsewhere. Overall, the style was simpler and rougher around the edges, and was lacking in intricacy and thoughtfulness.

Furthermore, the wares being sold on the sides of the streets further accentuated the fact that this continent was different from the others.

Even though it was getting dark, there were still quite a few people out on the streets, and after some observation, Han Li discovered that there were many foreign beings here that weren't commonly seen elsewhere in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region. After walking for only a few hundred meters, Han Li had already spotted a decent number of foreign beings with peculiar appearances and strange attire.

However, this was no surprise, considering that this continent was situated on the border of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

"Something smells really good, Uncle..." Jin Tong exclaimed as soon as she finished the tanghulu in her hand, following which she immediately rushed over to a streetside stall.

Standing behind the stall was a dark-skinned man with a well-built physique, and he smiled as he asked, "How can I help you, little girl?"

Han Li followed Jin Tong to the stall to find that there was a huge copper pot full of bubbling oil placed beside it. Beside the pot was a table that was laden with freshly deep-fried food that was rather unappealing in appearance, but were giving off an alluring aroma.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the food being sold.

There were appendages of roughly the same thickness as human arms, giant pincers the size of tables, and an eyeball from some type of unidentifiable beast, all of which had been fried to a golden color and a crispy texture.

"You want to eat this stuff?" Han Li asked.

"I do! I'll take all of it!" Jin Tong declared as she swept a hand through the air, and all of the food on the table was instantly stowed away into her storage bracelet.

A resigned smile appeared on Han Li's face as he paid the stall owner, who was ecstatic to have sold so much food at once.

As Han Li and Jin Tong continued to approach the inner city, the streets were becoming more and more packed with pedestrians.

There were many streetside stall owners loudly advertising their wares, and many verbal arguments could also be heard with no shortage of derogatory terms being thrown around.

There were also quite a few places where there were scantily dressed women leaning against the railing or standing at the entrance, waving their fans and their sleeves to attract patrons to their doors.

Most of the people in the city were mortals, and there were quite a few cultivators as well, but the majority of them possessed very lowly cultivation bases. Han Li was listening to the conversations taking place around him, trying to gather some useful information. However, that ultimately proved to be futile, so he grabbed onto Jin Tong's arm and rose up into the air to fly directly toward the inner city.

As they flew through the sky, Han Li suddenly raised an eyebrow at the sight of the countless specks of light down below, and he murmured to himself, "It seems like this entire city is a complex array... The larger the city is, the more stable the array. No wonder there are no city walls constructed here. How brilliant..."

"What's so brilliant, Uncle?" Jin Tong asked while crunching on a giant fried pincer.

An amused smile appeared on Han Li's face as he chuckled, "Don't worry about it, just focus on your food."

In contrast with the outer city, the buildings in the inner city were far more intricately constructed, and many decorative engravings could be seen on these buildings, but they were all depicting strange beasts that Han Li had never seen before.

The shops and restaurants that lined the streets had also turned into three-story pavilions, littered in between which were some large inns.

What was most intriguing to Han Li was that there was a giant hemispherical building every few streets, and these were always the liveliest and most bustling places on their respective streets.

Each of these buildings had four entrances, and the walls were riddled with fortification runes. Every once in a while, the sound of raucous cheering would ring out within these buildings.

"It sounds really fun in there, Uncle! Let's go in and take a look!" Jin Tong suggested with an intrigued expression.

"Those are just arenas where different beasts are pitted against each other, while bets are placed by the spectators," Han Li explained with a shake of his head.

Jin Tong immediately lost interest upon hearing this.

"We've been traveling non-stop recently, so let's take a rest in this city for tonight, then leave the city tomorrow to travel to the primordial land," Han Li said as he took a glance up at the starry night sky.

"You can do whatever you want, Uncle. I'm feeling a little drowsy after my meal, so I'm going to sleep for a bit," Jin Tong replied, then shrank down into a tiny golden beetle before landing on Han Li's finger as a golden ring.

Han Li could only shake his head with a resigned smile as he made his way toward the center of the city.

As he did so, he discovered that the buildings on the streets were becoming sparser.

This wasn't because the city wasn't sufficiently prosperous. Instead, it was because all of the buildings in the core area of the inner city had been constructed in accordance with that giant array. Hence, they couldn't be altered on a whim, and piling too many buildings into the area would compromise the array.

As Han Li made his way to the entrance of a street, he spotted a tall red archway. The pillars of the archway had intricate designs of dragons and phoenixes engraved upon them, and the words "Faint Smoke Garden" were inscribed on a plaque at the center of the archway.

Han Li peered into the archway with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes to find that the world's origin qi in the area beyond it was far more abundant than in other areas, and he began to make his way toward the archway.

Only as he approached the archway did he notice that there was a black wooden plaque nearby, upon which were inscribed the words: "Only cultivators at or above the Deity Transformation Stage allowed."

Han Li stepped through the archway, and he was immediately welcomed by a tall and slender female cultivator in a palace dress.

"Welcome, esteemed guest," the woman greeted as she extended a respectful curtsey.

Her etiquette and mannerisms were completely impeccable, but her smile was a little too uniform and professional, making her slightly cold and uninviting.

"Do you have any spare rooms?" Han Li asked.

"There's a vacant room in a peaceful location in the B-grade garden," the woman replied.

"There are different grades in the rooms here? Do you have any vacant rooms in your A-grade garden?" Han Li asked.

"This must be your first time in Primordial Origin City, right? There's an unofficial rule in all of the immortal inns in the city, which is that all rooms are split into four grades, A, B, C, and D, and A-grade rooms are only accessible to cultivators at or above the True Immortal Stage. Given your Grand Ascension Stage cultivation base, a B-grade room is most suitable for you," the woman explained with an apologetic expression.

"I see. That's fine, please lead the way," Han Li replied with a smile.

He was only planning to stay here for one night anyway, so it didn't really matter whether he stayed in an A-grade room or a B-grade one.

The woman hesitated momentarily, then asked, "You're not going to ask about the price?"

"Arrange for some food and wine to be sent to my room, I'll pay for everything when I leave tomorrow," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice.

"As you wish. Please come with me," the woman replied with another curtsey.

She then led Han Li out of the rear hall and along a winding corridor toward the backyard.

"If this is your first time here, why don't you spend a few more days in Primordial Origin City?" the woman suggested as she led the way. "There are some places that are worth visiting in the city, and it would be a pity not to pay them a visit."

"What are some of these places?" Han Li asked in a casual manner.

"The exact time when Primordial Origin City was first constructed is unknown. Throughout its history, the city has been destroyed on many occasions during battles between cultivators and primordial beasts, and the current iteration of the city was reconstructed with the support of all of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region's top sects after the most recent war," the woman introduced.

"Does that mean primordial beasts have managed to attack their way into the city before?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. The last large-scale war was a very long time ago, so there aren't many people around who still remember it, but I've heard that the primordial beasts were able to force their way into the city under the leadership of some primordial true spirits," the woman replied with a nod.

"Is the city jointly overseen by all of the major sects?" Han Li asked.

"That's not the case. Due to the special location of the city, it's currently being overseen by the city lord's manor, and the major sects play no part in its management. However, the city is on good terms with all of the major sects, so it'll generally receive reinforcements from those sects in its times of need," the woman explained.

"What about the Immortal Palace? Do they play no role in overseeing the city?" Han Li asked.

"The Northern Glacial Immortal Palace has expressed intentions of taking over the city in the past, but they've been opposed by all of the major sects, and the city lord of Primordial Origin City is a cultivator at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage, so the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace has been unable to usurp the city lord's manor. However..."

The woman's voice trailed off here as a hesitant look appeared on her face.

Han Li could already guess what she wanted to say, but he still asked, "What is it?"

"In the wake of the Blaze Dragon Dao incident, the state of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region will most likely undergo a change, and Primordial Origin City may be affected as well," the woman said with a concerned expression.

Han Li was rather relieved to hear this.

It seemed like word of what had happened in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor still hadn't spread across the Northern Glacial Immortal Region yet. At the very least, it appeared that those in Primordial Origin City were still oblivious to such matters.

Chapter 534: Sea of Sand

"Indeed, there seems to be some unrest brewing in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region of late," Han Li remarked.

"May I ask for what purpose you're visiting Primordial Origin City, esteemed guest?" the woman asked.

"Truth be told, I'm planning to travel to the primordial land tomorrow," Han Li replied in a candid fashion.

"You're going to leave the city?" the woman asked as she stopped in her tracks with a surprised look on her face. "Are you traveling with someone else?"

"No, I prefer to travel alone," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"Please pardon me for sticking my nose into your business, but... with your cultivation base, leaving the city alone will be no different from throwing yourself to the wolves," the woman said as she extended an apologetic bow.

"Why is that? Is there some source of significant peril outside the city?" Han Li asked.

"Outside Primordial Origin City is an extremely vast sea of sand that's filled with countless natural sand traps that are incredibly deep. Not only will it be impossible for a cultivator to traverse through the unforgiving terrain, even beasts from other deserts are unable to survive there. Only by traveling on one of the large ships in the city will you be able to reach the other side of the sea of sand," the woman explained.

"Why can't a cultivator just fly over the sea of sand then? Are there some perils present in the sky as well?" Han Li asked.

"Even a Golden Immortal cultivator most likely wouldn't dare to traverse through the sea of sand on an aerial route. Primordial Origin City is very close to the primordial land, and there were often powerful primordial beings roaming through the sea of sand. Even many late-True Immortal cultivators have met terrible fates upon running into some of these primordial beasts," the woman explained.

Han Li could tell from the tone of her voice that she wasn't merely trying to scare him, and his brows furrowed slightly in contemplation.

"Aside from that, even if one is lucky enough to avoid all of those ferocious beasts, there are many mirages and illusions in the sea of sand that could easily lead one astray. If luck is on one's side, perhaps they'll be able to stumble their way back to Primordial Origin City in a few centuries, but if luck isn't smiling upon them, then..."

The woman's voice trailed off there, but the implications were already very apparent.

"Where can I go to board one of these ships?" Han Li asked after some contemplation.

"The ship dock is located near the beacon tower on the western city gate. These ships only make two trips a year, but you're in luck as the next ship will be departing in just half a month," the woman replied.

"If cultivators are susceptible to being attacked upon entering the sea of sand, wouldn't a ship full of cultivators be even more prone to attracting primordial beasts?" Han Li asked with a puzzled expression.

"Rest assured, esteemed guest. These ships were crafted by the city lord's manor, and I've heard that there are certain mechanisms in the ship that completely conceal its aura to avoid the detection of primordial beings," the woman explained.

"So you're saying that the ship is guaranteed to be able to reach the other side of the sea of sand?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Nothing is truly guaranteed in life, esteemed guest. As recently as eight years ago, one of the ships was struck down by a primordial true spirit, and there were barely any survivors," the woman replied with a wry smile.

"If it can conceal its own aura, then how was it struck down?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

The two of them arrived in the backyard as they were speaking.

"From what I heard, a True Immortal Stage primordial hunter on the ship had slain a nest of juvenile Nine-eyed Centipedes on a hunting trip, infuriating the True Immortal Stage parent of the centipedes, which had been away from the nest at the time. It was able to catch a whiff of the cultivator's bloodline aura from the blood that he had shed at the nest, and that was what ultimately resulted in that tragedy," the woman explained.

"By primordial hunter, you're referring to cultivators who enter the primordial land to hunt for primordial beasts, right?" Han Li asked.

"Yes, but also no. Hunting primordial beasts is indeed one of the objectives of primordial hunters, but on top of that, they're also searching for strange and exotic plants, as well as ore, gemstones, and other resources from the primordial land," the woman replied.

"I'm sure there must've been countless primordial hunters over the years. Have any of them ever been able to piece together a map of the primordial land?" Han Li asked.

"I'm afraid not. If you're going to visit any of the shops in the city, make sure to be on your guard as all of the merchants claiming to have maps of the primordial land for sale are frauds," the woman replied with a shake of her head.

"Why is that?" Han Li asked.

"While it's true that countless cultivators have ventured into the primordial land over the years, they've only been able to explore a very limited area. The only people who have dared to venture deep into the primordial land and returned alive were almighty beings at or above the Golden Immortal Stage, and it's said that only cultivators at or above the High Zenith Stage have been able to pass through the primordial land to the neighboring Black Mountain Immortal Region. Cultivators of this caliber are extremely rare, and none of them would be willing to map out the primordial land as a public service for others," the woman explained.

"That does make sense," Han Li mused with a slight nod.

"You must've come to Primordial Origin City as you're also interested in becoming a primordial hunter, right? I advise you to limit your activities to the already charted areas of the primordial land. There will be no lack of bounties waiting for you even in those explored areas," the woman suggested.

Before long, the two of them had already arrived in front of a courtyard in the B-grade garden.

Han Li swept his gaze over the courtyard to find that it had been arranged in a triangular formation, with a main room at the center, on either side of which was a side room, and in the middle was a small garden filled with vibrant flowers and young immortal plants.

The woman pulled out an azure jade badge that was engraved with the words "Rain Hearing Courtyard", then swept it through the air.

The restriction that encompassed the entire courtyard instantly split open, following which a gentle, fragrant breeze blew out from within, and a pair of maidservants emerged before extending a collective curtsey toward Han Li.

"Both of these maidservants are Core Formation cultivators with their virginities still intact. If you take a liking to them, then that would be a great honor for them. Otherwise, you can just have them perform some servant duties for you," the woman said as she offered the jade badge to Han Li with both hands.

"I don't require any servants. I'm used to being on my own," Han Li said as he accepted the jade badge.

The two maidservants weren't inferior to the woman who had guided Han Li here in the looks department, and a hint of disappointment flashed through their eyes upon hearing this, but neither of them dared to say anything.

"In that case, I'll have them leave you in peace. Please rest for a moment, the wine and food that you ordered will be here shortly," the woman replied.

"You have my thanks," Han Li said as he tossed a brocade pouch toward the woman.

The woman caught the cloth pouch, then inspected its contents momentarily with her hand concealed up her sleeve, and a combination of shock and elation appeared on her face as she exclaimed, "I am in awe of your generosity, esteemed guest. How about I take you to an A-grade courtyard instead?"

"There's no need for that, this courtyard is just fine. You can all go now," Han Li said with a dismissive wave of his hand, then made his way into the courtyard.

A faint smile appeared on the woman's face as she looked on at Han Li's departing figure, and she pulled a top-grade spirit stone out of the brocade pouch for closer inspection.

......

The next day, Han Li departed from the Faint Smoke Garden early in the morning.

Having slept an entire night, Jin Tong was completely reinvigorated, and at this point, she had already picked up a wide array of different foods from the street side stalls.

"Are we leaving now, Uncle?" Jin Tong asked with a reluctant expression.

"There's no hurry to leave," Han Li replied in an ambiguous fashion, then made his way toward the western city gate, quickly arriving at the dock there.

"What are we doing here, Uncle?" Jin Tong asked.

"Wait here for me for a bit," Han Li said to Jin Tong, then made his way into a nearby black building.

A short while later, he emerged from the building with a black talisman in his hand, upon which was engraved a design of a large ship.

"What's this?" Jin Tong asked with a curious expression as she grabbed the spirit talisman from Han Li.

"It's a ship ticket," Han Li replied, then briefly explained to Jin Tong why they were going to travel by ship.

"With our powers, there's no need to travel by ship. It would be much faster if we just flew straight through the sea of sand," Jin Tong said as she pursed her lips in displeasure.

"This is going to be our first foray into the primordial land, so it's better to be a bit more cautious. On top of that, seeing as there's a ship that can cross this sea of sand, why wouldn't we take advantage of it?" Han Li said with a smile.

Jin Tong thought about this for a moment, then shrugged her little shoulders before continuing to enjoy her feast.

After stowing the ship ticket away, Han Li made his way toward the bustling streets in the city.

Even though he had a very large collection of pills and resources, most of them had been taken from the storage tools of Gongshu Jiu and the others, so they may not necessarily be useful to him. Hence, he had to prepare some things in preparation for the upcoming journey.

Given this city's close proximity to the primordial land, there had to be many resources unique to the primordial land being sold in the city, so it was definitely worth exploring.

However, Primordial Origin City was massive, and many places were enshrouded in restrictions that could keep out spiritual sense.

It was going to take far too long to just explore the city blindly, so Han Li made his way into a nearby variety store, where he purchased a book that introduced the city to newcomers.

After reading through the book, he developed a rough grasp of the city's layout.

He stowed the book away, then continued onward, and it wasn't long before he arrived in a prosperous area in the inner city.

In contrast with other parts of the city, this place was a giant white jade plaza.

There were close to 100 wide streets branching out in all directions with the plaza acting as the central point, and hovering in the air above the plaza was a white palace that looked as if it had been entirely constructed out of pristine white jade.

There were countless large white runes swirling around the palace, releasing bursts of white light that enshrouded the entire plaza and all of the streets around it.

This was the largest business area in Primordial Origin City, and it was certainly living up to its reputation.

Chapter 535: Lost

Han Li stood at the entrance of the street, looking up at the white palace in the sky with a thoughtful expression.

According to the book that he had read, the palace had been created by the city lord of Primordial Origin City, and those inside it could oversee everything that happened along the entire street.

Due to the fact that Primordial Origin City was situated on the border of the immortal region, it had a reputation for being somewhat chaotic, but this street was always a very peaceful place. The reason for this was that battles were strictly prohibited here, and anyone who went against this rule would be severely punished, even killed on the spot in some cases.

Over time, this floating palace became a symbol of power and a beacon of authority in the eyes of Primordial Origin City's cultivators.

Han Li quickly withdrew his gaze, then began to inspect the street around him.

Even though there were many streets branching off from the plaza, it didn't appear messy or cluttered in the slightest. Instead, everything had been arranged in an orderly fashion, and it was clear that the layout of the streets had been set out by experts in the field. Furthermore, all of the shops on each street specialized in only selling one type of merchandise, whether that be materials, or spirit treasures, or pills.

After observing his surroundings for a moment, Han Li made his way down one of the wider streets. All types of spirit plants were being sold in the shops on this street, and it was quite a lively and bustling street.

He began making his way toward one of the larger shops on the street, yet right as he was about to step into it, he suddenly stopped in his tracks, then turned around to look behind him with furrowed brows.

As it turned out, Jin Tong had suddenly vanished.

Han Li released his spiritual sense to search for Jin Tong, and as it turned out, she had rushed over to the nearby food stalls again.

Han Li shook his head in exasperation, but didn't summon Jin Tong back to his side.

Even though her powers still didn't quite place her at the very top of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, he was confident that there was no one in Primordial Origin City capable of harming her.

With that in mind, he made his way into the shop, which was quite large, spanning several thousand feet, and there were many shelves in the shop that were laden with spirit plants and materials.

At this moment, there were many other cultivators already in the shop, and Han Li was immediately greeted by an azure-robed employee.

"How can I help you, esteemed customer? We have the widest range and the cheapest prices that you'll find in Primordial Origin City."

"I'll take a look on my own," Han Li replied as he waved a dismissive hand.

The employee gave an affirmative response, but didn't walk away. Instead, he continued to trail along some distance behind Han Li.

Han Li swept his gaze over the surrounding shelves as he gave an internal nod.

Due to its location, Primordial Origin City was rather isolated from the rest of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, but the materials here were very much eye-opening for Han Li. They were all very rare items in other places, and in particular, most of the spirit beast materials here were unidentifiable to Han Li, so they most likely came from outside of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

Fortunately, all of the wares being sold in the shop had signs beside them that laid out their names and how they could be used.

It didn't take long before Han Li had explored the entire shop, and he was looking a little disappointed.

While it was true that the materials in the shop were quite rare, none of them were of a very high caliber, and most of them were only useful to cultivators below the True Immortal Stage.

The azure-robed employee noticed Han Li's expression, and he rushed over to Han Li before pointing at a staircase in the shop as he said, "Are you looking for some better materials, esteemed customers? The first floor only holds the ordinary spirit materials, while all of the high-grade materials are on the second floor."

"Alright, I'll take a look," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Please come with me."

The employee led the way forward, and it didn't take long before they arrived on the second floor.

In contrast with the first floor, there were only seven or eight shelves on the second floor, but they had clearly been constructed with better materials and design.

Han Li's gaze roamed over the materials on the shelves, and his eyes quickly lit up.

These materials were far more abundant in spiritual power than the ones downstairs. Almost all of them were meant for True Immortal cultivators, and there were even a few that could be used by Golden Immortals.

As Han Li walked along the shelves, his eyes suddenly lit up as he stopped in his tracks, and his gaze settled on a red vine.

"This is a length of Heavenly Siphon Vine. It's a very rare material, and we only recently secured it from a primordial hunter," the employee explained.

"Let me take a closer look at it," Han Li said.

The employee pulled out a badge to dispel the transparent restriction around the shelf, then carefully pulled out the red spirit vine before handing it to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the spirit plant, and an elated look appeared in his eyes following a closer inspection.

The Heavenly Siphon Vine was one of the main materials for refining Heavenly Luster Pills, one of the pills in the Huanan Pill Scripture, so it seemed that he was in luck.

"I'll take this vine. How much is it?" he asked.

Even though he had already gathered all of the ingredients required to refine Infernal Azure Pills, it naturally couldn't hurt for him to refine as many of the pills on the Huanan Pill Scripture as possible.

"Heavenly Siphon Pills are useful even to cultivators above the True Immortal Stage, and this one is over 100,000 years old, so it'll cost 350 Immortal Origin Stones," the employee replied after a brief hesitation.

350 Immortal Origin Stones was quite a large sum, even for a late-True Immortal cultivator, but Han Li didn't even hesitate as he replied, "I'll take it."

At the moment, he had over two million Immortal Origin Stones in his possession, so 350 was but a trifling sum.

The employee was ecstatic.

Han Li continued to browse through the wares on the shelves, but was unable to find any more materials that were useful to him.

Shortly thereafter, he left the shop with the Heavenly Siphon Vine.

However, instead of leaving this street, he made his way into another nearby shop.

Before long, almost an entire day had passed by, and Han Li had explored all of the materials shops in the area, securing many useful materials in the process.

Even though Primordial Origin City wasn't as large as some of the major cities in more prosperous parts of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, its location meant that there were many types of precious materials here, so it was no wonder that the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace wanted to seize control of the city.

Unfortunately, he was only able to find a few ingredients required for refining Heavenly Luster Pills, and there were still many missing.

The reason why he had been able to source all of the materials required for refining Infernal Azure Pills was because Xiao Jinhan had almost completed the entire list for him.

Han Li wasn't overly concerned or dismayed by this. He would just have to keep searching for Heavenly Luster Pill ingredients after he entered the primordial land.

After that, Han Li departed from the street of shops selling materials, then made his way onto a street lined with variety stores. He made his way into the largest shop on that street, then quickly emerged with a gray jade slip in his hand.

The jade slip contained a map of the primordial land, but according to the shopkeeper, the map had been created based on information purchased from primordial hunters.

The primordial land was fraught with peril, and a variety store like this one certainly didn't have the ability to verify the information that they had been supplied by these primordial hunters, so the shopkeeper didn't dare to vouch for the accuracy of the map.

In other words, it could only be used for reference purposes, and Han Li was both amused and exasperated to hear this.

Having explored countless places and purchased countless maps, this was the first time that he had heard something so irresponsible.

However, given the perils of the primordial land, all of the maps being sold in the variety stores in the city suffered from the same pitfall.

Han Li inspected the jade slip for a moment, then injected his spiritual sense into it.

The map inside the jade slip was split up into two sections, a small section that was white in color, and a far larger section that was gray.

All of the white areas were quite close to Primordial Origin City, and there was very detailed information presented in those sections, including what demon beasts resided in those areas and what types of materials could be found there.

As for the gray areas, they represented the unknown.

According to the shopkeeper, those white areas were ones that had been explored extensively by people sent out by the city lord, so they were essentially official maps that were very reliable.

As for the gray areas, the annotations on them had been made using information supplied by some primordial hunters, and it was impossible to verify the validity of the information.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li summoned another white jade badge, this one given to him by Wyrm 3, containing the map of the safe route through the primordial land.

The route began at Primordial Origin City and led all the way to the Black Mountain Immortal Region, but there were only some sparse pieces of information presented on the areas that the route passed through, while the other areas had been left completely empty.

Han Li compared the contents of the two maps to find that Wyrm 3's map and the official map supplied by Primordial Origin City were virtually identical.

However, outside of the official map, the gray areas displayed some rather significant differences compared with Wyrm 3's map, and it was impossible to tell which one was more accurate.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face as he made his way into another shop.

Before long, he had visited dozens of shops and purchased a large collection of maps.

There had to be some accurate information on these maps, and it certainly couldn't hurt to have more of them for his upcoming journey into the primordial land.

By the time Han Li emerged from the final variety shop, night had already arrived.

All of the streets in this area were lined with a type of white crystal that gave off a gentle white glow in the night, illuminating the area and giving it an air of wonder and opulence.

At this moment, Han Li's brows were slightly furrowed. He had just verified Jin Tong's location using their spiritual connection, and she was still in Primordial Origin City, but for some reason, her spiritual sense was trembling slightly, a situation that generally only arose whenever she was in a state of heightened excitement while in battle.

Han Li immediately set off for Jin Tong's location, quickly arriving in front of a huge dome-shaped palatial building.

The entrance of the palace was over 100 feet wide, and it was packed with people.

This was one of the arenas in Primordial Origin City, and there were restrictions set up nearby, making it impossible for someone to sense what was happening inside the building from the outside.

Han Li was rather perplexed to see this, and he immediately made his way into the arena.

Chapter 536: Demonic Man

From the outside, the black palace didn't appear all that large, but it was quite spacious on the inside with seven or eight giant rings that were enshrouded within transparent restrictions. Each ring was around 5,000 to 6,000 feet in size, and they were surrounded by raucous spectators.

Han Li stood at the entrance and swept his gaze over the surrounding area to find that fierce battles were taking place on all of the rings. Some were one-on-one battles between two demon beasts, some battles had more than two combatants, and some battles were taking place between demon beasts and cultivators.

Whenever any of the combatants sustained any injuries, the people gathered around the ring would immediately let loose thunderous cheers.

The raw brutality of these battles seemed to have ignited the bloodlust deep within the hearts of the spectators, and all of them were cheering with excitement.

At the center of the arena was a large stone plaque, upon which were inscribed the matchups for the ongoing and upcoming battles, as well as the odds on offer.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

He wasn't unfamiliar with these types of arenas as he had seen other similar places in the past, but he didn't enjoy this type of environment much.

He continued to scour through his surroundings, and he quickly caught sight of a familiar figure in the crowd beside one of the rings.

Just like all of the spectators around her, Jin Tong was currently yelling loudly at the ring, and her face was brightly flushed.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he heaved a long sigh before making her way toward Jin Tong.

Jin Tong seemed to be oblivious to his approach, and she was yelling at the top of her lungs, looking as if she wanted to jump into the ring to fight herself.

"Jump! Use your tail... Agh, what an idiot!"

Han Li cast his gaze toward the ring in front of Jin Tong to find that there was a pair of ferocious beasts locked in battle inside.

One of them resembled a giant lizard that was over 100 feet in length with its entire body covered in dark purple scales. There were also several sharp hooked spikes on its tail, and its mouth was filled with fangs that resembled sharp swords, giving it a very menacing appearance.

The opposing beast resembled a lion that was 70 to 80 feet tall. It had a single horn on its head and an extremely fearsome physique, coupled with claws that resembled anchors.

A hint of intrigue appeared in Han Li's eyes at the sight of the two beasts.

According to his knowledge, both of the beasts in the ring were primordial demon beasts that had been captured from the primordial land. They were extremely vicious, but their demonic power had been sealed, so there was no danger to any of the spectators.

At this moment, the two beasts were locked in an intense battle, with blood splattered in all directions, while scales and tufts of fur were flying everywhere.

It was clear that Jin Tong was supporting the lizard-like beast, but it was gradually being forced onto the back foot by its opponent.

Right at this moment, the lizard let loose a low roar before darting back like lightning, then swept its spiked tail horizontally through the air, lashing out viciously at its pouncing opponent.

However, the horned beast possessed agility that belied its bulky appearance, and it quickly darted away to the side, allowing it to evade the lizard's sweeping tail.

Before the lizard had a chance to do anything, the horned beast bit down like lightning, sinking its fangs into the midsection of the lizard's tail before whipping its head ferociously to one side.

The lizard was swung through the air before crashing heavily into the restriction that encompassed the ring.

Immediately thereafter, the horned beast pounced forward, and its horn pierced viciously into the lizard's belly, pinning it into the restriction.

A vast volume of blood erupted out of the lizard's body as it let loose an agonized wail, and it was struggling with all its might, but unable to break free.

As it continued to bleed, the lizard's struggles quickly became feebler and feebler, until it finally fell completely still.

The horned beast took a step backward, then whipped its head to the side again to send the lizard flying through the air.

A loud thump rang out as the lizard fell onto the ground, and its limbs spasmed a few times before quickly falling still.

A wave of thunderous cheers instantly erupted around the ring, and the horned beast stood with its head held high and its bloodstained horn pointed directly upward, as if it were basking in the cheers.

Jin Tong stomped her foot into the ground in frustration upon seeing this.

Standing beside her was a purple-robed young man, and he chuckled, "Looks like I win this time."

"Don't get cocky just from winning one bet!" Jin Tong scoffed with a displeased pout.

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this.

Jin Tong had always been quite resentful toward cultivators other than himself, so it was very surprising for him to see her interacting with another cultivator like this.

With that in mind, he took a glance at the purple-robed young man, upon which his pupils immediately contracted slightly.

The man was giving off a True Immortal Stage aura, but with Han Li's immense spiritual sense, he was immediately able to tell that this was a disguise, and that his true cultivation base was at the mid-Golden Immortal Stage.

Furthermore, the aura that he was giving off indicated that he was a demonic cultivator.

"Jin Tong," Han Li called out.

"Oh, what a coincidence, Uncle!" Jin Tong exclaimed as she rushed over to Han Li.

The purple-robed man also turned around to discover Han Li approaching him and Jin Tong.

The man appeared to be in his twenties with a head of slightly curly white hair and a set of handsome features. His eyes were particularly bright, and his pupils were a peculiar light purple color.

"I had to come looking for you because you've been gone an entire day, and it's already nighttime!" Han Li grumbled.

Jin Tong scratched her head in a sheepish manner as she replied, "Is it already that late? I didn't notice. You should come and play with us, Uncle. It's really fun here!"

Han Li paid no heed to Jin Tong as he asked, "Who is this fellow daoist, Jin Tong?"

"He's a friend I just made, his name is Shi Chuankong," Jin Tong replied.

At this point, the purple-robed man had also made his way over to Han Li, and he cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "I am Shi Chuankong, a primordial hunter. May I ask your name?"

As he raised his hands to cup his fist in a salute, his sleeves slid down his forearms to reveal a layer of fine purple scales over his skin.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and he returned the salute as he returned the salute and replied, "My name is Li Feiyu."

"It's a pleasure to meet you, Fellow Daoist Li. Jin Tong and I have been getting along quite well, and we've been having some fun betting on the battles here. I hope I haven't caused any trouble for you," Shi Chuankong said.

"Jin Tong has always been quite naughty, and I don't know how to keep her in check, so I'm very grateful that you've been looking after her for me," Han Li replied with a smile.

"That's good to hear. By the way, I heard from Jin Tong that the two of you have only just arrived in Primordial Origin City and are planning to travel to the primordial land. I also plan to travel to the primordial land by ship in half a month, so how about we travel together?" Shi Chuankong proposed.

"Thank you for the kind offer, Fellow Daoist Shi, but we already have other plans," Han Li refused with a shake of his head.

"Is that so? What a pity," Shi Chuankong replied with a disappointed expression.

"We still have some other matters to attend to, so we'll be taking our leave now, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li declared.

"Surely there's no hurry to leave, Fellow Daoist Li. Why don't you place a few bets as well?" Shi Chuankong proposed.

Right at this moment, another wave of raucous cheers rang out from the nearby ring, and another battle had begun.

An excited look immediately appeared on Jin Tong's face upon hearing this, but Han Li shook his head as he replied, "Once again, thank you for the kind offer, Fellow Daoist, but I'm not interested in betting on these arena battles, so I'll leave you to it."

He then grabbed onto the reluctant Jin Tong and dragged her toward the entrance of the hall.

Shi Chuankong shook his head in disappointment before turning back to the ring again.

......

"Why were you with that man, Jin Tong?" Han Li asked after exiting the arena.

"He was constantly betting against me, so we started challenging each other," Jin Tong replied as she placed her hands on her hips.

"What do you think of him?" Han Li asked.

"He has a similar scent to yours, so I don't detest him like other cultivators," Jin Tong replied as she summoned a tanghulu and began nibbling on it.

"That's certainly a rare occurrence," Han Li mused with a contemplative expression.

"Is there a problem with him, Uncle?" Jin Tong asked.

"There's more to him than meets the eye, so make sure to be careful if you run into him again," Han Li cautioned.

"For sure! Next time I see him, I'll definitely be more careful so that I don't lose to him again!" Jin Tong replied with a firm nod.

Han Li was left feeling rather speechless by this response, and he took a glance back at the arena, then returned to the Faint Smoke Garden with Jin Tong.

The next day, he shopped for some more things that could be useful for the upcoming journey into the primordial land, then returned to the Faint Smoke Garden and remained in his room the majority of the time thereafter.

As a safety precaution, he didn't allow Jin Tong to continue wandering the city as she pleased.

During his infrequent outings, he wasn't able to gather much information about the primordial land, but he did hear some things about the sea of sand outside the city.

The sea of sand wasn't just a barren desert. Instead, some earth-attribute spirit materials could be found there, and there was also a type of special sand beast residing in the area, beasts that could be slain for their precious sand crystals, which were similar to demon cores.

Many of the cultivators in Primordial Origin City often ventured into the outskirts of the sea of sand to slay some smaller sand beasts for their sand crystals.

However, there had been some unrest in the sea of sand recently, resulting in the disappearances of many of the cultivators who had ventured into it, so people were much more apprehensive about the area.

Chapter 537: Setting Off

Half a month flew by in a flash, and the day that the ship was set to depart quickly arrived.

Han Li left the Faint Smoke Garden early in the morning, then traveled straight to the western city gate with Jin Tong sitting on his finger as a ring.

The biannual ship departures were considered to be important events in Primordial Origin City, so aside from the cultivators traveling on the ship, many spectators had also gathered at the city gate.

By the time Han Li arrived, he discovered that there were already hundreds of cultivators that were lined up at the entrance of the black hall on the inside of the city wall, holding their ship tickets for examination.

Upon joining the line, Han Li briefly scoured through the surrounding crowd to find that only a small number of them were True Immortals, while the vast majority of them were Grand Ascension cultivators.

This wasn't all that surprising to him. After all, past experience had already shown that the chances of survival for cultivators below the Grand Ascension Stage entering the primordial land were simply far too low, even when it came to the already charted areas. However, even for Grand Ascension cultivators traveling through the same charted areas, their chances of survival also weren't very high.

Despite this, they were still willing to take the risk for the chance of being able to secure opportunities that could allow them to ascend to immortality.

Even though the line was very long, there was barely anyone speaking, and even some of the cultivators who were here in groups were conversing with one another in hushed tones or through voice transmission, so the atmosphere was rather solemn.

A few minutes later, the sun finally rose over the city wall, and the first ray of sunlight shone down upon the foot of the city wall, while the toll of a bell rang out from above.

As the bell toll rang out, a black-robed elderly man emerged from the entrance of the black hall, then announced that the ship was ready for boarding before beginning to examine the tickets and allowing the passengers into the hall.

The cultivators up ahead entered the hall one after another, and before long, it was Han Li's turn.

As he offered up his black spirit talisman, the black-robed elderly man flipped a hand over to produce a white jade badge, which he pressed against the talisman, and the latter instantly turned into a wisp of black smoke that seeped into the white jade badge.

Immediately thereafter, the words "A-grade cabin 13" appeared on the badge.

Han Li accepted the badge from the black-robed elderly man, upon which he discovered that there were many tiny characters engraved onto its back.

As he made his way into the hall, he flipped the badge over to see what was inscribed on the back, and at the top of the badge was inscribed the word "Rules", and the rules of the ship were laid out down below.

The first rule was that fighting was strictly prohibited on the ship, regardless of what purpose it was for, and breaking this rule was punishable by death.

The second rule was that no one was allowed to leave the ship for any reason, and this transgression was also punishable by death.

Overall, there were 17 rules in total, and death was the consequence for breaking most of them.

Upon entering the hall, Han Li caught sight of a stone staircase at the back of the hall that led up toward the top of the city wall, and there were currently many people making their way up the staircase.

Han Li did the same, and it didn't take long before arrived at the top of the majestic city wall.

The city wall appeared even wider than it did from down below, so wide that 100 people could easily walk along it side by side.

The giant slabs of black stone that were used to pave the city wall were riddled with marks that had been left behind by the passage of time, and at the moment, there were dozens of giant yellow louchuans hovering above the city wall.

These louchuans had bulging centers and tapered tips, and there weren't any fancy decorations on them.

However, they had been completely encased in some type of special metallic material that was riddled with strange runes, giving them a rough and antiquated appearance.

Furthermore, almost all of the ships were riddled with gashes that varied in depth and severity, with some that barely scratched the surface, as well as some that tore through the layer of metal casing and even cut deep into the exposed dragon bone down below.

Groups of black-robed cultivators holding disk treasures in their hands were gathered around the ships, using some type of special secret technique to repair them.

From Han Li's observation, he could see that the most common types of damage displayed on the ships were long and thin gashes and giant conical holes, seemingly having been inflicted by one or two types of primordial beasts.

Right at this moment, a purple figure caught up to him from behind, then began to walk alongside him as they introduced, "That's the handiwork of Sandthorn Snakes and Man-faced Scorpions. One possesses tails as sharp as blades, while the other possesses spike-like pincers. They're the two most common types of demon beasts in the sea of sand, and their offensive prowess is rather ordinary, but they're very abundant in numbers."

Han Li's brows furrowed ever so slightly as he greeted, "Welcome, Fellow Daoist Shi."

The purple-robed figure was none other than Shi Chuankong, who Han Li had previously encountered in the arena.

"It's good to see you here, Fellow Daoist Li. I've already been waiting for over three months in Primordial Origin City to take this ship. If I had to wait any longer, I would've died of boredom!" Shi Chuankong chuckled.

"I don't think you would've been bored with all of the arenas in the city," Han Li said with a smile.

"I was only doing a little bit of gambling to pass the time," Shi Chuankong replied with a slightly embarrassed expression. "By the way, where's the little girl who was with you last time?"

Before Han Li had a chance to reply, a gust of black wind suddenly blew onto the scene from a beacon tower to the north, and a middle-aged man wearing an embroidered black robe emerged.

The black-robed man had a golden badge hanging from his waist, upon which were inscribed the words "Primordial Origin City", clearly indicating that he was from the city lord's manor.

"He's the ship overseer sent by the city lord's manor, and he's responsible for maintaining order on the ship and dealing with unforeseen mishaps. In the past, this duty was occasionally assigned to several late-True Immortal cultivators, but ever since the incident from eight years ago, it's been solely Golden Immortals who have been assigned with this task," Shi Chuankong explained.

"It's time to board the ship," Shi Chuankong continued as he took a subtle glance at the golden ring on Han Li's finger.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the early-Golden Immortal Stage ship overseer descended onto a nearby ship, and shortly thereafter, what appeared to be an administrator emerged from the ship before commencing the boarding process.

It didn't take long for all of the passengers to board the ship, following which the administrator laid out the rules of the ship, which were identical to the ones inscribed onto the white jade badge.

After that, the administrator declared for the ship to depart, and most of the passengers quickly dispersed, returning to their own cabins.

"They say the same things every single time, I'm starting to develop calluses in my ears from hearing this spiel so many times! This is your first time traveling on a ship like this, right, Brother Li? The scenery in the sea of sand is quite spectacular, but I've already grown sick of it after seeing it so many times, so I'll leave you to appreciate the scenery on your own," Shi Chuankong said as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist," Han Li replied as he returned the salute.

Shi Chuankong smiled as he said, "Surely there's no need to be so cold and distant. How about you refer to me as Brother Shi from now on?"

Han Li merely smiled and offered no response to this.

Shi Chuankong shrugged in a nonchalant fashion, then casually strolled back to his cabin.

Han Li watched him depart for a moment, then turned his gaze elsewhere, but he was still pondering the motives of this excessively friendly demonic man.

It didn't seem like he harbored any sinister intentions, but Han Li decided that it would be best to keep his distance.

As these thoughts were flashing through his mind, the ship gradually began to ascend, rising up from the dock on the city wall.

After flying away from the city wall, the ship commenced a gradual descent, flying down the sheer cliff face toward the boundless sea of sand down below.

Right as the ship was about to descend into the vast sea of sand, all of the runes inscribed onto the ship lit up in unison.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of faint yellow light suddenly erupted out of the ship, forming a giant yellow light barrier that encompassed the entire ship.

At the same time, a peculiar primordial aura also began to emanate from the ship.

An enlightened look appeared on Han Li's face upon sensing this.

Now wonder the ship can avoid the detection of the majority of primordial beasts, it's using a protective array with the core of a powerful primordial beast as a foundation to disguise itself as a primordial being...

Right at this moment, the underside of the ship seemed to have finally come into contact with the bottom of the sea of sand, and after bobbing up and down slightly for a moment, it continued onward in a smooth and stable fashion.

Han Li made his way over to the railing of the ship, then looked down to find that the layer of metal that the ship was encased in seemed to possess a special type of magnetism that repelled the sea of sand, allowing the ship to hover just above the sea of sand as it glided along.

All of a sudden, the light radiating from the ship brightened considerably, and it accelerated drastically, shooting forward like a speeding arrow.

Han Li cast his gaze into the distance, and all he saw was a vast and peaceful expanse of yellow sand. There was no sound to be heard, and it seemed that the entire sea of sand was completely desolate and lifeless.

One of the rules on the jade badge was that cultivators weren't permitted to release their spiritual sense to examine the sea of sand in case they alerted some particularly sensitive primordial beasts, and the administrator had also emphasized the importance of abiding by this rule.

Han Li didn't want to cause any unnecessary trouble, so he was happy to follow the rule.

It was going to take at least half a year to reach the primordial land, and after watching the sea of sand for around two hours, Han Li also grew bored of the monotonous scenery, so he returned to his cabin as well.

Chapter 538: Unfamiliar Aura

Han Li's cabin was quite spacious, roughly twice the size of a normal room, and it was split up into two sections.

The inner room was the bedroom that housed a bed, while the outer room held a redwood table and a gray cushion.

The spirit fruits placed on the table weren't exactly of the highest caliber, but they were giving off a very sweet and fragrant aroma.

Upon entering the room, the ring on Han Li's finger immediately transformed into a golden beetle, then flew down onto the cushion, where it transformed into an adorable little girl wearing a red coat.

Jin Tong's eyes immediately locked onto the spirit fruits on the table, and her hand shot out like lightning to grab onto an ovular spirit fruit that was riddled with golden seeds. She sank her teeth into the fruit, and the entire room was instantly filled with a fruity aroma.

"Why didn't you let me show myself to that guy before, Uncle? The two of us get along quite well," Jin Tong asked while munching on her fruit.

"That man's aura indicates that he's a demonic cultivator, but it's also somewhat different. I'm unable to see through him without using my Eye of Truth. On top of that, he clearly knew that you were the ring on my finger, yet he still asked where you were, and I can't get a good grasp on his intentions," Han Li said in a thoughtful manner.

"Are you saying that he's plotting against us, Uncle?" Jin Tong asked.

"I can't say for sure for now, but given that we're in a completely unfamiliar place, it would be best to avoid trouble as much as possible," Han Li said.

"It would be great if he's considering coming after us. I'd have another Golden Immortal Stage nascent soul to eat then!" Jin Tong mused with a sly grin.

Han Li was left feeling rather speechless upon hearing this.

He was just about to warn Jin Tong not to start any trouble when his expression abruptly stiffened slightly.

"What's wrong, Uncle?" Jin Tong hurriedly asked.

"Just now, an extremely powerful aura locked onto the ship, but it vanished in a flash. Did you not sense it?" Han Li asked with slightly furrowed brows.

Before Jin Tong had a chance to reply, Han Li held up a hand to stop her as he said, "There it is again..."

Jin Tong hurriedly focused on her senses upon hearing this, but she was only able to detect a slight trace of what Han Li had detected.

"Did you feel that, Xiao Bai?" she asked in a hesitant manner.

The jade Pixiu offered no response as it hung motionlessly from Han Li's waist.

"How dare you ignore me? I think you're asking for a beating!" Jin Tong threatened as she placed her hands on her hips in an angry display.

"I'm not ignoring you, I just didn't want to show you up. I already sensed that aura the first time that it appeared," the jade Pixiu explained.

"So you're saying you're better than me?" Jin Tong asked as she raised an eyebrow.

"No, no, not at all! I came from the primordial land, so I'm naturally more sensitive to the auras of primordial beings," the jade Pixiu hurriedly explained.

"Can you determine the origins of this aura?" Han Li asked.

"I was born in the primordial land, but I was captured by primordial hunters not long after I was born, and I only learned from Gongshu Jiu that I was a primordial true spirit. Hence, I don't actually know much about the primordial land. All I can do is detect this aura, but not discern it," the jade Pixiu replied.

Right as Han Li was about to speak, that faint aura encompassed the entire ship once again.

"You stay here," he said to Jin Tong, then flew out of the room to emerge onto the deck outside.

As he did so, he discovered that there were only around 20 people on the deck gathered together in small groups, chatting with one another in a relaxed manner, and it was clear that none of them had detected this aura.

On the other side of the deck, he spotted the familiar figure of Shi Chuankong, who was currently looking around with a peculiar expression.

He faltered slightly upon spotting Han Li, then gave him a knowing smile, in response to which Han Li gave a slight nod before returning to his cabin.

After sweeping over the ship three more times, the powerful aura finally disappeared once and for all.

However, Han Li remained on his guard, not daring to grow complacent at all. In fact, his wariness was only continuing to grow by the day.

......

Over five months passed by in the blink of an eye.

The journey proved to be rather uneventful, and the ship was about to reach the primordial land.

Early in the morning, a cool morning breeze was blowing from the primordial land. Han Li stood on the ship with his hands clasped behind his back, peering into the distance with blue light flashing in his eyes. At the end of his field of vision was a speck of green, indicating that there seemed to be an oasis on the distant horizon.

There were already close to 100 people gathered on the deck, all of whom were passengers who were eager to disembark.

Jin Tong was standing beside Han Li, copying him by clasping her hands behind her back as well, and she asked, "Are you still worried about that aura, Uncle?"

"No, I'm thinking about how we should proceed once we reach the primordial land. There are quite a few disparities between the maps we purchased and the one given to me by Wyrm 3. I feel like the route that she gave me isn't actually the safest one, seeing as I haven't truly agreed to join the Reincarnation Palace. At the very least, the supplied route seems to be incomplete," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"Aren't you tired thinking about so much all the time? If there's no good path to take, then let's just establish one of our own!" Jin Tong proposed with a nonchalant smile.

Right at this moment, an alarmed voice rang out from within the crowd.

"What's that?"

"Something's coming from over there!"

Han Li turned to discover a long black line that was rapidly surging over the distant horizon like a black wave, and he could clearly see that this black line was comprised of countless giant creatures with human faces and black scorpion bodies.

Each of the creatures had a thick and burly tail, at the end of which was a crescent-shaped hook that was giving off a cold and menacing gleam.

"Those are Man-faced Scorpions!" someone exclaimed.

Man-faced Scorpions weren't particularly powerful among the demon beasts residing in the sea of sand, but there was an extremely vast number of them, and in the face of a beast tide of Man-faced Scorpions, even True Immortals would struggle to keep them at bay.

Right at this moment, a deep and resonant voice rang out from the top floor of the louchuan.

"There's no need to panic."

The ship overseer was standing there behind the railing, looking on with an unflustered expression, and his calm demeanor instilled within everyone on the ship a sense of confidence and reassurance.

"Those Man-faced Scorpions aren't anywhere near enough to pose a real threat. Make sure to keep yourselves grounded so that you don't get jostled out of the ship. If you fall off the ship, no one will come to save you," the ship overseer declared in a cold voice.

All of the passengers with lackluster cultivation bases hurriedly distanced themselves from the railing of the ship upon hearing this for fear of falling overboard, and some of them returned to their cabins altogether.

Han Li paid no heed to the warning as his gaze remained firmly fixed on the black wave in the distance.

"There's something else there in addition to Man-faced Scorpions," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

Jin Tong had also climbed onto the railing of the ship to look into the distance through narrowed eyes.

The sand beneath the wave of Man-faced Scorpions was constantly undulating, indicating that there was something traveling through the sand at a rapid speed.

"It's coming!" Han Li said as he hoisted Jin Tong down from the railing.

The wave of Man-faced Scorpions quickly arrived to block the ship's path.

Each Man-faced Scorpion was the size of a fully grown ox, and they were climbing on top of one another in layers, forming a small black mountain in front of the ship in the blink of an eye.

The ship overseer's brows furrowed slightly, and he seemed to have also realized that something wasn't quite right.

Such a large-scale scorpion tide wasn't very common, but it wasn't an unprecedented occurrence, either. However, never had the Man-faced Scorpions ever attacked in such an organized fashion.

Before he had a chance to get a grasp on what was happening, the ship had already crashed heavily into the black mountain with a dull thud.

The ship shuddered violently as it was slowed down significantly, and the yellow light barrier around it instantly began to glow brightly.

Immediately thereafter, all of the patterns engraved onto the ship also lit up, and the ship abruptly began to accelerate, forcing its way straight through the black mountain.

A string of grotesque cracks rang out incessantly, and it was the sound of countless Man-faced Scorpion exoskeletons being shattered one after another.

Everyone on the ship stabilized themselves while cheering at what they were seeing.

Han Li was holding onto Jin Tong with one hand while leaning over the ship's railing to peer into the sea of sand down below.

The yellow sand down below was churning incessantly, and there were countless yellow demon beasts that resembled maggots the size of dogs squirming and writhing within the sand.

Han Li was quickly able to identify these things, and he immediately yelled, "There are sand beasts that are eating away at the ship from below!"

Everyone was very alarmed to hear this, and they hurriedly rushed over to the railing of the ship to look down below.

At this point, there were already countless squirming sand beasts clinging to the ship, and its metal casing was already riddled with countless holes. To make matters even worse, there were several sand beasts that were significantly larger than their brethren eating their way through the dragon bones at the front of the ship in a frenzy.

These sand beasts had virtually no facial features, and if it weren't for their circular mouths that were lined with sharp fangs, it would be impossible to tell which end was their head and which was their tail.

Chapter 539: Sand Beasts

The ship overseer's expression also changed slightly upon seeing this. If these Sand Beasts were to bite their way through the dragon bone frame of the ship, the entire ship would become extremely frail, and it would completely fall apart before it reached the primordial land.

A grim look appeared on his face as he flew out of the ship, then descended out of the sky like lightning.

These Sand Beasts and Man-faced Scorpions were quite sensitive to cultivators, and as soon as they detected the ship overseer's aura, they immediately converged toward him at once.

Circles of black ripples instantly began surging out of the ship overseer's body, completely encompassing both himself and the ship. He had unleashed his spirit domain, but it was clear that he didn't want to cause too much of a commotion, as evidenced by the fact that the spirit domain encompassed only an area of 100 feet around the ship.

As soon as the surrounding demon beasts rushed into the spirit domain, they were immediately ensnared by wisps of black mist, following which their bodies were corroded and liquefied.

The three larger Sand Beasts were slightly more powerful than their brethren, but even they weren't able to get within 30 feet of the ship overseer before their bodies also disintegrated.

"Is that a spirit domain? That's incredible!"

"As expected of a Golden Immortal Stage ship overseer!"

......

All of the passengers on the ship were full of praise upon seeing this.

However, right at this moment, Han Li's expression suddenly changed slightly, and he grabbed onto Jin Tong before darting back in retreat as quickly as he could.

Immediately thereafter, the sea of sand in front of the ship abruptly erupted like a volcano, sending vast volumes of sand flying in all directions and flinging countless Man-faced Scorpions and Sand Beasts into the air.

In the next instant, an enormous Sand Beast that was over twice the size of the ship rushed out of the sea of sand. Its enormous mouth seemed to be capable of devouring heaven and earth, and it swooped down toward the ship with tremendous power.

An alarmed and horrified look appeared on the ship overseer's face upon seeing this, and he immediately attempted to flee, only for a dark red vortex to suddenly take shape within the Sand Beast's gargantuan mouth.

The vortex was giving off bursts of tremendous suction force that completely disregarded his spirit domain and immobilized him on the spot.

With just a single bite, the Sand Beast was able to devour the ship overseer alongside half of the entire ship.

The severely damaged ship immediately began plummeting toward the sea of sand, and passengers onboard had no chance to escape before they were completely inundated by Sand Beasts and Man-faced Scorpions.

A chorus of agonized howls rang out as the strong stench of blood spread through the air.

Aside from over 100 True Immortal cultivators who had reacted quite quickly and managed to survive the ordeal, all of the other passengers had been killed in the blink of an eye.

"Run!" someone yelled, and all of the True Immortals immediately fled in all directions in a blind panic.

Amid the chaos, a strange thought occurred to Han Li: Where is Shi Chuankong?

Shi Chuankong hadn't appeared at all ever since the beginning of this incident, and Han Li was certain that he wouldn't have fallen to his demise so easily.

However, there was no time to ponder such matters as Han Li prepared to flee toward the primordial land with Jin Tong, only to find that the giant sand beast was rushing directly at them.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this.

The Sand Beast was quite formidable, but it was only at the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, so it naturally posed no threat to him.

Right as he was about to engage it in battle, Jin Tong's voice suddenly rang out beside his ears.

"I'll take on that thing, Uncle!"

Jin Tong's eyes were glowing with excitement, and she sprang forward before Han Li had a chance to say anything, transforming into a golden beetle before pouncing at the giant Sand Beast.

Han Li hesitated slightly upon seeing this, but ultimately made no attempt to stop her as he watched her while standing in mid-air with his hands clasped behind his back.

Jin Tong slashed a pair of front legs through the air mid-flight, and hundreds of streaks of translucent golden light shot forth through the air, then dispersed before hurtling toward the Sand Beast from either direction.

The Sand Beast seemed to have realized that Jin Tong was a formidable opponent, and it stopped cold in its tracks, then conjured up two thick pillars of swirling sand that swept toward the oncoming streaks of translucent golden light.

A layer of yellow light emerged over the surface of each pillar of sand, and the yellow light was giving off bursts of law power fluctuations.

Golden light flashed within Jin Tong's eyes as the streaks of golden light brightened considerably, then fused together to form two enormous streaks of light that were several thousand feet in length each before striking the two pillars of sand.

As soon as the two came into contact with one another, the two giant streaks of golden light were able to slice through the pillars of sand in an instant, and they weren't even slowed down in the slightest as they continued to hurtle toward the giant Sand Beast.

The Sand Beast didn't take any evasive measures. Instead, another dark red vortex took shape within its enormous mouth, this one far brighter than the one that it had used to kill the ship overseer.

A burst of tremendous suction force surged out of its mouth in a frenzy, instantly sucking in the two streaks of golden light, which flew into the vortex before vanishing without a trace.

A hint of surprise appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, but he still displayed no intention of entering the fray.

Bright golden light erupted out of Jin Tong's body, and it transformed into a huge ball of golden light as it flew toward the Sand Beast, which opened its mouth up even wider, while the dark red vortex inside grew even brighter.

A burst of suction force that was several times stronger than before enveloped the ball of golden light, and the nearby space was collapsing in on itself.

The ball of golden light was sucked into the San Beast's mouth in a flash, and the white jade pendant hanging from Han Li's waist flashed momentarily before the Pixiu's concerned voice rang out from within it.

"Are you not going to save her, Master?"

"There's no need for that," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"But..."

Before the Pixiu had a chance to say anything further, an agonized roar suddenly erupted out of the giant Sand Beast's mouth, and it collapsed onto the sea of sand before writhing and squirming violently, as if it were enduring some type of immense pain.

A dull thump then rang out as a streak of radiant golden light shot out of the Sand Beast's body, punching a huge hole into it.

Vast volumes of viscous white liquid came pouring out of the wound, and it was unclear if this aws blood or something else.

Another string of dull thumps rang out as more bursts of golden light erupted out of Sand Beast's body, and before long, its entire body was riddled with holes.

Its thrashing became even more violent as it let loose a thunderous blood-curdling howl.

"Looks like I got worried for nothing," the Pixiu grumbled before falling silent again.

Finally, the giant Sand Beast let loose one final roar before its body exploded into countless chunks of flesh, following which Jin Tong flew out from its remains.

It was looking a little worse for wear, with several patches of its golden exoskeleton looking rather dull, as if it had been corroded, but these were only minor injuries.

At this moment, it was holding a yellow crystal the size of a human head, within which was a vortex of dark red light that was giving off bursts of formidable law power fluctuations.

It seemed that the crisis had been averted, but Han Li was looking a little concerned.

He felt like there was something abnormal about the roar that the Sand Beast had let loose prior to its death.

Jin Tong flew back to Han Li's side, then flew in a circle around him before asking, "I killed it, Uncle! Do I get a reward?"

"Once we get out of here, you can eat to your heart's content," Han Li promised with an amused smile, then reached out toward the yellow crystal that Jin Tong was holding. "Let me take a look at that crystal."

"No! It's mine!"

Jin Tong flew back so that she was out of Han Li's reach, then reverted back into her human form, following which the yellow crystal was stowed away amid a flash of golden light.

Han Li could only shake his head with a resigned expression as he said, "Let's get out of here."

Right at this moment, the entire sea of sand began to rumble and tremble without any warning, and huge waves of sand erupted into the sky.

At the same time, a tremendous aura emerged beneath the sea of sand before approaching at an incredible speed.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly grabbed onto Jin Tong, while his Thunderstorm Wings appeared on his back.

Immediately thereafter, he vanished from the spot amid a flash of lightning.

In the same instant, the sea of sand down below exploded, and an enormous head shot out from down below before chomping down viciously, but at this point, Han Li was already gone, so it bit down onto nothing.

Close to 100 kilometers away, Han Li re-emerged amid a flash of lightning.

The giant head that had just attempted to swallow him whole belonged to another gargantuan Sand Beast, this one at least 10 times the size of the one that Jin Tong had just slain.

The Sand Beast was giving off an immense aura that was infinitely approaching the High Zenith Stage, and a grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, but he didn't immediately flee the scene.

The sea of sand was completely unfamiliar to him, and if he were to flee blindly without any direction, he could run into even more trouble.

The mountainous Sand Beast had no eyes, but Han Li could sense its fury. All of a sudden, it opened its enormous mouth before letting loose a deafening roar, causing the nearby space to tremble and buzz violently.

Before Han Li had a chance to react, the head of the massive Sand Beast shot out of the sea of sand before pouncing at Han Li's duo.

Despite its tremendous size, it was as fast as lightning, and it reached no more than 100 feet away from Han Li and Jin Tong in the blink of an eye.

Bright golden light erupted out of Han Li's body as he shot back in retreat, while the giant Sand Beast opened its mouth to conjure up a gargantuan dark red vortex.

At this point, Han Li Jin Tong had only managed to fly no more than 10 kilometers away, and they were immediately caught within a burst of incredibly powerful suction force.

Chapter 540: Entering the Primordial Land

Han Li felt the surrounding air constrict around him, and he was stopped cold in his tracks before being sucked toward the giant Sand Beast's mouth by the massive vortex.

A fierce look flashed through Jin Tong's eyes as she prepared to pounce at the Sand Beast, only to be stopped by Han Li, who cast an incantation seal onto her, transforming her into a ring that fitted itself around his finger.

At this point, Han Li wasn't that far away from the giant Sand Beast to begin with, and instead of attempting to flee, he flew toward it instead, reaching its enormous mouth in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of golden ripples erupted out of his body before spreading rapidly in all directions, instantly forming a golden spirit domain that was close to 20 kilometers in size, encompassing a small section of the Sand Beast's body within it.

Everything within the golden spirit domain was instantly slowed down significantly, including the suction force surging out of the massive Sand Beast's mouth.

As a result, Han Li was able to steady himself before using his Thunderstorm Wings once again, vanishing on the spot before appearing behind the mountainous Sand Beast's head amid a rumbling thunderclap.

Immediately thereafter, he let loose a low roar as he adopted his Giant Mountain Ape form.

At the same time, a giant green sword appeared in the golden ape's grasp before it was swung at the Sand Beast with tremendous power.

An incredibly thick crescent-shaped dark green sword projection swept through the air, containing countless dark green runes that were giving off bursts of formidable law power fluctuations.

The mountainous Sand Beast immediately attempted to take evasive measures as it dodged to the side, and at the same time, a translucent yellow membrane of light emerged over the skin on the back of its head.

However, with its enormous body and crippling effect of Han Li's time spirit domain, its evasive measures proved to be completely futile, and the sword projection struck the back of its head with immense power.

The translucent yellow membrane flashed erratically as it attempted to keep the sword projection at bay, but it was only able to last an instant before it was severed.

The crescent-shaped sword projection sliced into the Sand Beast's body, inflicting an enormous wound that was close to 1,000 feet in length, and yellow blood immediately came gushing out from within, but Han Li wasn't elated at all to see this.

Relative to the Sand Beast's gargantuan body, this was nothing more than a minor gash.

The giant Sand Beast let loose a thunderous roar, as if it had been enraged by the injury, and bright yellow light erupted out of its body with countless yellow runes swirling within it.

The yellow light expanded outward in all directions, instantly forming a yellow spirit domain that was close to 100 kilometers in radius.

As soon as Han Li was encompassed within the yellow spirit domain, he immediately felt the surrounding gravity increase by several hundredfold.

Before he had a chance to do anything, a thunderous howling sound rang out, and he turned to discover that the Sand Beast's tail, which wasn't encompassed within his time spirit domain, was sweeping toward him with devastating power.

Upon entering the time spirit domain, the tail was slowed down significantly, but it was still sweeping through the air with astonishing speed and power.

Han Li was also bogged down by the heightened gravitational force, so evasion was not an option for him, and he could only lash out with the giant green sword in his hand.

A resounding boom rang out as the nearby space shuddered, and the golden ape was sent flying by the mountainous tail like a giant ragdoll before slamming heavily into the sea of sand down below.

Half of its body sank into the sea of sand, while golden blood trickled down from the corner of its lips, and the webbing between the thumb and index finger of its sword-wielding hand had also been torn open, but that was the extent of its injuries.

At this moment, the sea of sand was swirling like water, forming a giant vortex that enveloped the giant golden ape before attempting to suck it into the depths.

At the same time, several Sand Beasts abruptly sprang out of the nearby sand to pounce at Han Li.

These Sand Beasts weren't particularly massive, but they were entirely formed by sand, and they were giving off enormous Golden Immortal Stage auras.

At this point, the mountainous Sand Beast had also turned to Han Li and was chomping down upon him once again.

At the same time, the flesh on either side of the gash on the back of its head was quickly fusing together, and it wasn't going to be long before the entire wound was healed.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he slashed his giant green sword horizontally through the air.

At the same time, three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords emerged around him amid a flash of azure light before also sweeping through the air, unleashing bursts of peerlessly sharp sword qi that tore the surrounding sand apart.

As a result, Han Li was freed from the sand, and bright golden lightning instantly erupted out of his Thunderstorm Wings.

However, his lightning power was suppressed by the Sand Beast's spirit domain, so it was only around 30% as effective as it normally was.

In the next instant, Han Li vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden lightning before reappearing close to 10 kilometers away, which wasn't very far, but it allowed him to avoid the terrible fate of being devoured by the gargantuan Sand Beast.

His Thunderstorm Wings then lit up once again, and he began fleeing rapidly into the distance as an arc of golden lightning.

The giant Sand Beast let loose a thunderous roar of fury as it set off in pursuit, but its speed was slightly lackluster compared with Han Li's.

After using his Thunderstorm Wings several times in succession, Han Li was finally able to fly out of the Sand Beast's spirit domain.

With another flash of golden lightning, he appeared several thousand kilometers away, far away from the giant Sand Beast.

Immediately thereafter, he swept a sleeve through the air, and arcs of golden lightning sprang out of his body to form a lightning teleportation array.

With a flash of lightning and a resounding thunderclap, Han Li vanished into thin air, having teleported himself out of the giant Sand Beast's spiritual sensory range.

The mountainous Sand Beast let loose a thunderous roar of fury as it slammed its giant tail into the sea of sand in frustration, causing all of the sand in a radius of thousands of kilometers to churn and rumble like turbulent waves.

......

In the sky above a dense forest, a ball of golden lightning emerged amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, then expanded to form a golden lightning array.

Han Li appeared within the array, having already reverted back to his human form, while the giant green sword and his three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were circling around him.

He swept a sleeve through the air to stow the swords away, then released his spiritual sense to inspect his surroundings, and he heaved an internal sigh of relief upon confirming that he had shaken the Sand Beast off their trail.

Jin Tong immediately flew off his finger, then yelled, "Why did you run away, Uncle? You could've let that thing swallow me, and I would've taken it down from the inside!"

"That smaller Sand Beast was already powerful enough to injure you, the larger one would've surely been even more dangerous. I wasn't going to let you take the risk," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"Master is right. Safety should always be our top priority, so there's no need to take such risks," the jade Pixiu chimed in.

"Xiao Bai! Are you saying that I'm being stupid and unreasonable? I think you need to be taught a lesson!" Jin Tong yelled as she pounced onto the Han Li's leg, then threatened to bite into the white jade pendant that was hanging from his waist.

The Pixiu immediately yelled in alarm before begging for mercy.

Han Li picked Jin Tong up by grabbing onto her braids as if he were plucking a radish out of the ground, then scolded, "Be quiet, you two! We're already in the primordial land now, so we have to be careful."

Jin Tong didn't say anything further, but she was still making menacing expressions as the white jade pendant, while the Pixiu had fallen completely silent.

Han Li shook his head with an exasperated expression, then began to inspect his surroundings.

They were well and truly in the primordial land now, and they were currently situated in a vast primordial forest that spread as far as the eyes could see in all directions.

The world's origin qi here was just as abundant as some of the most prominent spirit veins in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, but it was rather chaotic and unstable.

The Pixiu emerged beside Han Li amid a flash of white light, then closed its eyes while inhaling deeply as a blissful look appeared on its face.

Han Li scanned the landscape down below for a moment, then descended onto a branch of a huge banyan tree.

The tree was at least 1,000 feet tall, and this branch was very spacious, able to seat 10 people side by side with no problems whatsoever.

These banyan trees were quite prevalent in some of the warmer and more temperate places on the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, but this one was at least 10 times larger than even the most massive banyan trees on the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

An intrigued look appeared on Han Li's face as he inspected his surroundings.

Not only was this banyan tree absolutely enormous, all of the other trees that were recognizable to him were also far more massive than they were elsewhere.

In fact, the same applied to all of the plants in this forest, making Han Li feel as if he had somehow been shrunk down to the size of an ant.

Of course, there were also some smaller trees in the area, but there weren't many of them.

"This place looks pretty cool," Jin Tong remarked as she also inspected her surroundings with an amazed expression.

"Are all of the plants in the primordial land so abnormally huge?" Han Li asked.

"This is how things are everywhere in the primordial land. On the contrary, I would argue that the trees everywhere else are abnormally small," the Pixiu replied.

Han Li nodded to himself with a contemplative expression upon seeing this.

"Master, all of the demon beasts here are extremely violent and bloodthirsty, so make sure to be careful when traveling through the primordial land," the Pixiu continued.

"Alright, I'll make sure to be on my guard," Han Li replied with a nod.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a ferocious roar rang out from nearby, and black ape that was around 20 feet tall with a dark red horn on its head sprang out from behind a nearby tree, then pounced at Han Li with its claws brandished.

Han Li remained still on the spot as he flicked a finger through the air, releasing a streak of azure light that instantly split the black ape's body in half, sending blood splattering in all directions.

"You certainly weren't kidding about their violent tendencies," Han Li remarked as he turned his gaze away from the black ape's remains.

In any case, they had finally left the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, so he didn't have to worry about the Heavenly Court for now, and that was a very pleasant thought for him. The primordial land was fraught with peril, but with his current powers, he was confident that he would be able to survive.

After taking a deep breath, he flipped a hand over to summon two objects, one of which was the map that had been given to him by Wyrm 3, while the other was another map that he had purchased in Primordial Origin City.

He inspected both maps briefly before stowing them away again, then swept a sleeve through the air to summon the green jade flying carriage.

"Let's go," he instructed.

The primordial land was a very dangerous place, but the fact that it was very rarely frequented by cultivators had to mean that there were many precious treasures and resources waiting to be uncovered. With that in mind, a sense of excitement welled up in his heart.

Jin Tong and the Pixiu also seemed to be quite excited, and they immediately jumped onto the carriage.

Han Li cast an incantation seal onto the flying carriage, and it immediately sped away as a streak of green light.

Chapter 541: Treasure Hunt

Not long after the green jade flying carriage sped away into the distance, the spirit patterns on its surface flashed momentarily, following which a cloud of white mist emerged to encompass the entire carriage.

This wasn't just a normal white cloud. Instead, it was able to conceal all of the spiritual power fluctuations emanating from the flying carriage.

From the outside, the carriage appeared no different from a normal cloud, and it was flying through the forest in a stealthy fashion without giving off any energy fluctuations.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this.

As expected of a transportation treasure used by Gongshu Jiu, the carriage had many brilliant uses, and even now, he still hadn't fully grasped all of the carriage's abilities.

As the carriage sped through the air, Han Li released his spiritual sense to inspect his surroundings, trying to ascertain their location as soon as possible.

After flying for close to half a day, an elated look suddenly appeared on Han Li's face, and the carriage began to fly to the left at his behest.

Shortly thereafter, a massive swamp emerged.

The ground in the swamp was a peculiar black color, and all of the vegetation inside was also black while giving off a putrid odor.

This swamp was most likely the Black Mud Swamp recorded on the map, and it was still quite far away from the route provided to him by Wyrm 3.

In any case, it had allowed Han Li to ascertain his current location, and he cast an incantation seal into his flying carriage, upon which it immediately accelerated even further.

"This swamp looks really interesting, Uncle. There should be a lot of good stuff inside. Are we not going to take a look?" Jin Tong suddenly asked.

"The Black Mud Swamp has already been annotated on the map, so I'm assuming many primordial hunters have come here in the past. Hence, there's no need to waste our time here. There will be many more places for us to visit in search for treasures anyway," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"You're right, let's keep going," Jin Tong said with an eager expression.

"Pixiu, you told me that you're very adept in searching for natural treasures and resources, this is your time to shine. I'll give you 30% of all of the treasures that we find," Han Li said.

"Really?" the Pixiu asked in a shocked voice as it instantly stood up.

"Of course," Han Li replied with a smile.

"Alright, I'm on it!" the Pixiu replied, and its eyes were glowing with excitement.

"I want some too, Uncle!" Jin Tong yelled in protest.

"You'll definitely get your share as well, but only if you contribute and don't slack off," Han Li said with a smile.

Jin Tong immediately nodded vigorously in response.

Five days later, a vast mountain range appeared before Han Li.

The mountain range wasn't all that tall or remarkable, but the gaps between the mountains were filled with dense black mist, making it very difficult to see the mountains, thereby enshrouding the entire mountain range in a sense of mystery.

"We're finally here," Han Li gently exhaled as he cast his gaze toward the misty mountain range.

This was one of the points on the route supplied to him by Wyrm 3.

Even though the route given to him by Wyrm 3 wasn't necessarily a truly safe one, he had no choice but to follow it.

......

"Master, there's a great abundance of water-attribute spiritual qi in this mountain range. I've already sensed many spirit materials in here. Should we begin?" the Pixiu asked while sniffing at the air.

"Alright, let's start here," Han Li replied with a nod, then made a hand seal, and the green jade flying carriage descended into the mountain range.

Thanks to the cloud of mist around the flying carriage, they hadn't been attacked by any primordial beasts, and at this point, they had already made it quite far into the primordial land.

In the beginning, Han Li had been able to spot the occasional primordial hunter, but as they traveled deeper into the primordial land, that was no longer the case.

At this point, there was no need to be in a hurry.

After flying into the sea of mist within the mountain range, the flying carriage became even more well concealed, and the Pixiu was scouring the area while continuing to sniff at the air as it said, "Around 1,500 kilometers directly up ahead is a spirit plant that should be over 100,000 years of age."

The flying carriage set off in that direction at Han Li's behest, then quickly descended in front of a hollow inside a mountain stream.

In a secretive location within the hollow was a dark red spirit plant that resembled a deer antler that had been carved out of red jade.

A vast abundance of spiritual qi was emanating from the spirit plant, and Jin Tong's eyes immediately lit up upon taking a whiff.

"This is a Deer Antler Herb," Han Li remarked.

This spirit plant could be used to refine some recovery pills at or above the True Immortal Stage, so it was very highly sought after, and the fact that it was a specimen that was over 100,000 years old only made it even more precious.

Right at this moment, a low roar rang out from within the mountain stream, and a giant green python that was several hundred feet in length sprang out before pouncing directly at Han Li.

The giant python possessed a formidable True Immortal Stage aura, but Han Li was completely unfazed as he swept a sleeve through the air, upon which an azure flying sword flew out before sweeping over the python's body like lightning.

The giant python instantly stiffened before its head separated from its body, and it began to thrash and struggle violently while blood gushed out of its decapitation wound.

Han Li paid no heed to the python as he slowly uprooted the Deer Antler Herb, then stowed it away before continuing onward.

Over an hour later, the Pixiu declared, "I can sense some precious spirit materials underground around 1,000 kilometers to our left."

Han Li quickly arrived at the specified location, then descended into the ground, and before long, he re-emerged with a fist-sized blue stone in his hand.

The sound of countless splashing waves could be heard coming from within the stone, and it was as if there were an entire large river inside.

This was a Thousandfold Profound Water Crystal that was an exceptional material for refining water-attribute immortal treasures, and it was a great find for Han Li.

......

In the blink of an eye, close to an entire month had already passed by since Han Li entered this mountain range.

The Pixiu hadn't been exaggerating at all about its treasure-hunting abilities, and at this point, they had already collected a massive bounty of close to 100 spirit plants and materials.

The mountain range was enormous, and as they had been searching for treasures this entire time, they were advancing quite slowly, so they had only just reached the central region of the mountain range.

"Master, I can sense some spirit plants about 1,500 kilometers up ahead... And there appears to be about 20 to 30 of them!" the Pixiu declared in a slightly surprised voice.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, and a short while later, the flying carriage descended into a basin.

At the center of the basin was a plot of flat land that had a light purple hue, and there were indeed 20 to 30 purple spirit plants growing here, all of which were releasing abundant spiritual qi and giving off a strong fragrance.

"These are Serene Purple Herbs!" Han Li exclaimed with an ecstatic expression.

This was one of the main ingredients used to refine Heavenly Luster Pills, so it was certainly a pleasant surprise to be stumbling upon so many of them here.

He immediately swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light to collect the Serene Purple Herbs, but right at this moment, countless thin streaks of blue light erupted out of the ground near the basin before hurtling directly toward him.

These streaks of blue light were no less powerful than attacks unleashed by the average Golden Immortal, and Han Li was very much caught off guard by this.

Upon descending into the basin, he had already scoured the area with his spiritual sense, and he hadn't detected anyone here.

Despite this, he was still able to react in a timely fashion, and he was just about to defend himself when Jin Tong suddenly flew up from the carriage as she said, "I'll take care of this, Uncle!"

She then flicked her delicate little fingers through the air to release countless streaks of translucent golden light, which intertwined with one another to form a giant golden lotus flower in the path of the streaks of blue light.

The streaks of blue light struck the golden lotus flower in rapid succession, and the latter only shuddered slightly before it was able to ward off the former with ease.

Han Li took a glance in Jin Tong's direction, then turned his gaze back to the Serene Purple Herbs.

A burst of azure light flew out of his hand, forming a giant azure palm projection that gently scooped up the Serene Purple Herbs along with the purple spirit soil beneath them.

By the time he flew back to the flying carriage, the beings that had attacked him had already revealed themselves.

As it turned out, it was a group of four or five giant apes with blue fur that stood at around 70 to 80 feet tall.

These blue apes were shimmering with blue light and giving off True Immortal Stage auras, while their leader possessed Golden Immortal Stage powers.

The apes were seemingly chanting an incantation in some type of unintelligible language, and thin threads of blue light shot out of their bodies to form a ball of blue light in front of them.

The blue apes were furious to see Han Li stowing away the Serene Purple Herbs, and the ball of blue light in front of them instantly brightened significantly as a flurry of threads of blue light shot out from within.

At the same time, the leader of the blue apes opened its mouth to release a burst of blue light, which transformed into a giant blue blade that was over 1,000 feet in length before sweeping toward Han Li and Jin Tong.

Jin Tong harrumphed coldly as she switched to a different hand seal, and countless streaks of translucent golden light shot out of the stamen of the golden lotus flower before clashing against the oncoming streaks of blue light.

The streaks of golden light were extremely dense and sharp, warding off the streaks of blue light with ease before quickly forcing them back.

Immediately thereafter, the streaks of golden light crashed into the giant blue blade, punching countless holes into the blade before destroying it altogether.

The wave of golden light then instantly descended upon the group of blue apes, which began to howl in agony, but a layer of blue light then abruptly emerged over their bodies.

A string of resounding booms rang out as their bodies exploded into streams of blue light that burrowed into the ground in a flash.

As soon as these streams of light surged into the ground, the auras of the blue apes instantly became one with that of the water veins underground, making it impossible to detect them.

Chapter 542: Deadly Swamp

All of this had taken place so abruptly and was so unexpected that Han Li was left feeling quite surprised, and he finally realized why he hadn't detected these blue apes earlier.

As soon as the blue apes burrowed into the ground, they immediately fled into the distance at an astonishing speed.

Han Li was looking on with a contemplative expression, but made no effort to pursue them.

These blue apes' concealment ability was quite profound, but he could still just barely detect their presence. However, he had no intention of hunting them down.

Jin Tong's senses weren't as sharp as Han Li's, and she immediately turned to him with a furious expression, clearly awaiting directions from him.

"Let them go," Han Li said with a shake of his head.

"Why aren't we chasing after them?" Jin Tong asked in an indignant manner.

"Those things aren't normal primordial beasts. Instead, I have a feeling that they come from a nearby primordial tribe, so it won't be wise to blindly pursue them," Han Li explained.

"So what? I can take on 1,000 of these blue monkeys at once!" Jin Tong grumbled as she raised her little fist.

"Don't underestimate these primordial beings. This is their home turf, and there's often great strength to be found in numbers. I'm sure there's no lack of formidable beings among them, just like that Sand Beast we encountered earlier. Our objective is to pass through the primordial land, so it would be unwise to seek out trouble," Han Li said.

Jin Tong's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and she didn't raise any further argument.

"It seems like you know quite a bit about the state of the primordial world, Master," the Pixiu remarked.

"We're going to be traversing through the primordial land for quite some time, so I naturally had to do some homework," Han Li replied with a smile.

In reality, he hadn't actually managed to find much information about the primordial land while in Primordial Origin City. In the end, he was only able to gather some valuable information from the Transient Guild at quite a high cost.

"Let's go. The primordial tribes here sorely detest primordial hunters, so I'm sure those things will be bringing back reinforcements soon," Han Li continued.

"This is so boring. I'm a little sleepy, Uncle. Call on me again when there's something fun happening!"

Jin Tong gave an unenthusiastic yawn as she spoke, then transformed into a golden ring that fitted itself around Han Li's finger.

Han Li then made a hand seal, and the flying carriage continued onward.

In order to avoid the reinforcements from the blue ape-like beings from earlier, they temporarily refrained from continuing their treasure-hunting endeavors. Instead, they traveled onward at full speed, and it didn't take long before they left the misty mountain range.

After leaving the mountain range, the terrain up ahead instantly became a lot more level, and it didn't take long before a slightly dark forest appeared up ahead.

From a distance, the trees in the forest appeared to be dark gray in color, and the foliage was very dense, so even though it was daytime, there was still a dark and foreboding aura about the forest.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he still spurred the flying carriage onward to fly into the forest.

"Something's not quite right here... The world's origin qi in this forest is quite abundant, but I can't sense any spirit materials," the Pixiu suddenly said after they had been flying for some time.

At this point, Han Li had also developed a sense that there was something strange about this forest.

Not only were there very few spirit plants in the forest, his spiritual sense told him that there weren't any primordial beasts around, either.

However, Han Li didn't pay this much heed. The lack of primordial beasts was something that he was happy to see as it would allow him to travel through the forest faster.

After flying for close to half a day, the Pixiu abruptly stood up as it declared in an excited voice, "I can sense extremely powerful spiritual qi fluctuations coming from the left! There must be something incredibly precious there!"

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, but after a brief moment of contemplation, he still redirected the flying carriage to set off in that direction.

Before long, a dead black swamp had appeared up ahead.

The swamp was filled with decaying black mud, and it was completely desolate and devoid of life. Occasionally, a large bubble would rise up from the mud, then pop loudly to release plumes of dark purple miasma.

"Didn't you say there was something of value here?" Han Li asked with slightly furrowed brows.

His spiritual sense was telling him that the world's origin qi here was much sparser than it was in the rest of the forest, and he couldn't even sense any living beings here, let alone any precious natural treasures.

"I'm certain that there's something deep in the swamp! If we find something good this time, don't forget that I was the one who led us here!" the Pixiu declared in a confident manner.

Han Li was still rather skeptical upon hearing this, but spurred on the flying carriage to continue onward, nonetheless.

After flying for a while, his expression suddenly changed slightly as he brought the flying carriage to a halt.

In this area, the dark purple miasma over the swamp had become extremely dense, making this place as dark as if it were nighttime.

Han Li was unbothered by this miasma, and the flying carriage descended out of the sky at his behest, then stopped over 100 feet above the swamp.

There were countless carcasses in the swamp down below, most of which were already severely decayed, but he could still tell that they belonged to various types of demon beasts.

These carcasses all varied in size from just over 100 feet to in excess of 1,000 feet in size, and there were countless more of these carcasses up ahead, stretching as far as the eyes could see.

The Pixiu seemed to be quite startled by this, and it didn't dare to say anything as it snuck a furtive glance at Han Li out of the corner of its eye.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, and after a brief pause, the flying carriage continued onward.

The further they ventured into the swamp, the more demon beasts carcasses that they saw until eventually, the entire swamp was completely filled with them, and the air temperature was also dropping sharply.

"Is it still further up ahead?" Han Li asked.

"Well... Yes, but this place is a little scary, so maybe we should turn back..." the Pixiu replied in an uneasy voice.

"I hope you're right," Han Li said.

Having already come this far, he was naturally unwilling to turn back. According to past experience, all precious natural treasures were guarded by powerful beasts. However, whatever guardian beast was here seemed to be quite formidable and was also very adept at concealing itself, to the point that Han Li still hadn't managed to detect it.

However, at this point in the primordial land, he had a feeling that he possessed sufficient power to at least ensure self-preservation, and if he encountered a foe too powerful for him to defeat, then he would just have to run away.

With that in mind, Han Li continued onward atop his flying carriage, but he had slowed down quite a bit and was also proceeding with caution.

Some time later, the flying carriage drew to a halt at his behest.

They had already ventured very deep into the swamp at this point, and there was an astonishing number of demon beasts carcasses here, forming a series of massive mountains of bones.

Additionally, the carcasses here were also far more massive than the ones from before, and the area was littered with giant skeletons the size of mountains.

Even Han Li was beginning to get a little spooked.

"Master, the treasure is right there!" the Pixiu suddenly declared as it pointed forward.

Between two massive mountains of bones several kilometers up ahead was a green pond that was several dozen feet in size, and the water in the pond was so clear that one could see all the way to the bottom.

At the center of the pond was a shimmering golden lotus flower with nine petals, all of which were also golden in color, but in different shades. Despite this, they somehow didn't appear to conflict with each other at all.

There were also nine golden rainbows of different shades hanging in the air above the lotus flower, and the flying carriage immediately began to approach it at Han Li's behest.

Even as they were still several thousand feet away, Han Li could already catch a whiff of an incredibly fragrant aroma from the golden lotus flower, and just this aroma alone was enough to loosen several of the immortal acupoints in his body ever so slightly.

He had no idea what this golden lotus flower was, but its aroma alone told him that it was definitely an exceptional spirit plant.

Right as he was about to get even closer, a piercing screech suddenly rang out from the distant sky.

As soon as he heard this screech, his soul abruptly shuddered, while his body began to sway unsteadily.

However, with his tremendous spiritual sense, he was immediable able to steady himself, following which he looked up to find that a giant black beast had appeared up above.

The black beast had an enormous body that wasn't inferior in size compared with the giant Sand Beast in the sea of sand, and it resembled a wyrm with a layer of huge black scales all over its body, each of which was over 100 feet in size. There were also several huge black bone spikes that were thousands of feet in length on its head, and its four sets of claws were astonishingly enormous.

The black wyrm was staring intently at the golden lotus flower with a greedy look on its face, but its gaze then immediately fell upon Han Li as a ferocious gleam surfaced in its eyes.

"Oh, I'm also feeling a little sleepy, Master!" the Pixiu exclaimed in alarm, then instantly flew back to Han Li's waist as a jade pendant.

Before Han Li had a chance to do anything, a gust of scorching wind swept toward him as the black wyrm whipped its tail at him with astonishing power.

Han Li felt the air constrict around him, and the giant draconic tail arrived before him in the blink of an eye, sweeping toward him with devastating power.

His expression changed drastically as he hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air, releasing three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that transformed into a trio of giant azure swords to form a protective barrier in front of him.

Before he had a chance to do anything else, the draconic tail struck the giant swords with an earth-shattering boom, and the three swords shuddered violently before they were flying in three different directions.

However, thankfully, they had managed to defend Han Li from the attack.

In the meantime, Han Li hurriedly made a hand seal, and the flying carriage shot back in retreat as he made a beckoning motion to summon his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords back to himself.

This black wyrm was even more formidable than that giant Sand Beast!

Chapter 543: Battle

After sending Han Li flying with a swipe of its claws, the black wyrm paid no further heed to him and swooped down to make a grab for the golden lotus flower.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this.

He could tell that the black wyrm possessed incredible power, but the golden lotus flower was an extremely rare and precious spirit plant, so he was naturally unwilling to pass it up without a fight.

With that in mind, he swept a sleeve through the air to stow the green jade flying carriage away, then flew directly toward the golden lotus flower as a streak of golden light.

However, he wasn't able to get very far before the ground up ahead began to tremble violently, as if an earthquake were taking place, and he instantly stopped cold in his tracks before darting back in retreat at an even faster speed.

Immediately thereafter, the ground up ahead split apart explosively, and an incredibly thick black appendage shot out from underground before sweeping toward the black wyrm.

The black appendage was releasing a burst of tremendous force that swept up a gust of ferocious wind, and even though Han Li was already several thousand feet away, he was still sent flying back involuntarily like a fallen leaf in a storm.

His entire body was dealt an incredibly heavy blow, and he felt as if he were about to fall apart at the seams. If it weren't for his fast reactions and his incredible physical prowess, he would've already been reduced to a pile of mincemeat.

After steadying himself close to 10 kilometers away, he cast his gaze forward to discover that the black appendage was a gargantuan black tentacle that was over 10,000 feet thick.

It was riddled with countless giant suction cups, and at this moment, the tentacle was wrapped around the black wyrm, which was made to resemble a tiny chick that had been caught in the talons of an eagle.

It was roaring and struggling with all its might, but its efforts to free itself were completely futile.

Several more resounding booms rang out in succession, and a few more identical black tentacles erupted out of the nearby ground before also wrapping themselves around the black wyrm, while Han Li looked on in astonishment.

There had been no warning signs at all prior to the emergence of these black tentacles, and he wasn't able to detect them even with his tremendous spiritual sense.

The entire swamp began to tremble and sway as an enormous black figure slowly rose up from the ground behind Han Li.

It was an unimaginably massive creature with a lizard-like upper body.

It had a long and thin neck and a bright red crown of flesh on its head that resembled the comb of a rooster.

However, its lower body resembled that of an octopus, consisting of around a dozen giant tentacles.

The mountainous creature was several dozen times larger than the black wyrm, and its enormous body obscured the entire sky.

Its gargantuan tentacles were flailing violently as they delivered the black wyrm into its mouth, making it resemble a large worm in the beak of a rooster.

An unfathomably powerful aura was emanating from the creature's body, and Han Li's face had turned deathly pale as a sense of horror welled up in his heart for the first time in a very long time.

He immediately turned around and summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, then unleashed his Reversal True Axis ability to flee the scene as quickly as he could.

The creature's bright red eyes immediately settled on him, following which a black tentacle shot forth like lightning. Han Li was already several dozen kilometers away from the gargantuan creature, but its tentacle was able to catch up to him in the blink of an eye before wrapping itself around him.

Wrapped within the black tentacle, a burst of tremendous force was constricting around Han Li from all directions, causing all of the bones in his body to creak and groan.

He gave a muffled groan as he reversed the direction of revolution of his Mantra Treasured Axis so that it was revolving conventionally again.

Countless golden ripples emerged before spreading outward in all directions, instantly encompassing the surrounding area in a radius of over 10,000 feet, enveloping part of the black tentacle as well.

The part of the tentacle that was enshrouded within the golden ripples was instantly immobilized, and the black creature let loose a low roar as it tugged its tentacle back with tremendous force.

The golden ripples shuddered violently, looking as if they were about to fall apart at any moment.

Right at this moment, a burst of golden lightning flashed past, and all of the golden ripples vanished in a flash.

As a result, the black tentacle was freed, and it flew back to the gargantuan creature, which unfurled its tentacles, only to discover with a surprised expression that Han Li was already nowhere to be seen.

Meanwhile, Han Li appeared out of thin air thousands of kilometers away amid a flash of golden lightning. His face was deathly pale, there was blood trickling down from the corner of his lips, and one of his arms had been twisted to a grotesque angle.

He paid no heed to his own injuries as a burst of dazzling golden lightning erupted out of his body to form another lightning teleportation array, immediately following which he vanished from the spot once again.

......

In the sky above a lush forest, a golden lightning array quickly took shape, and Han Li appeared at the center of the array, then scoured his surroundings momentarily before heaving a long sigh of relief.

Immediately thereafter, Jin Tong and the Pixiu appeared beside him, and the former's face was also pale from fright as she exclaimed, "What was that thing, Uncle? I was so scared..."

The Pixiu was also looking quite shell-shocked.

At this point, Han Li had regained some of his composure, and he replied, "I'm not sure. It must've been some kind of primordial true spirit."

"Are primordial true spirits that scary? I thought they would all only be similar to that big Sand Beast," Jin Tong said with a hint of lingering fear in her eyes.

She then turned to the Pixiu with an enraged expression as she accused, "Xiao Bai, weren't you born in the primordial land? How could you lead us into such a dangerous place? Were you trying to get us killed?"

"I was born in the primordial land, but I was taken away by primordial hunters not long after I was born, so I don't know much about this place at all. On top of that, I've already signed a contract with Master, and if he dies, I'll be in a terrible position as well, so there's no way I would've willingly led us into danger like that!" the Pixiu hurriedly argued.

This made sense to Jin Tong, and she gave a cold harrumph before dropping the subject.

"Looks like we've underestimated the primordial land," Han Li murmured to himself.

They hadn't encountered any significant peril during this journey through the primordial land thus far, and as a result, he had become a little complacent, which had almost cost him his life.

He quickly swallowed a recovery pill to heal his broken arm, then cast his gaze toward the primordial landscape up ahead with furrowed brows.

It hadn't been long since they entered the primordial land, yet they had already encountered such a fearsome creature, and there was no telling what other perils laid up ahead.

"What do we do now, Uncle?" Jin Tong asked.

Han Li made a hand seal to conjure up a projection of a map in mid-air, one that depicted the areas that they had previously passed through, as well as areas that appeared repeatedly in the maps that he had previously purchased.

This was a map that he had put together by referencing the map given to him by Wyrm 3 and the ones that he had purchased from Primordial Origin City.

"Let's go here," Han Li decided as he pointed at a hilly region on the map.

"Bright Deer Hill..." Jin Tong read aloud as she looked at the spot on the map that Han LI was pointing at.

"According to the map, Bright Deer Hill isn't too far away from here, and there aren't any large primordial tribes residing in the area, so let's go and rest there for a while before we make a decision on where to go next," Han Li said.

He then swept a hand through the air to erase the projected map, following which the green jade flying carriage set off into the distance at a low altitude.

In the wake of that close call, Han Li knew that he had to be more wary of the primordial land, and he activated all of the flying carriage's protective restrictions, even though doing so was quite costly in terms of Immortal Origin Stones. On top of that, he didn't search for any more treasures, and after flying uneventfully for about half a month, they finally arrived on the edge of Bright Deer Hill.

The dense vegetation on the ground below was gradually becoming sparser here, and even though it was already late at night, Han Li could still see some ferocious beasts prowling through the forest for food or engaged in battle with one another down below.

Some of the more sensitive creatures were able to detect the flying carriage, and they immediately roared up at the heavens to establish their dominance.

Han Li cast his gaze into the distance, and a perplexed look suddenly appeared on his face.

He could sense bursts of powerful spiritual qi fluctuations surging through the air several hundred kilometers up ahead, and it seemed that there were many people locked in battle there.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to stow his flying carriage away, then put on his Dragon 5 mask, using which he disguised himself as an unremarkable-looking middle-aged man.

At the same time, he completely concealed his own aura before flying toward the battlefield up ahead in a stealthy fashion.

As he flew through the air, the spiritual qi fluctuations up ahead became stronger and stronger, and upon reaching within 25 kilometers of the battlefield, Han Li descended into sparse forest down below before advancing through the forest on foot.

Before long, he arrived in front of a spacious clearing where an elevated bonfire stand was situated. There was a bright bonfire lit on the stand, illuminating the entire surrounding area, while two groups of strange-looking foreign beings were locked in a fierce battle.

One of the camps of foreign beings were humanoid in appearance, but they were very tall and wiry with extremely long necks. Each of them was standing at around 10 feet tall, and their bodies were dark green in color. Furthermore, there were pairs of long white tusks protruding out of their mouths before curling away to the side.

In contrast, their opponents were far more horrific in appearance.

These creatures were only around five feet tall, but they possessed extremely wide and bloated bodies that were gray in color and covered in thick slabs of armor-like exoskeletons. They had virtually no necks, with nothing separating their chins and chests, and their lips were wide and thick, giving them the appearance of giant bipedal toads.

Chapter 544: Conflict

Han Li observed the unfolding battle with a contemplative look in his eyes.

Each side only had several dozen people, but they were displaying some rather interesting modes of attack.

Among the humanoid creatures, some of them were holding short flutes crafted from some type of unknown material, some were holding small drums crafted from beast bones and beast hide, while others were holding copper bells, and they were playing these instruments to release bursts of soundwaves.

Under the influence of these soundwaves, hundreds of demon beasts of different descriptions were rushing toward the opposing toad-like creatures like puppets on strings.

As for the toad-like creatures, they were exposing their bellies, and it sounded as if there were someone pounding their bellies from inside their bodies, producing a peculiar sound that sent various types of spirit insects flying through the air or rushing out of the ground to swarm toward the opposing humanoid creatures.

Among these spirit insects were golden praying mantises the size of cows and horses, as well as some that were as tiny as bees. Individually, none of them were all that formidable, but under the influence of the toad-like creatures, their auras were combined as one, allowing them to match up against their opponents on equal terms.

Among the demon beasts, some had thick exoskeletons, some possessed enormous bodies, some were able to blast forth flames and lightning, and some were extremely fast, but they were unable to keep the spirit insects at bay and were constantly being forced back further and further into retreat.

The humanoid creatures could see that the situation was unfolding against their favor, and one of them, a man with the longest neck, wearing a necklace crafted out of beast bones, let loose a loud roar.

All of the sounds that were controlling the demon beasts and the spirit insects instantly subsided, and as a result, a temporary truce ensued.

The man then opened his mouth to say something that was completely unintelligible to Han Li.

"Can you understand what they're saying?" Han Li asked through his spiritual connection between himself and the jade Pixiu.

"He's speaking in the universal language used by the primordial tribes, and he's talking to a person called Tureev, asking him why they were so insistent on hunting down their Longneck Tribe, even though they had already abandoned the forest that they had been residing in for generations to flee all the way here," the Pixiu translated.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he cast his gaze toward the toad-like beings.

One of the toad-like creatures that was wearing a layer of azure leather armor around its waist stepped forward, then said something in response in a loud and resonant voice.

"He says, don't be naive, Taj. Our Gray Toad Tribe and your Longneck Tribe have always been sworn enemies. Now that your Longneck Tribe has fallen from grace, of course we have to hunt you down and eradicate all of you," Xiao Bai translated without even being prompted by Han Li.

"How dare you! Are you trying to instigate a war between our Beast Race and your Insect Race? Are you not afraid of repeating the same horrific tragedy from millions of years ago? If you spark a war between our two races, our Beast Race will be sure to wipe out all of you once and for all!" Taj replied in a furious voice.

"I know that you've led us here as a distraction to try and divert us away, while your father led the majority of your tribesmen to the Peacock Spirit Tribe over at the Peacock River, but I can tell you now that your efforts are completely futile. Even the Tower Elephant Tribe and the Dark Hog Tribe have already been conquered by our Insect Race, let alone the Peacock Spirit Tribe," Tureev chortled as he slapped his own belly with his large hands.

Taj's expression instantly changed drastically upon hearing this. "What did you say? That's impossible!"

"In the face of the insect spirits that we revere, the true spirits that you worship are nothing more than a bunch of toothless dogs! Our Insect Race has been plotting its revenge for the past several million years, and it's finally time for your Beast Race to face the flames of our wrath!" Tureev continued as a fervent look appeared in his eyes.

After hearing Xiao Bai's translation, Han Li concluded, "Looks like this is a conflict between two primordial tribes that has nothing to do with us."

He then turned to depart, but right at this moment, the golden ring on his finger transformed into Jin Tong, who landed by his side, and her cheeks were slightly flushed with apprehension as she said, "Don't leave just yet, Uncle, I'm getting a very strange feeling..."

"Could it be that you've been affected by the insect manipulation techniques used by those creatures? Surely not! Even their leader is only a True Immortal, how could they possibly have affected you?" Han Li mused with a perplexed expression.

"I... I don't know... I just feel... really strange..." Jin Tong stuttered.

As soon as her voice trailed off, a pair of golden praying mantises suddenly pounced at Han Li and Jin Tong from either flank before lashing out with their scythe-like appendages.

Han Li immediately swept a sleeve through the air upon seeing this, releasing two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that shot forth toward the pair of oncoming praying mantises, slicing them in half in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, a swarm of black beetles converged from all directions to surround Han Li and Jin Tong, and some of the Gray Toad beings also began to make their way toward Han Li's duo.

Seeing as they had already been exposed, Han Li emerged into the clearing with Jin Tong.

Tureev took a glance at Han Li and Jin Tong, and his expression changed drastically as he began to speak again, and furious looks instantly appeared on the faces of the Longneck beings upon hearing what he had to say.

"What are they saying?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"Tureev is accusing the Longneck Tribe of falling into depravity and colluding with humans. He says that it's no wonder that even the true spirits that they worship aren't able to protect them, and the Longneck beings are very angry to hear this," the jade Pixiu replied.

"It sounds like humans aren't very popular around these parts," Han Li mused with a wry smile.

"Humans aren't the only ones that are denounced here, any beings of any race who come from the immortal regions have always come to the primordial land solely to plunder and steal and..."

The jade Pixiu's voice trailed off here.

Indeed, the title of primordial hunter sounded quite prestigious, but they were nothing more than opportunistic gatherers and bandits.

"Tell them that we're just passing through, and that we have no intention of getting involved in their conflict," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air, and the jade pendant hanging from his waist flew through the air before transforming into a jade Pixiu that was around 10 feet in length.

Xiao Bai took a glance at Han Li, then turned to the two groups of primordial beings as it relayed Han Li's message to them.

Tureev took a glance at Xiao Bai, then turned his gaze to Jin Tong before finally turning his attention to Han Li, following which it declared in the language of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, "I would've been willing to let you go, but you just killed two of our spirit insects. How do you plan to compensate for that?"

"What compensation do you want from me?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Leave that little girl behind and I'll let you go," Tureev declared as he pointed a finger at Jin Tong.

Han Li couldn't help but heave a forlorn internal sigh upon hearing this. He knew that a peaceful resolution was out of the question now.

Sure enough, before he had a chance to say anything, Jin Tong had already stepped forward with an enraged expression as she began rolling up her sleeves.

"You want me to stay, do you?" she asked in a cold voice as her aura began to swell rapidly.

Tureev was very alarmed to sense her rapidly elevating aura, and all of the black beetles around Jin Tong instantly began to rush back in retreat out of an instinctive sense of fear.

Tureev took a few steps backward before hurriedly urging all of his tribesmen to spring into action, and the other Gray Toad beings immediately began to produce the same croaking sound from before with their bloated bellies.

A small portion of the spirit insects that they had summoned were still surrounding the Longneck beings, but the rest were all swarming toward Jin Tong.

"Go and help her," Han Lin instructed with slightly furrowed brows.

Xiao Bai immediately did as it was told, swelling drastically in size as it let loose a loud roar before pouncing at the swarm of spirit insects.

The dense swarm of black beetles inundated Xiao Bai in an instant, but a layer of bright white light had emerged over its body to keep all of the black beetles at bay.

At the same time, it opened its mouth to release a burst of tremendous suction force, which sucked in all of the surrounding black beetles in a frenzy.

Meanwhile, Taj and the other Longneck beings were discussing how to proceed, yet all of them had fallen silent and were staring at Xiao Bai with stunned looks on their faces.

At the same time, Jin Tong had transformed into a giant golden beetle that was slashing its front legs through the air in rapid succession, releasing streaks of translucent golden light that swept forth in all directions, shredding all of the spirit insects in their path.

Tureev was horrified to see this.

In the blink of an eye, his army of spirit insects was on the verge of complete eradication!

In contrast, Taj was ecstatic to see this, and he hurriedly began yelling something in the primordial language.

The Longneck beings were instantly reinvigorated, and they began playing their instruments again, spurring on their demon beasts to attack the surrounding swarm of spirit insects.

The previously orderly ranks of the Gray Toad beings were instantly thrown into complete disarray by Jin Tong and Xiao Bai, and Tureev was frantically instructing his spirit insects to unleash a final wave of attacks while simultaneously instructing his own tribesmen to retreat.

Chapter 545: Esteemed Guest

Han Li couldn't understand what Tureev was seeing, but he was immediately able to see through his intentions, and he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing several thousands dark yellow beans that transformed into Dao Warriors before rushing into the swarm of insects.

Meanwhile, Jin Tong flew out of the swarm of insects as a streak of golden light before arriving in front of the Gray Toad beings in a flash, then lashed out with her front legs to send a flurry of streaks of translucent golden light sweeping through the air, instantly killing most of the Gray Toad beings.

Tureev could see that escape wasn't going to be possible, and he immediately fell to his knees as he pleaded, "Please spare us! Why are you killing us when you're a member of the Insect Race yourself? All of us Gray Toad beings are insect envoys, we are loyal servants of the revered insect spirits! I only asked him to leave you behind so that we could take you back to our Insect Race and save you from having to serve as that human's pet!"

Jin Tong ceased in her attacks upon hearing this, and she reverted back to her human form before returning to Han Li's side, then asked, "What is this insect spirit that you speak of?"

"I... I'm afraid I don't know. Our Gray Toad Tribe is nothing more than a tiny branch of the Insect Race. Even though I'm the chief of the tribe, I've only ever heard of the revered insect spirit and never actually had the honor of meeting them," Tureev replied in a hesitant voice.

Jin Tong turned to Han Li upon hearing this, then asked, "Can we use a soul search technique on him, Uncle?"

"Sure," Han Li replied with a nod, then pointed a finger forward, upon which a thread of translucent light flew into Tureev's glabella.

"No!" Tureev wailed with a horrified expression, only for his head to explode violently just an instant later.

"That's quite a nasty restriction," Han Li remarked as his brows furrowed slightly.

The remaining Gray Toad beings were furious to see the demise of their chief, and they began charging at Han Li once again.

Several seconds later, the entire clearing fell completely silent, and all of the Gray Toad beings had been eradicated.

After stowing his Dao Warriors away, Han Li turned to the Longneck beings, who were clearly apprehensive of him, but didn't dare to leave without permission.

All of the Longneck beings were also looking back at Han Li with a mixture of fear and confusion in their eyes, and it was clear that they didn't know how to react to what had just happened.

The man by the name of Taj hesitated momentarily, then voluntarily approached Han Li before extending a grateful salute as he said in the language of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, "Thank you for saving us, Senior."

"Seeing as you can understand my language, I'm sure you're already aware that I didn't kill those Gray Toad beings to save you and your tribesmen," Han Li said as he took a glance at Taj.

"In any case, you've saved all of us by killing those Gray Toad beings, and that is a great kindness that we must repay. However, at the moment, our tribe has been severely ravaged by the Insect Race, so I'm afraid we're in no position to be holding a reception. Otherwise, we would be sure to invite you to our tribe as an esteemed guest," Taj replied in an apologetic manner.

Han Li wanted to dismiss the Longneck beings, but after taking a glance at Jin Tong, he decided to raise some questions instead. "What's going on with the Beast Race and the Insect Race?"

A hesitant look appeared on Taj's face, and only after a brief pause did he reply, "The Insect Race and our Beast Race have different beliefs, and as a result, we've become sworn enemies. We've been fighting relentlessly against each other over the years, and many large-scale wars have taken place between our two races."

"What are these differing beliefs of yours?" Han Li asked.

"Our Beast Race is split up into many different tribes, and all of us worship different true spirit holy beasts. We don't always see eye to eye, but all of us revere true spirits, while all of the tribes of the Insect Race worship different insect spirits," Taj explained.

"I see. That's all I have to ask, you can go now," Han Li said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

"Thank you, Senior," Taj hurriedly replied with a respectful bow, then began making his way back to his tribesmen.

"Let's go," Han Li said as he turned to Jin Tong and Xiao Bai, the latter of which reverted back into a jade pendant before flying back to Han Li's waist.

Meanwhile, Jin Tong was looking a little hesitant, and Han Li knew that this had to have something to do with those Gray Toad beings, so he didn't try to rush her.

Right at this moment, Taj made his way back to Han Li, then extended another respectful salute as he said, "After careful consideration, I feel that it's necessary to invite you to travel to the Peacock Spirit Tribe with us so we can show you some hospitality and repay you for your kindness."

"If you really want to display your sincerity, then get your true leader to come out and see me," Han Li said in an indifferent voice.

A surprised look appeared on Taj's face upon hearing this.

Immediately thereafter, the group of Longneck beings parted to open up a path, following which a a figure dressed in a large gray cloak with a gray cloth concealing their facial features emerged.

"Young Mistress Yifan, you can't..."

Taj hurriedly tried to stop them, but the cloaked figure paid no heed to him as they made their way over to Han Li, then crossed their arms of their chest before extending a salute to him.

After that, they removed the gray cloth that was concealing their face to reveal an extremely intricate set of facial features that were virtually no different from those of a human. The only difference was that their skin was light blue, and their ears tapered to sharp points, while a pair of sharp fangs were protruding out from behind their lips.

"You're not a Longneck being?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

Earlier, he had noticed that Taj seemed to have been acting under the instructions of someone else, and he had thought that perhaps the chief of the Longneck Tribe was among them, but that didn't appear to be the case.

"I am Nuo Yifan, the daughter of the Calm Dawn Tribe, and I was sent here to unite all of the tribe of the Beast Race to put up a collective resistance against the Insect Race, but as soon as I arrived at the Longneck Tribe, we were attacked by the Gray Toad Tribe and several other tribes, and we fled all the way here. It's only thanks to your timely intervention that we were able to survive, Senior," the blue-skinned woman said.

"Seeing as you're the one calling the shots here, I presume it's you who's inviting me to the Peacock Spirit Tribe?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. You must be a primordial hunter, right, Senior? The Insect Race has recently become more and more aggressive. Not only are they attacking our Beast Race, I've heard that they instructed the Sand Beasts to attack a ship not long ago. If you're not familiar with this area, then you could easily stumble into their territory, and even with your unfathomable powers, a grueling battle would be inevitable," Nuo Yifan said.

"So you're extending this invitation to me for my sake?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"I wish to repay you for saving all of us, but of course, my motives aren't entirely unselfish. I'm hoping that you can protect us on the way back to the Calm Dawn Tribe," Nuo Yifan replied in a candid fashion.

"Would your tribe happen to have a map of the primordial land?" Han Li asked.

"The primordial land is an enormous place, and many areas are ruled over by different powerful beings and tribes, making them inaccessible to others. Hence, even our Calm Dawn Tribe only has a map of some areas occupied by our Beast Race. As long as you're willing to escort us back to our Calm Dawn Tribe, I'll do my best to collect all of the maps in the possession of the nearby tribes," Nuo Yifan promised.

Han Li considered the offer for a moment, then decided to agree.

A hint of elation immediately flashed through Nuo Yifan's eyes as she said, "Thank you, Senior! May I ask your name?"

"My name is Li Feiyu," Han Li replied.

As Taj brought Han Li and Jin Tong back to the rest of the group, the other Longneck beings all began to watch Han Li's duo with clear apprehension and fear in their eyes.

Taj said something to everyone in the primordial tongue, and only then did all of the Longneck beings look away from Han Li and Jin Tong before commencing the process of cleaning up the battlefield.

At the same time, some of them began to collect the carcasses of the Gray Toad beings and the spirit insects, clearly finding them to be useful as materials.

Shortly thereafter, one of the Longneck beings exchanged a glance with Nuo Yifan, following which the former carried a storage ring that was crafted out of bone and laden with materials to Han Li.

Han Li wasn't particularly interested in these materials, but he still accepted the storage ring. After all, if he were to refuse, then that would most likely only make the Longneck beings even more uneasy as they could develop the false impression that he was harboring certain ulterior motives.

However, after accepting the storage ring, he immediately assigned its contents to Xiao Bai and Jin Tong for them to split and devour as they pleased.

Shortly thereafter, the entire group of Longneck beings set off once again, this time toward the south.

Taj was leading the way from the forefront, while Han Li and Nuo Yifan were walking alongside one another at the center of the unit, surrounded by all of the other Longneck beings. As for Jin Tong and Xiao Bai, they had already turned back into a pair of accessories that were fitted around Han Li's finger and hanging from his waist, respectively.

"Once we pass over this hilly region, we'll enter an area where a Hundred-eyed Centipede is active. The centipede is extremely formidable and aggressive, and it's been known to attack anything flying overhead. Hence, we'll only be able to take flight on demon beast steeds once we've passed through that area," Nuo Yifan explained.

"That's fine. The primordial land is a very dangerous place, so it makes sense to take some safety precautions," Han LI replied in an indifferent voice.

At this point, they were already deep in the primordial land, so he naturally had no interest in taking any risks unless it was absolutely necessary to do so.

As he continued to walk along, Han Li declared through voice transmission, "Xiao Bai, I want you to teach me the primordial language."

Xiao Bai was very much taken aback to hear this, and it exclaimed, "The cultivators of the immortal regions have always regarded the primordial language as a lowly language that's completely beneath them. Are you sure you want to learn it, Master?"

"Languages are but tools for communication, so I don't perceive any languages to be above or below others," Han Li replied.

"Alright, if you want to learn, then I'll teach you," Xiao Bai replied.

Chapter 546: Large Primordial Tribe

Over a month flew by in the blink of an eye.

In the sky above a lush, primordial forest, giant flying creatures of different descriptions were soaring through the air, carrying Longneck beings on their backs as they descended toward the center of the forest.

There was an unremarkable-looking male human among these Longneck beings, standing out like a sore thumb, and it was none other than Han Li.

Taj was straddled atop a winged black deer while flying alongside Nuo Yifan, who was riding a white snow eagle, and they were on a diagonal descent toward a clearing at the center of the forest.

As for Han Li, he was riding a gray mammoth with a pair of ears that were as large as wings, and he was also descending out of the sky a little behind the Longneck beings.

After landing on the ground, Han Li inspected his surroundings briefly to find that there were some dome-shaped buildings concealed within the foliage, blending into the surrounding environment in a harmonious fashion.

However, most of these buildings had already been damaged. Some were half-collapsed, while others had been completely razed to the ground, and a series of lifeless bodies were littered around the buildings.

Most of these bodies belonged to a type of short and petite gray-skinned creature with large heads and facial features that were very similar to those of humans, except their eyes, noses, and mouths were all squished together, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

Additionally, there were also many bodies belonging to Longneck beings and demon beast carcasses strewn around the area, most of which had been horribly disfigured by spirit insect bites.

After conducting a brief search through the area, the expressions of all of the Longneck beings had darkened significantly, and all of them were clearly infuriated by what they had seen.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li saw Taj carrying the body of an elderly Longneck being out of the one of the semi-collapsed buildings, and there was a grief-stricken look on his face.

The body's facial features bore a strong resemblance to Taj, and this observation made it apparent to Han Li that this was most likely Taj's father and the chief of the Longneck Tribe.

Nuo Yifan made her way over to Taj, then crossed her arms in front of her chest and extended a deep bow toward the lifeless body in Taj's arms. After that, she patted Taj on the shoulder and said something to him in the primordial language.

Having already learned some of the primordial language from Xiao Bai on the way here, Han Li was able to discern that she was offering him some condolences.

Taj took some time to compose himself, then fished a long length of black bone that was as smooth as jade out of his father's pocket. He raised the bone up high as he let loose a cry of grief, and all of the other Longneck beings immediately gathered around him while echoing the same sound.

Meanwhile, Nuo Yifan made her way over to Han Li's side as she explained in a slight weary voice, "Taj's father died in battle, and he's about to become the new chief of the tribe."

"It looks like your Beast Race isn't in a very good place right now," Han Li remarked.

"Ever since we defeated the Insect Race during that war several million years ago, all of our tribes have been far too complacent. We've always been keeping close tabs on the Insect Race's activities, but they've been planning these attacks for a very long time, and they struck without any warning, so we were caught completely off guard.

“Having said that, the king of the true spirits that we worship are definitely far more powerful than their insect spirits, so once all of our tribes unite to summon our king, the complete eradication of the Insect Race will be imminent," Nuo Yifan replied in a determined voice.

Han Li wasn't very interested in hearing about these matters, and he said, "I suppose I can only wish you the best of luck. How long left until we reach your Calm Dawn Tribe?"

"At our current speed, we'll be able to return to our Calm Dawn Tribe in three more months at most," Nuo Yifan replied.

Han Li nodded in response and didn't say anything further.

The Longneck beings held a simple ceremony to grieve the dead, then packed up the bodies of all of their fellow tribesmen and the Peacock Spirit beings before setting off once again.

After leaving the settlement of the Peacock Spirit Tribe, everyone clearly sped up significantly, perhaps because they were out of the territory under the complete control of the Beast Race. Aside from several occasions where they had to slow down to avoid some particularly powerful primordial beasts, the rest of the time was spent traveling at full speed.

During this time, Han Li continued to learn the primordial language from Xiao Bai while keeping tabs on the area that they had passed through so that he could incorporate them into the map that he was compiling.

At this point, the maps that he had purchased from Primordial Origin City early were largely useless. The map given to him by Wyrm 3 was still somewhat useful, but it had no overlap with the route that he was currently taking, so he could only use it to ascertain his approximate location.

Two and a half months later, Han Li and the Longneck beings finally made it out of the vast forest.

The Longneck beings were very familiar with this forest, so they were able to pre-emptively avoid many of the powerful true spirits residing in the area, but they were still intercepted by a few ambush attacks from enemy Insect Race beings. Han Li had refrained from getting involved in those battles, leaving Jin Tong and Xiao Bai to do the fighting for him.

Over time, the animosity and wariness that the Longneck beings harbored toward Han Li gradually faded, and Han Li was able to learn more about the primordial land from Nuo Yifan and Taj.

At this moment, they had arrived in front of an enormous canyon.

This was the Dark Star Canyon where the Calm Dawn Tribe resided.

Even though Han Li had already been made aware that the Calm Dawn Tribe was one of the most powerful tribes of the Beast Race, he was still astonished by the sight laid out before him.

Ahead of him was a majestic mountain range that stretched as far as the eyes could see, and there were countless acres of lush vegetation separated by a gargantuan white rift, much like a gash on the body of a giant beast.

At the entrance of the white canyon stood an enormous white stone pass, which was riddled with watchtowers and flags, giving it the appearance of a massive white fortress.

The entire fortress was over 100,000 feet tall, virtually the same height as the two lips of the canyon, and there were three giant arch gates that were around 60,000 to 70,000 feet tall standing at the center of the fortress, in front of each of which was a black metal fence.

A massive, turbulent river was flowing through the central arch gate, and the water in the river was a rather murky green color, churning along while producing a sound akin to that of rumbling thunder.

Upon arriving at the fortress, Nuo Yifan removed the long gray cloak that she had been wearing the entire trip, revealing the luscious curves of her body, which were only accentuated by the light and tight-fitting clothes that she was wearing underneath the cloak.

All of the male Longneck beings couldn't help but gawk at her for a moment before hurriedly looking away.

As for Han Li, he was watching Nuo Yifan with a hint of surprise in his eyes. He didn't know what material the gray cloak was woven from, but it had completely concealed Nuo Yifan's aura, and only now did he realize that she was at the late-True Immortal Stage.

It seemed that even in the primordial land, there existed some tool refinement techniques, but he presumed that only a small number of powerful primordial tribes would be able to afford the services of these tool refinement masters.

Right at this moment, several dozen figures flew out of the fortress, and all of them were rather similar to Nuo Yifan in appearance, with light blue skin and tapered ears, clearly indicating that they were also Calm Dawn beings.

The majority of them were men, who were slightly taller than their female counterparts and had some dark patterns on their skin. However, they weren't physically imposing at all, and not only were they all quite handsome, there was a slightly effeminate appearance about them.

Their leader was a middle-aged man holding an azure jade staff, and he bore a strong resemblance to Nuo Yifan, except the lines of his face were more angular and defined, and he was wearing a long off white robe that gave him a scholarly appearance.

"Yifan," the man called out, and an ecstatic look immediately appeared on Nuo Yifan's face upon catching sight of him.

"Father!"

Meanwhile, the Longneck beings and Han Li were all hovering in the air some distance away.

At this point, Han Li was able to understand the primordial language without much trouble, but he still had some trouble speaking the language due to lack of practice.

"I'm sorry for putting you through such an ordeal, my precious daughter. I'm so glad that you've returned safe and sound," the middle-aged man said with a pained expression as he gently stroked Nuo Yifan's hair.

"I wanted to go on this trip, so you're not to blame, Father. It was a dangerous trip, but thankfully, we've managed to contact all of the northern tribes, and they've all decided to join forces with our Dark Star Canyon. I'm sure it won't be long before we unite the entire Beast Race in the war against the Insect Race," Nuo Yifan said.

"You did very well, my daughter. Over the past half a month or so, some tribes have already arrived at our Dark Star Canyon. However, I heard from them that the Longneck Tribe and the Peacock Spirit Tribe were attacked. Were you affected by the attacks?" the middle-aged man asked.

"While I was at the Longneck Tribe, we were attacked by several enemy tribes, including the Gray Toad Tribe and the Azure Scorpion Tribe, but Chief Taj of the Longneck Tribe was able to divert most of the enemy forces away by fleeing to the Peacock Spirit Tribe, while the other Longneck beings and I fled to Bright Deer Hill.

“After that, the Gray Toad beings caught up to us, but thankfully, Senior Li here intervened to save us and eradicate the Gray Toad beings," Nuo Yifan replied as she gestured to Han Li.

A hint of lingering fear appeared in the middle-aged man's eyes upon hearing this, and he was feeling even more remorseful after hearing about his daughter's close call.

Upon hearing that it was Han Li who had eradicated the Gray Toad beings, he cast his gaze toward his daughter's savior, upon which his pupils instantly contracted slightly.

Not only was he very much taken aback to see that Han Li was a human, all of the other Calm Dawn beings displayed a similar reaction upon catching sight of him.

Due to the fact that Calm Dawn beings were quite similar in appearance to humans, Han Li could clearly see the detest and wariness etched on their faces.

Nuo Yifan could also see the animosity that everyone was displaying, and she immediately added, "It was only thanks to Senior Li's protection that we were able to make it back here safely."

The middle-aged man's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he flew toward Han Li with everyone else.

"Thank you for saving Yifan and escorting her back to our Dark Star Canyon. If you want anything for compensation, feel free to state what you desire," the middle-aged man said in the language of the immortal regions as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this.

It was clear that the chief of the Calm Dawn Tribe intended to send him away with some treasures, as opposed to allowing him to enter the Dark Star Canyon.

Chapter 547: Stay

"There's no need to thank me. On the topic of compensation, I've already told your daughter what I want," Han Li replied in an expressionless manner.

The white-robed man's brows furrowed with befuddlement, and he turned to her with an inquisitive expression, upon which Nuo Yifan relayed Han Li's request for maps of the primordial land to him through voice transmission.

The white-robed man's brows furrowed even more tightly upon hearing this, and he turned back to Han Li as he said, "My apologies, Fellow Daoist Li, but I'm afraid that my daughter has made a promise that she can't keep. Our Calm Dawn Tribe is quite a large tribe, but it's still completely insignificant in the context of all of the Beast Race tribes, so we're not capable of gathering all of the maps of the different tribes.

“Hence, I'll have to ask you to state another condition. I know the rules of the human race, and I'll be sure to offer you satisfactory compensation."

"I'm not a primordial hunter, and I'm only asking for these maps as I wish to cross the primordial land en route to another immortal region. Hence, you can remove the locations of the tribes on the maps that you give me and only mark out the more dangerous areas and places where formidable beasts reside," Han Li said.

A contemplative look appeared on Nuo Qinglin's face upon hearing this, and he didn't immediately respond.

Nuo Yifan approached him, and the two of them communicated a while longer through voice transmission before the latter seemed to have finally arrived at a decision.

Nuo Qinglin turned back to Han Li, but still found himself unable to ascertain Han Li's cultivation base.

"In that case, I'll get you to stay in our Dark Star Canyon for a few days. The other tribes of the Beast Race will be gathering here over the next few days, and I'll be able to collect their maps once they arrive," he said.

"I'll be in your care then," Han Li replied with a nod.

While conversing with Nuo Qinglin, Han Li had been observing him the entire time as well, and he noticed that Nuo Qinglin seemed to have also concealed his own aura, and that he was most likely around the early-Golden Immortal Stage.

However, given how these foreign beings were able to use demon beasts in battle, their true combat prowess most likely had to be overestimated by half a rank. As for the other Calm Dawn beings behind Nuo Qinglin, they were all somewhere between the mid-True Immortal Stage and the early-Golden Immortal Stage, with the majority of them at the True Immortal Stage.

Nuo Qinglin gave Han Li a nod, then turned to Taj with a solemn expression as he said, "Thank you for escorting Yifan back to our Dark Star Canyon. Our Calm Dawn Tribe will remember what you've done, and after the war is over, we'll be sure to do everything in our power to assist your tribe in rebuilding a home and making a resurgence."

"Thank you, Chief Nuo!" Taj replied with a grateful expression as he crossed his arms over his chest and extended a slight bow.

"Prior to that, you and your tribesmen can treat our Dark Star Canyon as your own home," Nuo Qinglin continued.

Taj and the other Longneck beings were even more grateful upon hearing this, and some of them had even burst into tears.

After that, Nuo Qinglin led Han Li and the others over the giant fortress before flying into the canyon.

As they flew over the fortress, Han Li could see that there was a giant lizard-like winged beast prowling behind each of the watchtowers on the fortress. Their scales were reflecting a black gleam, and they occasionally opened their eyes to look up at the sky.

Han Li could clearly sense that all of their animosity was directed toward him.

Only after passing over the fortress was the true scale of the Dark Star Canyon fully revealed to Han Li.

There was a green river that was over 10,000 feet wide flowing through the center of the canyon with the sound of rumbling thunder, and on either side of the river were sheer cliff faces that were as steep as they were majestic.

On the sheer mountain faces at an even higher altitude were a series of hollowed-out caves of different shapes and sizes, all of which were interconnected by a system boardwalks that were embedded into the mountain faces to form an enormous and complex cluster of buildings.

Furthermore, these weren't just some simple and crude caves. Instead, there were intricate engravings and well-crafted pillars and railings on the outside, and their openings were sealed with round or rectangular wooden doors of different styles that also had beautiful engravings on them. On top of that, these caves were surrounded by moss, vines, and flowers to give them an even more delightful appearance.

If the Peacock Spirit Tribe settlement had been a small village in a forest, then the Dark Star Canyon where the Calm Dawn Tribe resided would be the equivalent of a thriving human city.

The Dark Star River within the canyon was a winding river that twisted and turned, and the deeper Han Li flew into the canyon, the more surprised he became. A series of giant altar-like buildings had begun to appear on the surrounding mountain faces, and they were giving off bursts of faint array fluctuations.

Han Li knew that he was a rather sensitive figure here, so he only casually glanced at the passing scenery instead of scrutinizing the layout of the entire canyon too closely, and he also refrained from using too much of his spiritual sense.

Nuo Qinglin had been secretly observing Han Li this entire time, and a pleased look appeared on his face upon seeing this.

As the group approached the center of the valley, everyone descended onto a cliff with relatively flat terrain. Nuo Qinglin turned to Han Li as he said, "This is quite a peaceful place. You can stay here for the next few days, Fellow Daoist Li."

Han Li inspected his surroundings to find that the cliff was surrounded by Calm Dawn Tribe settlements, and they weren't overly close, but it was very convenient for them to conduct surveillance on this place or surround it on very short notice.

"Thank you, Chief Nuo," he said with a smile, and Nuo Qinglin and the others promptly departed, flying deeper into the canyon.

Nuo Yifan hesitated momentarily, then decided to stay behind as she approached Han Li with an apologetic expression as she said, "Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Li. Unfortunately, my tribesmen are still quite apprehensive of humans."

"I've always wanted to ask you this: why is it that you aren't wary of humans like your tribesmen?" Han Li asked.

"Truth be told, my deceased mother was a human, so I'm half-human myself," Nuo Yifan explained after a brief hesitation.

Han Li nodded in response and didn't say anything further.

After the two of them parted ways, Han Li inspected his surroundings briefly with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, then descended onto the cliff and began to make his way toward the hollowed-out cave abode there.

He opened the heavy stone doors of the cave abode, and his brows furrowed slightly at the state of the cave abode.

Everything was covered in a thick layer of dust, clearly indicating that it hadn't been inhabited for a very long time. He swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a gentle breeze that swept out all of the dust in the cave abode.

Immediately thereafter, a series of lamps on the walls lit up on their own, illuminating the entire stone chamber while also giving off a faint musky aroma.

Han Li looked around to find that the cave wasn't very large, and it was split into two rooms that were only slightly larger than the average room.

In the outer room was a stone table and a stone chair, while only a stone bed could be found in the inner room, presenting a set of extremely minimalistic furnishings.

After closing the stone doors, Han Li pulled out a series of array flags and array plates before setting them up around the cave.

Around an hour later, the array was complete, and Han Li sat down onto the stone bed with his legs crossed before tapping the golden ring on his finger.

The golden ring immediately took on Jin Tong's human form before landing beside Han Li, and he said, "Jin Tong, I'll be going into seclusion for a while to see if I can elevate my cultivation base a little. During this time, you and Xiao Bai will be tasked with protecting me."

"Why are you suddenly going into seclusion at a time like this, Uncle?" Jin Tong asked.

"During our time in the primordial land, we've encountered many powerful primordial beasts. Even though we'll be staying in the Calm Dawn Tribe for the near future, so we'll be a little safer than before, but we still have to prepare for the journey ahead. The Heavenly Court isn't going to stop coming after me, and the primordial land is far more perilous than I anticipated.

“Only by elevating my own powers as much as possible can we continue to survive here," Han Li replied.

"Alright, you can count on me, Uncle! No one will be able to disturb your cultivation as long as I'm here!" Jin Tong vowed with a determined expression.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he flipped a hand over to produce a storage pouch before handing it to Jin Tong.

"Here's some food for you, make sure to eat it sparingly."

Jin Tong was ecstatic as she accepted the storage pouch from Han Li, then skipped her way to the outer room before sitting down onto the stone table with her legs crossed to inspect the contents of the storage pouch.

"Don't forget about me!"

Xiao Bai immediately jumped down from Han Li's waist before rushing over to Jin Tong's side and cuddling up to her like an affectionate little dog, only to be slapped away by Jin Tong with a disdainful expression.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he withdrew his gaze before sweeping a sleeve through the air to activate the array and temporarily cut off the inner room from the outside world.

He then flipped a hand over to produce a pair of jade slips and an ancient yellow scripture, and these were none other than the three time-attribute cultivation arts of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, the Water Divination Time Arts, the Mantra Axis Scripture, and the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture.

He had already read through the entirety of the three cultivation arts, and he felt like there was some type of connection between the three, but he had never gotten the chance to conduct a closer examination.

Hence, he was planning to compare the three cultivation arts carefully here to see if he could glean some insights that could assist him in his cultivation.

Among the three cultivation arts, the Mantra Axis Scripture was naturally the most familiar one to Han Li. At this point, he had already obtained six levels of the cultivation art, and his progression in the cultivation art had been quite smooth thanks to the Heaven Controlling Vial.

He hadn't begun using either of the other two cultivation arts yet, but given the foundation that he had already had, he was confident that he would be able to make fast progress in those two cultivation arts as well.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he picked up the Water Divination Time Arts first and began to carefully read through it.

Chapter 548: The Three Cultivation Arts

Han Li pressed the jade slip that contained the Water Divination Time Arts to his own glabella, then closed his eyes and fell completely still.

Initially, his brows were slightly furrowed in befuddlement, but they quickly unfurrowed again as if he had been struck by some enlightenment. However, shortly thereafter, his brows furrowed slightly once again before relaxing for a second time, and the cycle continued to repeat itself.

As time passed, Han Li's brows became more and more tightly furrowed, and this time, he remained stumped by the obstacle that he had encountered.

Sweat was beginning to bead up on his forehead, and remained in the same seated position for three days and three nights.

Upon opening his eyes, his back was already completely drenched in sweat, while his eyes were severely bloodshot, giving him an exhausted appearance.

"How could this be?" he murmured to himself as he removed the blue jade slip from his forehead.

The Water Divination Time Arts consisted of seven chapters, and during the initial phase of its cultivation, he had to manifest a treasure similar to the Mantra Treasured Axis.

This treasure was called the Clear Time Vial, and it could derive time water droplets from absorbing the light of the sun and the moon.

Upon reaching the fourth chapter of the cultivation art, one would be able to refine the time water droplets that they had collected in order to manifest threads of time.

These threads of time weren't unfamiliar to Han Li. Even back in the Spirit Realm, he had seen these threads being produced by the Asura Spiders. [1] These were extraordinary threads that could only arise from the river of time, which contained time law powers, and they could extend the lifespans of mortals and low-grade cultivators, or delay the onset of heavenly tribulations for high-grade cultivators.

From the description in the cultivation, the threads of time refined using the Water Divination Time Arts were supposed to contain a greater abundance of time law powers, thereby making them even more potent, and they could even delay the onset of the three decays for True Immortals.

However, as was the case with the Mantra Treasured Axis, an item that contained time law powers was required to refine the Clear Time Vial. Additionally, many other precious natural treasures were also required, thereby posing a very steep barrier of entry for this cultivation art, and this was presumably why so many Vast Flow Palace cultivators had ultimately refrained from pursuing this cultivation art.

Unlike the Mantra Axis Scripture, this cultivation art didn't allow one to open immortal acupoints as they progressed. Instead, the improvement in one's cutivation base more so hinged upon the rate at which they were able to manifest time water droplets.

Apparently, once one accumulated sufficient time water droplets to form a river, they would be able to unleash even more unfathomable abilities. However, these time water droplets took a very long time to manifest, and in the initial phase of one's cultivation, it would take centuries to accumulate even a single time water droplet, so it was unclear how much time it would take to accumulate an entire river's worth.

From what he had read, Han Li determined that the Water Divination Time Arts was slightly inferior to the Mantra Axis Scripture, but it had its own unique advantages as well.

At this point, he had only read through the cultivation art several times, and he hadn't begun cultivating it at all, so his understanding of it was naturally still rather limited.

He took a deep breath to suppress the befuddlement in his heart, then began to read through the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture.

The inner room was completely silent with the exception of the sound of rustling pages, and over a day passed by in a flash before Han Li closed the book.

He massaged his sore glabella momentarily, but at the same time, a faint smile had appeared on his face.

The Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture was even more unique than the other two time-attribute cultivation arts. As opposed to a cultivation art, it was more accurate to call it a tool refinement scripture.

The reason why Han Li thought this was because upon reaching a certain stage in the cultivation art, one would be able to break down certain items that contained time law powers to derive something called Illusory Dawn Sand.

After refining this Illusory Dawn Sand using a special technique, one would be able to to create a small closed-off space known as an Illusory Dawn Sand Domain using these grains of sand, and that could come in any form, such as an Illusory Dawn Sand Box, an Illusory Dawn Sand Vial, etc.

Inside the space within these vessels, the rate at which time flowed could be altered.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li.

If I had a sufficient amount of Illusory Dawn Sand, would I be able to...

However, a self-deprecating look then appeared on his face.

Setting aside whether that's even possible, how am I supposed to obtain so much Illusory Dawn Sand? Items that contain time law powers aren't so easy to find.

With that in mind, he turned his gaze back to the three cultivation arts as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

All three of them were time-attribute cultivation arts, but they focused on different things, and aside from the Mantra Axis Scripture, which could be used as a cultivation art, the other two were more related to treasures that contained time law powers.

After closely examining all three cultivation arts, Han Li became even more convinced that some type of connection existed between them.

Of course, there were bound to be some similarities, considering all three were time-attribute cultivation arts, but Han Li felt like the connection wasn't as simple as that, but at the same time, he couldn't put his finger on exactly what the connection was.

......

Around half a month flew by in a flash.

Inside the inner room of the cave, Han Li was standing while holding the three cultivation arts in his hands with a wry smile on his face.

Even after extensive examination and pondering, he was still no closer to a definitive answer.

"I should take a break. If I keep forcing myself deeper into this hole, I'm going to end up hampering my future cultivation," he sighed to himself, then stowed the three cultivation arts away.

The laws of time was one of the three paramount laws, so its cultivation arts were bound to be different from the average cultivation art, and Han Li decided that he wasn't going to pursue the other two cultivation arts before he figured out exactly what type of connection existed between the three.

Of course, another important factor behind this decision was that he didn't have the time to go into seclusion for an extended period.

With that in mind, he sat back down with his legs crossed, then flipped a hand over to produce a white jade vial, and he tipped out a pill that was as translucent as jade from within before swallowing it.

The pill was called a Snow Soul Pill, and it was one of the Golden Immortal Stage pills that he had obtained from Xiao Jinhan, so it was perfect for him to consume.

After swallowing the pill, Han Li closed his eyes to meditate, and once his heart had settled into a calm and tranquil state, he pressed a white jade slip to his own glabella.

This jade slip contained the fifth level of the Mantra Axis Scripture.

Layers of golden ripples spread in all directions from the jade slip, basking Han Li in a soft, golden glow.

In contrast with how difficult the fourth level of the cultivation art had been to understand, the fifth level felt more straightforward to Han Li, and after memorizing its contents, he stowed it away again.

After that, he placed one hand over the other in front of himself to make a hand seal, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared before him.

The array in the room concealed the energy fluctuations of the Mantra Treasured Axis, but Jin Tong and Xiao Bai were still able to detect something through their spiritual connection with Han Li, and both of them turned to face the inner room.

The Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis lit up as a string of radiant miniature suns, and over three months quickly passed by in seclusion.

During this time, the Dark Star Canyon had become quite lively. Aside from the other large tribes that ranked alongside the Calm Dawn Tribe, close to half of the smaller Beast Race tribes had also traveled to the Dark Star Canyon.

As a result, things became very busy for the Calm Dawn Tribe. Nuo Yifan paid Han Li two visits in the first month, but on both occasions, she was told that Han Li was in seclusion, and she hadn't returned since. It seemed that everyone had forgotten that there was still a human residing in the canyon.

On this day, both Jin Tong and Xiao Bai were staring at the light barrier that separated the room that Han Li was in from the outside world, and their eyes were wide with intrigue.

About an hour ago, Han Li had eaten a small round fruit that was riddled with tiny golden spots, and his Mantra Treasured Axis had immediately become brighter as a result.

At the same time, a tiny golden vortex had appeared on the outside of his thigh, and a vast expanse of golden light had begun surging toward the vortex. This was none other than his 61st immortal acupoint!

With the formation of this immortal acupoint, two more Time Dao Runes had appeared on the Mantra Treasured Axis.

A short while later, the surrounding energy fluctuations gradually subsided, and Han Li slowly opened his eyes, but he was looking more concerned than elated.

Even after consuming a fruit that's imbued with time law powers, I was only just barely able to open a single immortal acupoint. How much resources will it take to reach the High Zenith Stage?

With that in mind, a wry smile appeared on his face, but before he had a chance to dwell on this thought, the Heaven Controlling Vial suddenly flew up on its own.

Han Li hurriedly cast his gaze toward his Mantra Treasured Axis, upon which he was ecstatic to discover that an 11th time law thread had appeared around it.

The golden fruit that he had obtained from Gongshu Jiu had allowed him to manifest another time law thread, and that was certainly a pleasant surprise.

Furthermore, judging from the reaction of the Heaven Controlling Vial, it seemed that he was about to be sucked into another vision.

Sure enough, a burst of rumbling rang out, and the Heaven Controlling Vial, which had already swelled to the size of a millstone, released a thick pillar of green light that struck the light barrier around the inner room to form a translucent wall of light.

Jin Tong and Xiao Bai were unable to tell what was happening inside due to the light barrier that was in their way, so they could only return to the stone table in a bored manner.

A green vortex slowly took shape within the wall of light, immediately following which a burst of tremendous suction force erupted forth, sucking his soul out of his body and into the wall of light in a flash.

[1]. For more information on Asura Spiders, please refer to RMJI Chapter 2287: Battle Against the Asura Spiders (1).

[Back]

Chapter 549: Vision of the True Mantra Sect

Han Li's consciousness slowly returned to him, and he opened his eyes to inspect his surroundings.

He was already mentally prepared this time, so he wasn't feeling panicked at all. Instead, there was only a sense of excitement and curiosity in his heart.

These experiences were extremely precious, and they had always benefited him greatly while only temporarily costing him the use of his Time Dao Runes.

As he looked around, he was greeted by the sight of several white plazas, which were surrounded by a series of white jade palaces that stretched as far as the eyes could see.

There were some mountains hovering in mid-air, and they were also riddled with palaces.

It seemed that he was situated in a large sect.

However, at this moment, there was smoke rising up all over the sect, and many of the palaces and hovering mountains in the sky had been damaged, indicating that a battle was taking place.

Sure enough, there were countless cultivators locked in battle up above, and they were split into two sides, with one side dressed entirely in white robes, while the other side was dressed in golden robes.

The golden robes weren't unfamiliar to Han Li as it was the attire of the Heavenly Court.

The two sides were quite evenly matched, and it didn't appear as if a decisive outcome were going to arise anytime soon.

After taking in his surroundings, Han Li cast his gaze forward to find that a faint projection of his Mantra Treasured Axis was hovering in front of him.

The Time Dao Runes on its surface were radiating semi-transparent light, and a couple of them had already faded.

The rate at which the Time Dao Runes was fading was the same as before.

He then turned his attention to the body that he had possessed, and he discovered that it was a white-robed cultivator laying in a corner of the plaza.

The man was tall and thin with a head of straw-like yellow hair, and his skin was as wrinkled and wizened as the bark of an old tree. It appeared that this was the body of a foreign being.

There was a large hole in the man's lower abdomen, and his body had almost been sliced into two. On top of that, he was laying in a puddle of his own green blood, and he seemed to met his demise quite some time ago.

Hold on a second, this man looks so familiar... Where have I seen him before?

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face as he tried to recall where he had seen this man in the past, but was unable to do so.

He quickly shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought, then attempted to inspect the man's memories.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out in the sky, and the clouds up above began to rapidly revolve, forming a giant vortex in the blink of an eye.

The vortex was releasing an earth-shattering rumbling sound, and beams of golden light were shooting out from within it.

The golden light was as blinding as the sun, and Han Li was astonished to detect the tremendous law powers imbued within these beams of golden light.

This was a type of law powers that was very familiar to him; it was the power of time laws!

The time law powers within these beams of golden light was downright unfathomable, and they struck the beholder with a sense of awe and veneration.

In contrast, Han Li's time law powers was nothing more than trash!

Who could've possibly cultivated the power of time laws to such an extent?

Han Li was so astonished by what he was seeing that he forgot to draw upon the memories of his host body.

All of a sudden, the beams of golden light that had erupted out of the vortex transformed into balls of fire that resembled lotus flowers before raining down from above.

One of the golden fireballs descended toward a Golden Immortal Stage white-robed cultivator, who hurriedly conjured up several layers of protective barriers while shooting back in retreat.

However, the protective barriers weren't able to pose any resistance against the golden flames, which passed through them with ease before landing upon the white-robed cultivator's shoulder.

The white-robed cultivator didn't even get a chance to cry out before his body rapidly aged within the golden flames before disintegrating into ashes.

Han Li drew a sharp breath upon seeing this.

Meanwhile, the other golden fireballs also descended toward other white-robed cultivators, avoiding the Heavenly Court cultivators with unerring accuracy, and in the blink of an eye, close to half of the white-robed cultivators had been reduced to ashes.

Right at this moment, a radiant golden cloud rose up from the largest mountain that was hovering in mid-air, and it gave off rays of dazzling golden light.

Han Li was shocked to discover that the golden cloud was also giving off bursts of time law powers.

The time law powers radiating from the golden cloud wasn't as formidable as that of the vortex in the sky, but it was still countless times more formidable than Han Li's time law powers.

The cloud rapidly expanded to obscure the entire sky in the blink of an eye, keeping all of the golden fireballs at bay, but during the process, the golden cloud was also whittled down significantly.

All of a sudden, a rotund red-robed monk appeared above the golden cloud.

The monk was extremely tall and portly, resembling a mountain of flesh, and the rolls of flab on his face had reduced his eyes to narrow slits.

Han Li's eyes immediately widened in shock at the sight of the red-robed monk.

This was the very same lecturing monk that he had once seen through the Heaven Controlling Vial!

Upon catching sight of the red-robed monk, Han Li was also immediately able to recall that the host body that he had possessed belonged to one of the five people who had been listening to the red-robed monk's lecture.

The red-robed monk was largely expressionless as he made a hand seal and declared, "Let there be wind!"

A string of azure runes flew out of his mouth, then transformed into an incredibly thick azure tornado, within which countless azure blades of wind were swirling incessantly. The tornado left a series of inky-black spatial rifts in its wake, while also sending waves of spatial fluctuations sweeping in all directions as it swept toward the vortex in the sky with devastating power.

This is his Mantra Domain!

Han Li was immediately able to identify the ability that had been unleashed by the red-robed monk.

It was thanks to overhearing part of the monk's lecture that Han Li had been able to master this ability.

However, the Mantra Domain that he unleashed was nothing more than an illusion, yet this azur tornado was very much real.

By Han Li's own estimates, if he were to be swept up in that tornado, then he would most likely be instantly reduced to a pile of mincemeat.

Gusts of howling wind were also sweeping through the white palace down below, and some of the weaker cultivators on the battlefield were instantly sent flying away.

The body that Han Li had possessed was also swept away by the fierce gusts of wind, and this was exactly what he wanted.

He hurriedly drew upon the remaining immortal spiritual power in the body, and a layer of yellow light appeared over his body as he vanished into the ground in a flash before fleeing into the distance as quickly as he could.

To Han Li's surprise, not much of the body's immortal spiritual power remained, but it was extremely pure, even more so than his own immortal spiritual power.

Right at this moment, a burst of golden light flashed within the vortex in the sky once again, and an enormous golden hand appeared.

The hand was over 100 acres in size, and at its center was a huge golden halo, which descended from above as the hand came pressing downward while giving off a burst of tremendous time law powers.

The azure tornado instantly fell completely still, as did the gusts of the ferocious wind that were sweeping through the air down below, as well as all of the other combatants on the battlefield.

The red-robed monk above the golden cloud had raised his hands as if he were preparing to unleash some other ability, but he had also been immobilized.

Han Li's escape also drew to an abrupt halt, and he had fallen still as well, suspended within the soil underground.

Everything in the world had fallen still, and the only thing that could still move was the giant golden hand that was descending from above.

As soon as the azure tornado came into contact with the giant hand, the former instantly disintegrated into countless specks of azure light.

Meanwhile, the enormous golden hand continued to descend without pause, then landed upon the red-robed monk in a seemingly gentle manner.

Right before Han Li's astonished eyes, the red-robed monk's body also disintegrated just like the azure tornado.

After slaying the red-robed monk, the giant golden hand didn't continue to descend. Instead, it shrank back into the vortex up above in a flash, and in the next instant, everything returned to normal.

The cultivators on both sides were a little dumbfounded, unsure of what had just happened, but they then spotted the remains of the red-robed monk falling from the sky.

The white-robed cultivators' expressions instantly turned to grief and despair, while the Heavenly Court cultivators were ecstatic.

At this point, the Heavenly Court cultivators far outnumbered the white-robed cultivators, and morale had also completely plummeted for the latter, so the battle quickly became very one-sided.

Deep underground, Han Li was also able to move again in the wake of the disappearance of the giant golden hand.

What just happened?

Just now, his consciousness seemed to have faded, but it was only for a moment, and he couldn't tell if it had merely been a figment of his imagination.

However, he then quickly realized that it hadn't been his mind playing tricks on him as two of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis had suddenly faded.

He immediately released his spiritual sense to inspect what was happening on the surface, upon which he noticed that in the place of the red-robed monk now stood a pile of disintegrated flesh.

Despite this, Han Li was still able to identify the aura of the pile of remains, and his expression instantly changed drastically upon seeing this.

The red-robed monk had just displayed power that was far superior to any cultivator he had ever seen, yet he had been killed in an instant.

At this point, the vortex in the sky was also slowly fading, and before long, it had vanished entirely.

Han Li was momentarily rooted to the spot, then snapped back to his senses before channeling the immortal spiritual power of his host body once again. However, instead of fleeing further into the distance, he burrowed even deeper into the ground, and only after he was extremely deep underground did he draw to a halt.

There, he was finally able to heave an internal sigh of relief before drawing upon his host body's memories.

A string of memory fragments instantly surged into his mind, and after sorting through these memories, Han Li discovered that the sect outside was none other than the True Mantra Sect.

Chapter 550: Past Secrets

According to the host body's memories, this immortal region was called the Black Soil Immortal Region, and it was countless times larger than the Northern Glacial Immortal Region. As for the True Mantra Sect, it was the undisputed number one sect of the immortal region, and it had been in existence for countless years with innumerable disciples within its boundaries.

As for the body that Han Li possessed, it belonged to a man called Mu Yan, who was one of the True Mantra Sect's five grand elders.

The red-robed monk was Sect Master Miro of the True Mantra Sect and also Mu Yan's master. He was a Great Encompassment cultivator who stood at the pinnacle of the Black Soil Immortal Region and was reverently referred to as Immortal Lord Miro.

Aside from Mu Yan, Immortal Lord Miro had four other direct disciples, and they were the four other grand elders of the True Mantra Sect, as well as the four other people listening to Immortal Lord Miro's lecture from Han Li's vision.

As direct disciples of Immortal Lord Miro, all five of them were High Zenith cultivators.

Despite Immortal Lord Miro's unfathomable powers, he had been killed in an instant, so it was clear that the owner of the giant hand was an extraordinary figure. However, the only thing that Mu Yan seemed to be aware of was that this was a significant figure in the Heavenly Court.

As far as Han Li was aware, only a select group of people could kill a Great Encompassment cultivator with such ease.

Could it be the Time Dao Ancestor?

It was clear that the True Mantra Sect had been attacked by the Heavenly Court, it seemed that the sect had ultimately fallen to its demise after Immortal Lord Miro was slain by the Time Dao Ancestor.

Han Li couldn't help but wonder why the Heavenly Court had been so determined to stamp out the True Mantra Sect, to the point that even the Time Dao Ancestor had been personally involved in the sect's eradication.

As one of the three paramount laws, the laws of time were fundamentally superior to all other laws with the exception of its two counterparts. If it really was the Time Dao Ancestor who had slain Immortal Lord Miro, then he was most likely one of a handful of the most powerful beings in the entire True Immortal Realm.

Han Li took a deep breath to compose himself, then continued to browse through Mu Yan's memories, trying to find out more information about the Heavenly Court.

After killing Gongshu Jiu in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, Han Li had well and truly become an enemy of the Heavenly Court. Even though he currently didn't possess the power to oppose the Heavenly Court, it certainly couldn't hurt to know more about the enemy.

Before long, Han Li's heart was pounding with excitement.

As a High Zenith cultivator, Mu Yan possessed a vast wealth of knowledge and experience, and his memories contained a great deal of information pertaining to the Heavenly Court.

In the past, Han Li had attempted to gather information on the Heavenly Court, and he was able to uncover some things, but most of the information was publicly available anyway, so it wasn't very useful.

Right as Han Li was about to take a closer look at Mu Yan's memories, he was suddenly struck by a rush of dizziness.

Alarmed by this sudden onset of dizziness, Han Li hurriedly stopped what he was doing, and only then did the dizziness subside.

Could it be because the person I've possessed on this occasion is far superior to me when it comes to cultivation base?

Even though he had possessed Mu Yan's deceased body, its memories didn't belong to him, and forcibly scouring through those memories was very similar to performing a soul search technique.

Mu Yan had been a High Zenith cultivator at his time of death, thereby possessing a far superior cultivation base to Han Li, and even though Han Li's spiritual sense was far superior to that of other mid-Golden Immortal cultivators, it was still too much of a stretch for a Golden Immortal to search a High Zenith cultivators soul.

In fact, if it weren't for the fact that Mu Yan was already dead, then Han Li wouldn't have been able to get away with only such minor consequences.

With that in mind, Han Li could only give up on trying to glean more of Mu Yan's memories, and he began inspecting his surroundings while waiting for his soul to recover.

At this moment, he was deep underground, and it wasn't very comfortable having so much soil clinging so tightly to his body.

He swept a hand through the soil, and a burst of yellow light instantly spread outward, forming a space that was around 50 to 60 feet in size, forcing out all of the surrounding soil.

After that, he sat down with his legs crossed and began to rest and recuperate.

The Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis faded one after another, and only after over 30 of them had been snuffed out did his soul gradually return to its original condition.

After that, he continued to search through Mu Yan's memories, attempting to connect the fragmented memories, and he was quickly able to uncover more information about the Heavenly Court.

As the most powerful official organization of the entire True Immortal Realm, the Heavenly Court exerted its control upon all of the immortal regions through Immortal Palaces, while the Heavenly Court itself was situated in a place known as the Middle Earth Immortal Region.

There was indeed a Time Dao Ancestor in the Heavenly Court, and he was the most prestigious and long-standing Dao Ancestor.

Once again, Han Li's soul began to waver, and he was forced to stop for a second time.

Who exactly is this Time Dao Ancestor? Han Li thought to himself as he took some time to recuperate.

Time slowly passed by, and several dozen more of the Mantra Treasured Axis's Time Dao Runes faded before Han Li was fully recovered once again, and he began to search through Mu Yan's memories for a third time.

This time, a grim look gradually appeared on his face, and his expression only darkened further and further.

He had finally found some information pertaining to this battle.

Theoretically speaking, with a Great Encompassment cultivator like Immortal Lord Miro at the helm, the True Mantra Sect should've been able to thrive for the foreseeable future. After all, no one aside from Dao Ancestors could reliably defeat Great Encompassment cultivators.

However, unfortunately, Immortal Lord Miro was also the root cause behind the True Mantra Sect's demise.

As it turned out, the Time Dao Ancestor had begun to regard Immortal Lord Miro as a threat, and the former had decided to strike before things could get out of hand.

As for why Immortal Lord Miro was viewed as a threat, that concerned a secret that very few were aware of.

All of the 3,000 Great Dao laws were derived from the Great Dao of heaven and earth. Just as two tigers couldn't reside on the same mountain, each law could only have a single Dao Ancestor, and if a Great Encompassment Stage Immortal Lord's mastery over a certain type of laws exceeded that of the corresponding Dao Ancestor, then the Dao Ancestor would be replaced.

As for exactly what happened during this process, that was naturally something that wasn't known to a High Zenith cultivator like Mu Yan.

However, it seemed that all Dao Ancestors paid a great deal of attention to cultivators who had mastered the same type of law powers as themselves, particularly when it came to cultivators at or above the High Zenith Stage. Unless those cultivators were willing to pledge their subordination to the Dao Ancestor, they would be eliminated before they could develop their powers any further.

Even so, some Dao Ancestors had still been replaced in the past, and it could be said that all Dao Ancestors had risen to the top by treading upon the bodies of other prospective Dao Ancestors as stepping stones.

Having already cultivated the laws of time to the Great Encompassment Stage, Immortal Lord Miro posed a significant threat to the Time Dao Ancestor, and even though he had done everything in his power to conceal his cultivation base, he was still eventually exposed, thereby leading to the demise of the True Mantra Sect.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

At the moment, he was still quite far away from the High Zenith Stage, but wouldn't he eventually also have to worry about being targeted by the Time Dao Ancestor?

Cultivators really do constantly have the odds stacked against them...

For all cultivators who had mastered a type of law powers, the corresponding Dao Ancestor was essentially the heavens, and only by overcoming the heavens could one truly reach the pinnacle.

However, there was no way that he could currently contend against the Heavenly Court, so Han Li only considered this subject briefly before casting aside this train of thought to continue searching through Mu Yan's memories.

At this point, only a small portion of Mu Yan's fragmented memories were still yet to be inspected, and all of a sudden, an elated look appeared on his face.

As it turned out, these remaining memories contained aspects of Mu Yan's cultivation. Just like his master, he had also been cultivating the laws of time, and even though these memories didn't contain the cultivation arts used by Mu Yan, they did contain much of his cultivation experiences and insights.

Han Li had never had anyone that he could turn to for mentorship in his progression in mastering the laws of time, so this was exactly what he needed, and he immediately began poring over these memories.

A short while later, an intrigued look appeared on his face.

He discovered that these cultivation experiences were all very much related to the Mantra Axis Scripture, the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture, and the Water Divination Time Arts.

Han Li had always felt like these three cultivation arts were somehow connected, but he had never been able to find the connection.

However, through these memories, he seemed to have found some ways to integrate the three cultivation arts into one.

Could it be that some type of connection really does exist between the three cultivation arts?

After quickly browsing through Mu Yan's remaining memories, Han Li raised his head to look up at the projection of the Mantra Treasured Axis.

At this point, most of the Time Dao Runes on its surface had already faded, and there were only several dozen that were still lit, indicating that he didn't have much time left.

With that in mind, Han Li began to search Mu Yan's body for his storage tools.

Presumably, Mu Yan's storage tools had to contain the cultivation arts that he had been using, and if he could find them, then he should be able to uncover the connection between the three aforementioned cultivation arts.

However, he quickly discovered that Mu Yan's storage tools were nowhere to be found.

They must've been taken by whoever killed him...

With that in mind, a disappointed look appeared on Han Li's face.

All of a sudden, a burst of intense resentment rose up from within the remnants of Mu Yan's soul at the thought of his killer, and it seemed that there had been some treachery involved.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he sensed this burst of fury, and only after some words of consolation from him did the disembodied burst of anger begin to subside.

Chapter 551: Familiar Aura

Could it be that he perished to a sneak attack?

The reason that Han Li was speculating this was due to the wound on Mu Yan's lower abdomen.

He wasn't able to find out how Mu Yan was killed through his memories, but he could sense a great deal of resentment in the remnants of Mu Yan's soul.

All of a sudden, Han Li noticed something on a corner of Mu Yan's sleeve, and he reached out to tear the sleeve apart, revealing a small white silken handkerchief that was riddled with tiny text.

The material of the handkerchief was identical to that of his clothes, and it had been concealed very well. If it weren't for the fact that Mu Yan's sleeve was currently stained with blood, Han Li would've failed to notice the handkerchief.

After examining the handkerchief for a moment, an elated look immediately appeared on Han Li's face.

The passage of the text on the handkerchief contained none other than the Mantra Domain secret technique, and this was most likely the full version, one that was much more comprehensive and even more profound than the incomplete version that Han Li had derived from Immortal Lord Miro's lecture.

He began to pore over the passage of text, and the more he saw, the more stunned he became.

The Mantra Domain was one of the most advanced secret techniques of the True Mantra Sect, and it was said that upon achieving full mastery of the secret technique, one could speak things into existence and influence heaven and earth with their words.

Of course, at the very least, one had to be at the High Zenith Stage to even have a chance of achieving such miraculous feats, and at Han Li's current cultivation base, he could only use the Mantra Domain to unleash some illusions.

Even so, it had proven to be very useful in several past battles, and if he could use it wisely in conjunction with his time spirit domain, he was confident that it would serve him very well in future battles.

Han Li quickly read through the entire passage of text on the silken handkerchief, committing it firmly to his memory, and not a moment too soon as the final Time Dao Rune on the Mantra Treasured Axis faded almost immediately thereafter.

After a rush of dizziness, Han Li's spiritual sense quickly returned to his body.

The translucent wall of light in front of him was gradually dissipating, while he looked on with a dazed expression.

The vision had shown him what had happened in the final moments of the True Mantra Sect, while also displaying to him the power of the Time Dao Ancestor.

Even though all of these things had happened in the distant past, Han Li was still reeling from what he had seen.

Through cultivating the Spirit Refinement Technique, he had already pitted himself against the Heavenly Court, and now, his cultivation of the laws of time was eventually going to set him on a collision course with the Time Dao Ancestor.

Even a Great Encompassment Stage mighty figure like Immortal Lord Miro had stood no chance against the Time Dao Ancestor, how was a mere Golden Immortal like himself going to fare?

The Time Dao Ancestor most likely wouldn't even have to lift a finger to kill him.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face at this sobering thought, but there was no point in thinking excessively about such matters. Inevitably, such a day would come, but for now, he had to focus on becoming more powerful and making it out of the primordial land alive.

With that in mind, he flipped a hand over to produce a blank jade slip, then pressed it against his own forehead and recorded the Mantra Domain secret technique that he had just memorized into it.

Three more months passed by in the blink of an eye.

During this time, Nuo Qinglin had visited Han Li to apologize on several occasions, claiming that some major crises had swept through the entire Beast Race, and that there were many important tribes that were still yet to arrive, so the delivery of the maps that he had been promised was going to be delayed.

Han Li had spent this entire time reflecting on Mu Yan's cultivation insights, and even though he still wasn't able to identify the connection between the Mantra Axis Scripture, the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture, and the Water Divination Time Arts, he had developed a better grasp on the laws of time. Hence, this peaceful cultivation environment was perfect for him, and he decided to stay.

Inside his secret chamber, Han Li sat with his legs crossed and his eyes closed while channeling the Water Divination Time Arts.

As he began to chant an incantation, waves of rippling golden light rose up over his body, then converged in front of him to form a ball of golden light.

Another week flew by in a flash.

Han Li remained seated with his legs crossed while making a string of hand seals, and the ball of golden light in front of him had already become as radiant as a miniature sun.

All of a sudden, a golden vial emerged at the center of the ball of light.

The vial had a wide bottom that gradually tapered upward, and it had a pair of crescent-shaped handles at its opening. The vial was very blurry, but it was still giving off a profound aura, and as soon as it appeared, all of the nearby golden light instantly surged into it.

All of a sudden, the ball of golden light vanished, leaving only the blurry vial projection hovering completely still in mid-air.

Han Li opened his eyes, and as his gaze fell upon the vial projection, a hint of elation and surprise appeared on his face.

Initially, he had only been planning to cultivate the Water Divination Time Arts a little so that he could get an initial grasp on it, but to his surprise, he had managed to manifest a Clear Time Vial with ease.

According to the Water Divination Time Arts, this was supposed to have been extremely difficult, and that only someone who possessed exceptional aptitude and a certain degree of mastery over the laws of time could have any chance of manifesting a Clear Time Vial after an extensive period of cultivation.

Evidently, this was not the case for Han Li.

Was this because he had already established a foundation through his cultivation of the Mantra Axis Scripture, or was there some other factor at play?

Han Li pondered this question briefly before setting the train of thought aside to continue his cultivation.

He began to chant an incantation while making a string of hand seals, and two thick beams of golden light shot out of the palms of his hands.

There were countless golden runes flashing within the beams of light, and all of them fused into the vial projection, causing it to slowly revolve on the spot while attaining a more and more substantial form.

Some time later, the vial projection had already turned into a semi-transparent vial that appeared as if it were a physical object.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this. With that, he had completed the cultivation art's second chapter as well.

After taking a deep breath, he moved on to the third chapter.

A month later, Han Li conjured up the Clear Time Vial once again, and this time, it was a little smaller than before, and countless white star designs had appeared on its surface.

Up to this point, Han Li had mastered the cultivation art's third chapter as well.

He took a glance at the Clear Time Vial, then closed his eyes once again while making a string of hand seals, and countless specks of radiant golden light began to emerge within his body, every single one of which was giving off astonishing time law power fluctuations.

These specks of golden light surged steadily into the golden vial at Han Li's behest, and a series of tiny specks of golden light instantly began to appear within the vial.

Close to a year flew by in a flash, and at this point, the Clear Time Vial was already filled with specks of golden light, resembling a translucent bottle that was filled with golden fireflies.

Han Li sat completely still on the spot with his legs crossed, and his entire body was basked in a radiant river of golden light, with countless specks of golden light continuing to surge out from within before entering the Clear Time Vial.

The vial seemed to have reached its maximal capacity, and all of the specks of golden light instantly began to converge to form a ball.

That ball of golden light then vanished into the vial in a flash, manifesting itself as a Time Dao Rune.

At this point, there were already five other Time Dao Runes on the vial.

With the addition of this latest Time Dao Rune, the Clear Time Vial began to buzz audibly, and Han Li suddenly stopped what he was doing, upon which all of the flowing golden light around him quickly vanished.

Immediately thereafter, he rubbed his hands together, and the Clear Time Vial vanished as well.

The fourth chapter had been far more difficult to cultivate than the third one, requiring one to manifest six Time Dao Runes, but once again, it had barely posed any obstacle to Han Li at all.

He rose to his feet and exhaled as he swept a hand through the air to withdraw the restrictions around his cave abode, then made his way over to one of the windows in the outer room.

It was late at night at the moment, and there were countless bright stars in the clear sky.

Han Li took a glance up above, then made a hand seal, and his Clear Time Vial appeared on the window sill in front of him amid a flash of golden light.

The six Time Dao Runes on the vial instantly began to flash, and tiny specks of white light emerged within the moonlight that was spilling in through the window before being drawn into the opening of the vial.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this.

However, the rate of absorption of moonlight was very slow, and at this rate, it was going to take a considerably long time to manifest a time water droplet.

Right at this moment, the sound of footsteps rang out from outside, and Jin Tong entered the cave abode while riding on Xiao Bai's back.

Her brows were tightly furrowed, indicating that she was troubled by something, and Xiao Bai could sense that she was in a bad mood, so it was making sure to walk very carefully to avoid jostling her.

"What's wrong, Jin Tong?" Han Li asked as he stowed his Clear Time Vial away.

Jin Tong opened her mouth to say something, but seemed to be rather hesitant.

"It's alright, if you have something on your mind, then tell me. I'll look out for you," Han Li assured with a smile.

"I've been feeling a very familiar aura... Well, it's not actually that familiar, it's just very similar to mine, like another me, and this aura is currently getting closer," Jin Tong revealed.

"An aura very similar to yours? Could it be..."

Chapter 552: Uniting Against a Common Enemy

"Could it be another you?" Xiao Bai exclaimed before Han Li had a chance to reply.

"What did you just say? I think you need to have some sense beaten into you, Xiao Bai!" Jin Tong snapped as she began rolling up her sleeves.

"No, what I meant to say is, could it be another Gold Devouring Immortal?" Xiao Bai hurriedly amended with a fawning smile.

"Why would another Gold Devouring Immortal be coming here? Can you sense how powerful it is?" Han Li asked.

"It seems... to be a little more powerful than I am," Jin Tong replied in a concerned voice.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but internally, he was quite stunned to hear this.

At the moment, Jin Tong was already at the late-Golden Immortal Stage, so did that mean that a High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal was currently approaching them?

Xiao Bai was also very alarmed to hear this, and it urged in a trembling voice, "We have to run, Master!"

As soon as its voice trailed off, the sound of thunderous drumming rang out from outside, and the peaceful valley immediately erupted into action as countless figures rose up into the sky as streaks of light.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

"Stay in the cave abode for now, I'll go out and take a look," he instructed, then made his way out of the cave abode.

At this moment, more and more beings for the Beast Race were flying out of the Dark Star Canyon, and they were all flying outside.

All of a sudden, a streak of light arrived from afar, then landed in front of Han Li's cave abode to reveal Nuo Qinglin.

"How has your stay been so far, Fellow Daoist Li?" Nuo Qinglin asked with a smile.

"It's been fine. Thank you for the hospitality, Chief Nuo. May I ask what's happening right now?" Han Li asked.

"We're being attacked by the Insect Race, but we already anticipated this and have set up defensive measures, so there's nothing to fear," Nuo Qinglin replied in a confident manner.

"That's good to hear. May I ask why you've come to visit me then?" Han Li asked.

"We're going to be using the restrictions within the Dark Star Canyon later to unleash a secret technique, and no one can remain in the canyon during this time, so I'll have to ask you to leave the canyon with me," Nuo Qinglin explained.

"That's not a problem. I'll go pack up my belongings, then come back out to join you," Han Li replied with a nod, then returned to his cave abode, while Nuo Qinglin continued to wait patiently outside.

After entering his cave abode, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he made his way into his secret chamber.

"The Insect Race is attacking, and there's a High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal among them! We need to leave right away, Master!" Xiao Bai immediately yelled in an urgent voice.

"What do you think, Jin Tong?" Han Li asked.

"I'm sure you already know what happens when two Gold Devouring Immortals encounter one another," Jin Tong said, and a hint of resolve and killing intent appeared in her eyes.

Han Li didn't say anything upon seeing this.

"While traveling through some other immortal regions with Gongshu Jiu, we ran into some Gold Devouring Immortals, and at the same cultivation base, they're far more powerful than primordial true spirits! There's no way we can overcome a High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal, so we have to run!" Xiao Bai urged.

"There's no running away from them. Gold Devouring Immortals are extremely sensitive to one another, so even if we run, it'll definitely still come after us," Jin Tong replied with a shake of her head.

Xiao Bai opened its mouth to say something else, but ultimately decided against it.

"Just as Jin Tong said, even if we leave this place, that Gold Devouring Immortal will definitely continue to pursue us, so we may as well stay here and wait for it," Han Li said.

A bitter look appeared on Xiao Bai's face upon hearing this, and it reluctantly nodded in agreement.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light that sucked both of them into a spirit beast pouch, then instructed, "Stay in the spirit beast pouch for now."

After that, Han Li withdrew the restrictions in the cave abode before emerging outside again.

"Sorry to keep you waiting, Chief Nuo," he said.

"Not at all, Fellow Daoist Li. Please come with me," Nuo Qinglin replied, then flew up into the sky as a streak of light, while Han Li trailed along behind him.

As they flew through the air, he suddenly turned to a certain direction in the canyon, where there was a ball of churning black qi in the distance.

The ball of black qi was situated very far away, but with Han Li's exceptional eyesight, he was able to see that there were dozens of giant stone pillars standing around it to form what appeared to be an array, which was giving off bursts of spatial power fluctuations, much like a teleportation array would.

Han Li was rather surprised to see this, but he didn't ask any questions, and Nuo Qinglin also displayed no intention of explaining anything to him.

Inside Han Li's spirit beast pouch, Jin Tong suddenly said, "Xiao Bai, you once said that you have a space within your body that's completely isolated from the outside world, right?"

"That's right, what an exceptional memory you have!" Xiao Bai confirmed in a fawning manner.

"Alright, I want you to eat me," Jin Tong said.

Xiao Bai was naturally astonished to hear this, and it immediately began shaking its head vigorously.

"You want to use the space in my body to conceal your aura? You can't do that! Living beings can't survive in my internal space, and any living being that enters will quickly be digested!"

"That may be the case for other living beings, but you won't be able to digest me! Hurry up! I'm sure I'll be fine as long as I don't stay in there for too long," Jin Tong urged.

Xiao Bai could only reluctantly oblige upon hearing this, opening its mouth to release a burst of suction force that sucked Jin Tong into its belly.

......

Meanwhile, Han Li and Nuo Qinglin quickly arrived outside the Dark Star Canyon.

All of the Beast Race tribes were already prepared for this battle, so they had reacted very quickly, and all of them had emerged in full force, culminating in an army of tens of thousands.

Han Li swept his gaze over his surroundings to find that there were around 30 to 40 tribes present, and the Longneck beings were also here, but they were situated near the back.

There were also close to 1,000 giant black war chariots that were laden with Beast Race beings hovering in the sky.

These black chariots were giving off a metallic sheen, and there were also numerous glowing black patterns engraved onto their surfaces, giving them an indestructible appearance.

Ahead of all of the Beast Race beings was an even larger army of millions of demon beasts.

Somehow, the Beast Race beings had managed to arrange all of the demon beasts into several organized and uniform units that weren't chaotic in the slightest.

Han Li couldn't help but be a little surprised to see this.

"What do you think of our Beast Race army, Fellow Daoist Li?" Nuo Qinglin asked with a hint of pride in his voice.

"It certainly is a sight to behold," Han Li praised.

Nuo Qinglin burst into laughter upon hearing this, then flew up higher into the sky, while Han Li trailed along behind him.

Hovering in front of the war chariots was a black platform that was over 1,000 feet in size and shimmering with spiritual light, clearly indicating that it was a powerful treasure.

At this moment, there were around 30 to 40 Beast Race beings standing on the platform, and it seemed that they were important tribal leaders.

Nuo Qinglin descended onto the platform with Han Li, and their arrival was immediately met with a furious reaction.

"Chief Nuo Qinglin, why have you brought a human primordial hunter here?"

Han Li turned to discover that a dark-skinned man who was built like a massive black bear was the one who had spoken.

The man was at the pinnacle of the early-Golden Immortal Stage, possessing a slightly higher cultivation base than Nuo Qinglin.

Meanwhile, all of the other tribal leaders were also glowering at Han Li with animosity in their eyes.

There were over 10 Golden Immortals among them, but all of them were at the early-Golden Immortal Stage, while most of the remaining tribal leaders were at the late-True Immortal Stage.

"Don't be alarmed, everyone. This is Fellow Daoist Li Feiyu. He may be a human, but he's not a primordial hunter. Instead, he's only trying to pass through the primordial land enroute to another immortal region, and on top of that, he has assisted our Beast Race, specifically the Longneck Tribe in the past, so he's no enemy of ours," Nuo Qinglin hurriedly explained.

Nuo Yifan was also present, and she declared, "On the way back from the Longneck Tribe, we were attacked by the Insect Race, and it was only thanks to Senior Li's intervention that we were able to return safely to the Dark Star Canyon."

Taj was standing near the edge of the platform, but he made his voice loud and clear as he chimed in, "That's right. Fellow Daoist Li will forever be a friend of our Longneck Tribe."

Everyone else's expressions eased slightly upon hearing this, but they still regarded Han Li with clear distrust in their eyes.

"Don't mind them, Fellow Daoist Li. Human primordial hunters are sworn enemies of our Beast Race, so it's nothing personal against you," Nuo Qinglin said with an apologetic smile.

"I completely understand, Chief Nuo. There's no need to look out for me. My powers are very limited, but I can definitely look after myself," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"You're far too modest, Fellow Daoist Li. If things take a turn for the worse for our Beast Race in the upcoming battle, I'll be counting on you to lend us your assistance again," Nuo Qinglin said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

All of the other tribal leaders' expressions changed drastically upon hearing this, and the burly dark-skinned man who had spoken earlier exclaimed in a furious voice, "Nuo Qinglin, we are the regal Beast Race! How could you ask for assistance from a deceitful and honorless human?!"

"Brother Ulu, do not forget that the enemy of our Beast Race is the Insect Race. In order to defeat them, we must recruit all possible allies and unite everyone against a common enemy. I have already spoken to our king about this, and he also approves of my decision," Nuo Qinglin said.

The dark-skinned man's temper immediately died down upon hearing mention of their king, while the other tribal chiefs fell silent as well.

Chapter 553: Fierce Battle

"You're far too kind, Chief Nuo. I'm just a mere passerby in the primordial land, and I came to your territory by chance to request a map, I certainly wouldn't dare to get involved in a battle between your two races," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"My sincerest apologies about the map. This is the map that I've managed to compile thus far. Once the final few tribes arrive, I'll give you a complete one," Nuo Qinglin said as he summoned a white bone shard before handing it to Han Li, who accepted the bone shard, then inspected its contents momentarily with his spiritual sense before giving a nod.

The bone shard was similar to a jade slip, and it contained a detailed map of the primordial land. There were many missing areas, but it was certainly still much better than nothing.

"Also, I'd like to offer you a little something from our Beast Race in exchange for your services. Once we force back the Insect Race, we'll be sure to issue an additional reward," Nuo Qinglin continued as he pulled out a bone ring before handing it to Han Li as well.

Han Li accepted the ring, then injected his spiritual sense into it to find that it contained roughly 5,000 Immortal Origin Stones.

Han Li weighed the bone ring on the palm of his hand for a moment, then said, "Seeing as you're being so sincere, I can offer my services just this once. However, let me make this clear in advance: I won't take any undue risks. If the enemy is too strong, then I'll prioritize my own safety."

At this point, 5,000 Immortal Origin Stones was no longer a significant sum for him, but for the Calm Dawn Tribe, this was most likely quite a huge expenditure. Most importantly, Han Li had some other intentions and was only pretending to have been roped in by this reward to further his own agenda.

The other tribal leaders were furious to hear this.

"Why call upon him, Chief Nuo? He's clearly a coward!"

"Exactly! If you're so scared for your own safety, then don't come to the primordial land!"

"Everyone, we are currently facing a formidable enemy, so let's all look at the bigger picture here. Fellow Daoist Li, proceed as you please," Nuo Qinglin said with a smile, defusing the situation.

Han Li gave Nuo Qinglin a nod, then made his way off to the side.

Nuo Qinglin asked Nuo Yifan to keep Han Li company, then began to discuss strategy with the other tribal leaders.

Now that Han Li had a chance to take a closer look at the Beast Race army, he was rather taken aback by what he saw.

There were many tribes in the Beast Race, but three tribes clearly stood out in terms of population.

One of them was a tribe of extremely muscular, bear-like beings with thick black fur all over their bodies, looking much like Ulu from earlier.

The second tribe was the Calm Dawn Tribe, and at this moment, almost all of them were riding atop winged giant lizard beasts with large blue bows slung across their backs.

The final tribe of beings were extremely similar to humans in appearance, except their skin was green, and each of them had a single green horn on their head.

The warriors from these three tribes made up close to 70% of the entire Beast Race army.

Nuo Yifan could see the intrigue in Han Li's eyes, and she explained, "Those two tribes are the Violent Bear Tribe and the Monohorn Tribe, both of which are among the eight holy tribes of our Beast Race. Chief Ulu is the chief of the Violent Bear Tribe."

"What are the eight holy tribes?" Han Li asked.

"Our Beast Race has many tribes, and the eight most powerful ones among them are referred to as the eight holy tribes. Our Calm Dawn Tribe is also one of those eight tribes. It's a pity that only three have gathered here. Otherwise, there's no way the Insect Race would've dared to attack," Nuo Yifan said in a resentful voice.

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

All of a sudden, he raised his head and cast his gaze into the distance.

A burst of thunderous rumbling rang out from that direction, and black line appeared on the distant horizon before quickly expanding in Han Li's field of view.

A vast spirit insect army had appeared where heaven and earth met, and it was even more enormous than the army of demon beasts.

Behind the spirit insect army was a massive gray cloud with tens of thousands of Insect Race beings standing atop it, and they also seemed to outnumber the Beast Race beings.

Han Li swept his gaze across the Insect Race army, and his expression remained unchanged, but he was stunned to discover that the Insect Race had close to 30 Golden Immortals, which, once again, far outnumbered that of the Beast Race.

It seemed that the Beast Race was at a disadvantage in all measures, and unless it had some special tricks up its sleeve, it was most likely going to lose this battle.

Grim looks appeared on the faces of all of the tribal leaders upon seeing this, but Nuo Qinglin then declared in a resolute voice, "Chief Ulu, Chief Marlon, Chef Sahan, let's proceed according to the original plan."

The three of them stepped forward as they were called upon, and Han Li cast his gaze toward them.

He already recognized Ulu, standing beside whom was an imposing green-skinned man with a single green horn on his forehead. He was clad in a suit of green armor, and his face and body were riddled with scars.

Nuo Yifan informed him that this man was Marlon, the chief of the Monohorn Tribe.

As for Sahan, he cut a very diminutive figure, and his entire body was concealed with a large dark red cloak, thereby hiding his features.

The three of them cupped their fists in a collective salute toward Nuo Qinglin, then descended from the platform down into the Beast Race army.

Chief Ulu swept a hand through the air, and a crimson giant rhinoceros beast appeared by his side. It was so enormous that it resembled a moving fortress, and it was giving off an extremely formidable aura.

Ulu jumped onto the rhinoceros beast's back, then summoned a giant crimson ax, and he was instantly brimming with battle intent.

The crimson rhinoceros ascended into the heavens, carrying Ulu into the sky above the Beast Race army.

"Brave warriors of the Beast Race, our sworn enemies are up ahead, while our tribesmen stand behind us! We must defend the honor of our Beast Race! It's time to fight!" Ulu roared in a thunderous voice, priming the Beast Race army for the battle to come.

"Fight! Fight! Fight!"

All of the Beast Race warriors echoed, and the earth trembled in the wake of their collective voices.

The Violent Bear, Calm Dawn, and Monohorn Tribes were charging at the forefront, while the army of demon beasts also rumbled forward with tremendous power.

As for the Insect Race army, it accelerated even further upon seeing this, but all of the Golden Immortals of the Insect Race had stopped in their tracks to face Han Li and the others from afar.

The two armies were like a pair of formidable waves that were crashing toward each other with devastating force, causing heaven and earth to tremble violently.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this.

The armies of the two races had filled his entire field of view, and the atmosphere of battle in the air was getting even him a little worked up.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom suddenly rang out from behind him, and a series of giant fireballs were launched up into the sky before hurtling toward the Insect Race army up ahead.

One giant fiery cloud after another erupted within the Insect Race army's ranks, forming a sea of crimson fire that swept up all of the nearby spirit insects before incinerating them into ashes.

Han Li turned around to find that these fireballs had come from those black war chariots, at the front of each of which was a thick cylindrical barrel that was glowing bright red.

The spirit patterns on the chariots lit up, and a thunderous boom rang out as a fireball that was over 100 feet in size shot out of each of the barrels before crashing down upon the Insect Race army.

"Those are our Beast Race's Fire God War Chariots. They're extremely powerful, but the materials required for them are quite difficult to come by, and they're also very difficult to construct. If we could construct 10,000 of these chariots, they would be enough to wipe out the Insect Race on their own," Nuo Yifan explained, and Han Li gave a slight nod in response.

Right at this moment, a series of black shadows that were roughly 1,000 feet in size rose up from the Insect Race army, then exploded into vast plumes of tiny black shadows before hurtling toward the Beast Race army at an astonishing speed.

These tiny shadows were countless strange insects that were as tiny and sleek as tiny daggers, and they seemed to be extremely sharp.

A chorus of agonized howls rang out from the Beast Race army as many Beast Race beings had holes punched into their bodies by these insects, resulting in countless casualties.

However, upon piercing through their targets, these insects would also explode and perish themselves.

"Those are Bone Needle Insects!" Nuo Yifan exclaimed with a resentful expression.

With Han Li's exceptional eyesight, he was able to see over 100 mountainous black shadows at the back of the Insect Race army. Each of them was several thousand feet in size, resembling giant silkworm cocoons, and they were constantly rising up into the air one after another.

The rate at which these cocoons were releasing Bone Needle Insects was far inferior to the rate at which fireballs were being blasted out of the Fire God War Chariots, but each cocoon contained an astonishing number of Bone Needle Insects, so there were many that managed to slip through the cracks.

This initial clash alone resulted in a huge number of casualties, but not a single warrior backed down.

The two armies were rapidly approaching each other, and at a certain distance, the Calm Dawn Tribe warriors suddenly stopped before rising up higher into the sky while raising their bows and nocking arrows.

These clearly weren't normal arrows, as evidenced by the blue patterns engraved upon them, and they were shot into the Insect Race army like rain.

Large swathes of Insect Race warriors and spirit insects were instantly shot down before falling out of the sky, and the arrows were so powerful that some of them even managed to pierce through several Insect Race beings in succession.

Not only that, but after piercing through their targets, the arrows would explode amid bursts of blue light, sending balls of blue flying spraying in all directions.

All of the Insect Race beings that came into contact with the blue flames were quickly reduced to sets of burning skeletons amid bloodcurdling howls.

The Calm Dawn Tribe warriors continued to rain down arrows relentlessly, severely ravaging the Insect Race army.

Right at this moment, an ear-piercing screech rang out, and a swarm of golden beings rose up from the Insect Race army.

These golden Insect Race beings all had wings on their backs and scythe-like arms that appeared extremely sharp, giving the the appearance of humanoid praying mantises.

Their wings were flapping rapidly, and they were able to move with extraordinary speed, pouncing at the Calm Dawn Tribe warriors as streaks of golden light.

The Calm Dawn Tribe warriors were forced to divert their attention to these humanoid praying mantises, which were instantly inundated by a volley of arrows that exploded into a sea of blue fire.

However, in the next instant, all of the humanoid praying mantises that had survived the assault flew out of the sea of fire, and even though almost all of them were carrying injuries, most of them had survived as they continued to charge onward, reaching the Calm Dawn Tribe warriors in the blink of an eye.

As a result, the Calm Dawn Tribe warriors had no choice but to put their arrows away in exchange for long blue sabers to engage in melee combat.

Chapter 554: The Battle is Only Just Beginning

"This is bad news..." Nuo Yifan murmured to herself as her brows furrowed slightly.

"What's wrong?" Han Li asked.

"These are warriors of the Golden Mantis Tribe, a major tribe of the Insect Race similar to the eight holy tribes of our Beast Race. They're supposed to be quite far away from here, residing near the Divine Elephant Tribe and the Falcon Wing Tribe. Similarly, the Bone Needle Insect nests are also very far away from here. On top of that, this attack is also one of a far larger scale than previous attacks," Nuo Yifan explained.

"Are you saying that this is a rather abnormal display of aggression from the Insect Race?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. While our Beast Race and the Insect Race have always been sworn enemies, most of the conflicts that take place between us are distributed throughout the land, and there's never been an attack of this scale in a single place before," Nuo Yifan replied as a concerned look appeared on her face.

"That does seem rather abnormal. It's a good thing that you've made ample preparations. Otherwise, this place would've most likely already been conquered," Han Li replied.

Right at this moment, the two armies down below finally clashed as well.

The Violent Bear Tribe beings were charging at the forefront, and a series of crimson patterns appeared over their brawny bodies, causing them to expand even further in size. The axes that they were wielding were of a similar size to their bodies, and as they were swung through the air, a series of giant crimson ax projections were unleashed.

Even with its numbers advantage, the Insect Race army was unable to oppose the Violent Bear Tribe at all, and the latter tore through the former's ranks, meeting no equal in their path.

The other Beast Race warriors rushed into the hole in the ranks of the Insect Race army torn open by the Violent Bear Tribe, and they were making rapid inroads.

Meanwhile, the bodies of the Monohorn Tribe warriors began to glow green, and a thick layer of enamel took shape, causing them to also expand drastically in size. At the same time, the horns on their heads had also thickened by roughly twofold, while a series of green patterns appeared upon them.

Beams of green light then shot forth from the horns toward the opposing Insect Race army, and these beams of light possessed tremendous penetrative power, with each one often piercing through the bodies of seven or eight Insect Race beings before finally dissipating.

The Insect Race warriors who were struck by these beams of green light were instantly rooted to the spot and immobilized, reducing them to sitting ducks for the Beast Race warriors.

Even though the Monohorn Tribe warriors weren't making as bold and violent a statement as the Violent Bear Tribe, the rate at which they were slaying enemies wasn't slower in the slightest.

The Violent Bear Tribe and Monohorn Tribe warriors formed the spearhead of the Beast Race army, rapidly plunging deep into the Insect Race army's ranks.

Right at this moment, a burst of peculiar screeching rang out from within the Insect Race army, and the Insect Race warriors in front of the Violent Bear Tribe warriors suddenly retreated like the receding tide before countless giant black ants emerged out of seemingly nowhere.

Each ant was the size of a millstone with gleaming black bodies that gave off a metallic sheen. Their tiny eyes were glowing an eerie green color, and they presented a harrowing sight to behold.

The Violent Bear Tribe warriors roared as they swung their axes through the air, unleashing a flurry of ax projections toward the giant ants.

A string of loud clangs rang out as many of the black ants were sent flying, but their bodies were extremely sturdy, and barely any of them were killed. All of the wounded giant ants instantly had their bloodlust ignited, and they began to rush forward once again.

The vast colony of black ants formed a black wave that stood in the path of the Violent Bear Tribe warriors, and even more of them were appearing on either flank.

The Violent Bear Tribe warriors were still attacking with all their might, but their speed was significantly hampered by these fearless black ants.

At the same time, the earth in front of the Monohorn Tribe warriors began to rumble and churn, and an army of earthy yellow scorpions emerged.

Each scorpion was around the same height as a grown man, and what was particularly disturbing about them was that all of them had human faces.

The penetrative power of the beams of green light being released by the Monohorn Tribe warriors was significantly reduced upon striking these human-faced scorpions, and each beam of light was only able to pierce through one scorpion before fading away.

Furthermore, the human-faced scorpions were only immobilized for an instant after being struck by the green light before continuing to charge toward the Monohorn Tribe warriors.

As a result, the progress of the Monohorn Tribe warriors was also significantly hampered.

High up in the sky, the Calm Dawn Tribe warriors were occupied by the Golden Mantis Tribe warriors, so they were unable to assist their fellow comrades.

Initially, the Beast Race army had seized all the momentum, but all of a sudden, they were put in a very awkward situation where neither advancing or retreating seemed like appealing options.

The numbers advantage of the Insect Race army was gradually beginning to manifest itself, and the momentum was rapidly shifting, much to the concern of the Beast Race tribal leaders watching the unfolding battle from the black platform in the sky.

"Inform Chief Sahan that it's time to strike," Nuo Qinglin instructed in a grim voice.

One of the Calm Dawn Tribe beings beside him immediately vanished from the spot, departing to carry out the instruction.

Before long, a red-robed figure shot out from the front lines of the Beast Race army, then raised both hands to release three balls of gray light that appeared above the Beast Race army in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, the red-robed figure began to chat an incantation, and the balls of gray light exploded violently, causing the entire battlefield to tremble violently.

Three mountainous figures abruptly plummeted out of the sky, then crashed down at the center of the Insect Race army.

Countless giant black ants and man-faced scorpions were crushed into mincemeat beneath the enormous weight of these mountainous figures, which were three gray-skinned giants that were over 10,000 feet tall.

Their upper bodies were completely bared, while their lower bodies were covered up by loincloths formed by countless pieces of beast hide stitched together. Furthermore, each of them was wielding an enormous club that they swung toward the Insect Race army.

These gray-skinned giants were downright hideous, possessing giant faces that only had features of a single huge vertical eye, as well as a completely flat and smooth nose consisting only of two nostrils.

The massive maces that they were wielding resembled giant pestles that ground down everything in their path into pulp, and countless giant black ants were crushed, upon which vast volumes of fluorescent green fluid erupted out of their bodies.

The green liquid spread over the ground, corroding everything in their path to send plumes of white smoke rising up into the air.

Following a brief moment of panic, the black ants took a moment to rearrange themselves before charging forward once again, quickly surrounding the three enormous giants.

The ants then began to climb up the bodies of the gray-skinned giants, tearing viciously into the giants' skin with their sharp mandibles while more fluorescent green fluid gushed out of the mouths, corroding the giants' bodies in conjunction with the slicing effect for their mandibles.

The gray-skinned giants were thrashing around frantically while attempting to swat the black ants away with their hands, but these things were extremely stubborn and clung on with all their might.

Right at this moment, the sound of a loud horn rang out, and a unit of warriors with human upper bodies and zebra lower bodies appeared behind the Beast Race army.

Each of them was holding a large bow crafted from vines, and they were pulling out green arrows that were around half a foot in length each before nocking them on their bows.

Their movements were eerily synchronized, and all of them raised their bows to the heavens in unison. As they drew their bowstrings, azure light began to converge from all directions, forming an azure vortex above the tip of each arrow.

The arrows were then let loose, shooting up into the sky before raining down upon the Insect Race army as an azure volley.

The gray-skinned giants were extremely sturdy, and even after being ravaged by the black ants for so long, they had only developed some red spots on their skin. As the volley of azure arrows fell upon them, they were able to remain completely unscathed, but the black ants weren’t as sturdy, and they exploded one after another.

On the other side, Over 1,000 Beast Race demon beasts that were over 1,000 feet tall and clad in thick yellow exoskeletons emerged. Each of them had a pair of thick conical horns on either side of their heads, and they rushed headfirst into the Insect Race army with tremendous power.

The Insect Race was at a clear disadvantage when it came to strength and physical attributes, and with the majority of the man-faced scorpion army at the forefront crushed into mincemeat, their formation was forced back by several dozen kilometers.

However, shortly thereafter, the Vajra Spider and Gray Toad Tribe warriors rushed forward to fill the hole, clashing against the Beast Race army once again.

"It looks like your Beast Race has an advantage now, but they're eventually going to run out of steam, and the Insect Race army far outnumbers you. At this rate, you're going to be defeated," Han Li remarked.

"It's too early to say that, Senior Li. The battle is only just beginning," Nuo Yifan replied in a confident manner.

As soon as her voice trailed off, the sound of dull drumming rang out, immediately followed by some type of strange chanting that was erupting all over the battlefield.

The language being used for the incantation wasn't the language of the Beast Race, nor was it the language prevalently used throughout the immortal regions. However, it still struck Han Li as being somewhat familiar.

After listening for some time, it suddenly occurred to him what language this was.

This seems to be the language of some type of true spirit...

Han Li swept his gaze over the battlefield to find that there were several special gray-robed beings interspersed throughout the armies of the Violent Bear Tribe, and the Monohorn Tribe, and the Calm Dawn Tribe.

All of them possessed different statures, but their attire was identical, and each of them was holding a black wooden staff. At this moment, there were many Beast Race warriors dancing around them, and they were the ones chanting the incantation.

These gray-robed figures only formed a tiny part of the Beast Race army, yet their voices possessed a special penetrative quality that allowed them to be heard across the entire battlefield, and a peculiar atmosphere was beginning to arise.

Chapter 555: Evenly Matched

Upon hearing the incantation from these gray-robed figures, all of the Beast Race warriors on the battlefield instantly became extremely excited, and some of them were even beginning to sing the war songs of their tribes mid-battle.

Compared with this strange incantation, the war songs of the Beast Race were more riveting and impactful, but it was the incantation that was more attention-grabbing to Han Li, and it was causing all of the blood in his body to churn in an involuntary fashion.

Han Li took a moment to regain his focus and shrug off that strange onset of emotion, and as he cast his gaze toward the battlefield again, he discovered that a layer of dark red mist was currently rising up over the Violent Bear Tribe warriors.

Crimson light emerged over the backs of all of the Violent Bear Tribe warriors, and projections of fierce beastly heads appeared within the crimson light, then bared their fangs in a menacing fashion before vanishing into their bodies in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li saw all of the eyes of the Violent Bear Tribe warriors turn bright red, while their bodies swelled several times further in size. In particular, the sharp fangs in their mouths were beginning to jut out, causing drool to flow down from the corners of their lips.

"Kill! Kill! Kill!"

A string of thunderous roars erupted out of their mouths, shaking the entire battlefield.

In that instant, the auras of all of the Violent Bear Tribe warriors had become filled with violence and bloodlust, and they resembled a pack of wild animals as they rushed at the Insect Race army in a frenzy.

On the other side, projections of beastly heads appeared on the bodies of the Monohorn Tribe warriors as well, but these projections glowed green, and each of them had a single horn on their head.

After these projections vanished into their bodies, the Monohorn Tribe warriors didn't grow any taller, nor were they filled with bloodlust like the Violent Bear Tribe warriors. Instead, bones that resembled sharp blades had come protruding out of their elbows and shoulder blades.

At the same time, eight sections of long and thin bones that resembled spider legs emerged from their backs, and each one resembled a steel spear that had been refined hundreds of times.

Additionally, all of the other Beast Race warriors had also been enhanced in different ways.

"Is this a bloodlust technique of your Beast Race?" Han Li asked.

Nuo Yifan faltered slightly upon hearing this, then shook her head as she explained, "Bloodlust technique? That's quite a fitting name, but that's not what we call it. Instead, this is our totem sacrificial technique. The grand elders of all of the tribes sacrifice their own blood essence to draw upon some of the power of the true spirits revered by all of the tribes."

Only then did Han Li realize that the gray-robed figures among the tribes were the grand elders of their respective tribes, and the projections that had appeared on the bodies of the Beast Race warriors were totem symbols of the true spirits that they revered.

"If the tribes can call upon the true spirits that they worship, then why don't they just summon the true spirits onto the battlefield?" Han Li asked with a perplexed expression. "Surely that would easily put an end to this battle."

"Aside from the eight holy tribes of our Beast Race, each tribe worships their own true spirit, but this is not a true contractual relationship. Hence, the revered true spirits only provide some protection to the territories of the tribes. As for whether they're willing to lend their power to those tribes, that depends on how close the bond between tribe and true spirit is.

“Having said that, our Beast Race has always been extremely reverent to our true spirits, so they're willing to help us under the majority of circumstances. Even so, it's very rare for any true spirit to personally descend onto a battlefield," Nuo Yifan explained.

"Is this not a major crisis that warrants their presence?" Han Li asked.

"There are many limitations on true spirits that descend through sacrificial techniques. In particular, if a true spirit is called upon outside of their territory, even the enhancements they'll be able to provide to their worshippers will be lessened, and it's certainly not possible for them to descend.

“Here in the Dark Star Canyon, many of the tribes are already far away from their settlements, so that makes it even more difficult to summon any true spirits," Nuo Yifan explained.

Han Li gave a contemplative nod upon hearing this, and he felt like the relationship between the Beast Race and these true spirits was rather to that between the people and the Earthly Immortals of the Black Wind Sea. Of course, in the case of the latter, the connection wasn't as close as that of the former.

Right at this moment, one of the three gray-skinned giants that was tearing through the ranks of the Insect Race army suddenly toppled forward like a crumbling mountain.

Han Li's pupils instantly contracted slightly upon seeing this.

As it turned out, the ground beneath the gray-skinned giant's feet had suddenly caved in, and a Sand Beast that was even more massive than the giant had pounced out of the earth before opening its mouth, which was lined with circles of sharp teeth, before biting down upon the gray-skinned giant.

Han Li was immediately able to identify the Sand Beast as the very same one that had attacked the ship from Primordial Origin City, the one that was infinitely approaching the High Zenith Stage.

As the gray-skinned giant toppled forward, it was as if its head were being delivered into the massive Sand Beast's mouth, and a loud crack rang out as the giant's head was bitten off in an instant, sending blood spraying in all directions.

Blood began to gush incessantly out of the giant's headless body, which was tilting to the side, but even in its dying moments, it was still swinging its club at the Sand Beast with all its might.

A resounding boom rang out, and the Sand Beast descended back into the earth in the wake of the almighty blow. Meanwhile, the headless giant tumbled to the ground, crushing thousands of giant black ants that were too slow to get out of the way.

A burst of rustling then rang out as the earth churned incessantly, and countless smaller Sand Beasts rose up from the ground to inundate the gray-skinned giant's headless body.

Several seconds later, all of the Sand Beasts vanished back into the ground, and all that remained of the gray-skinned giant was an enormous puddle of blood.

The other two gray-skinned giants had witnessed the demise of the third giant, and they smashed the oncoming wave of man-faced scorpions into pieces with their clubs, then turned around and began retreating back toward the Beast Race army.

However, right at this moment, a short and green humanoid figure that was no more than six feet in height suddenly appeared at the back of the Insect Race army.

Han Li could see that its body was rather similar to that of a human, but its face was very strange and angular, and its eyes were completely black with no white sections within them.

Furthermore, there was a pair of thin and long antennae on its head, giving it the appearance of a giant humanoid grasshopper.

A strange call erupted out of its mouth, and the sound of flapping insect wings instantly rang out from behind the Insect Race army. Immediately thereafter, a dark green cloud rose up from the ground, then began sweeping toward the Beast Race army.

"Those are Green Locust beings! How are there so many of them?" Nuo Yifan exclaimed in a stunned voice upon seeing this.

"Is there a problem?" Han Li asked as he took a glance at the dark green cloud.

"The Green Locust Tribe devours everything that they encounter, and any place that they pass over is often left completely devoid of life. Hence, even in the Insect Race, they're ostracized and denounced by all of the other tribes. They live in swamps all year round, and there aren't supposed to be many of them, but it seems like their population has increased drastically of late," Nuo Yifan replied with tightly furrowed brows.

At this point, the dark green cloud had already caught up to the remaining two gray-skinned giants.

The giants were clearly also aware of how fearsome these things were, and instead of engaging the Green Locust beings in battle, they rushed back in retreat even faster.

Even though there was a vast number of Green Locust beings, they were unable to stop the gray-skinned giants in their tracks. Instead, they would surround the giants, only for the latter to charge straight through them, and the cycle would be repeated.

However, Han Li could tell that each time the giants broke out of an encirclement, their speed would be hampered, and by his estimates, they would only be able to escape seven or eight more times before they would be completely surrounded.

As the gray-skinned giants drew closer and closer, the reinforcements from the Beast Race army also arrived.

A series of giant winged lizards rose up into the sky, then circled around momentarily in the air before opening their mouths to release bursts of scorching black smoke that instantly inundated a large swathe of Green Locust beings.

The dark green cloud was instantly set alight, following which one Green Locust being after came tumbling out of the sky.

The remaining Green Locust beings instantly swooped downward to descend onto the Beast Race army, and these ordinary Beast Race warriors clearly didn't possess comparable physical constitutions to the gray-skinned giants.

In the wake of the Green Locust beings, countless pristine white skeletons were left behind, some of which were still in the process of carrying out whatever motion they had been in the middle of right before they died.

Finally, the two gray-skinned giants managed to escape from the Green Locust beings, but their bodies were riddled with countless tiny bite wounds, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

Their footsteps were quite heavy as they trudged back toward the Dark Star Canyon, and it seemed that they were going to take a rest before re-entering the battle.

However, what everyone had failed to notice was that a barely visible swarm of tiny crimson beetles with glowing tails like those of fireflies were flying toward the pair of giants, and they quickly wriggled their way into the tiny wounds on their bodies.

The two giants instantly stopped in their tracks and turned their gaze to the parts of their bodies that had been infiltrated by these insects, and a series of large red tumor-like growths instantly began to emerge from those wounds.

In just a few seconds, these growths had swelled to the same size as the giants' heads, and both of them were extremely alarmed to see this, but before they had a chance to do anything, the bulbous red growths exploded violently amid flashes of red light, blowing the giants into countless pieces and sending vast volumes of blood splattering down upon the entire battlefield.

Chapter 556: Caught Off Guard

"Those are Blood Leeches!" Nuo Qinglin exclaimed.

A puzzled look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and Nuo Yifan explained, "These leeches are capable of entering a host's body and fusing as one with their blood, making them almost impossible to expel. On top of that, they'll devour the host's blood to form blood tumors, then self-detonate to kill their host along with themselves.

“Due to how tiny and fast they are, they pose an extremely potent threat, but these leeches are very difficult to nurture, so the Insect Race shouldn't have too many of them."

Han Li nodded in response, and he was just about to say something when his expression suddenly changed drastically, and he grabbed onto Nuo Yifan before flying away from the floating platform as a streak of azure light.

Nuo Qinglin and the others faltered slightly before also doing the same, darting away in all directions.

In the next instant, the ground beneath the black platform abruptly exploded, and a gargantuan mouth erupted out into the open. The mouth belonged to none other than that giant Sand Beast from before, and it swallowed the entire platform whole in one go.

Nuo Qinglin and the majority of the tribal leaders were able to escape just in the nick of time, but several of the True Immortal Stage chiefs were not so fortunate, and they were devoured alongside the platform.

A string of bloodcurdling howls rang out from within the giant Sand Beast's mouth before quickly subsiding.

The tribes that had suddenly lost their chiefs were instantly plunged into a state of disarray, but thankfully, these tribes only comprised a very limited portion of the entire Beast Race army.

Meanwhile, Han Li and Nuo Yifan reappeared in the sky close to 20 kilometers away.

Han Li's brows were slightly furrowed, while Nuo Yifan was looking a little pale, and she hurriedly expressed her gratitude to Han Li.

After steadying themselves, Nuo Qinglin and the others were infuriated by the attack, and they immediately prepared to join forces to retaliate against the giant Sand Beast.

However, the Sand Beast paid no heed to them at all. Instead, it erupted out of the ground before pouncing at Han Li's duo at an extraordinary speed.

Han Li immediately grabbed onto Nuo Yifan upon seeing this, and at the same time, a burst of golden lightning flashed over his body, following which the two of them sped away as an arc of golden lightning.

Han Li's lightning movement technique was extraordinarily fast, and even though he was dragging along someone with him, he was still significantly faster than the giant Sand Beast.

The Sand Beast let loose an enraged roar as a flurry of countless yellow runes surged out of its body.

Immediately thereafter, it shrank down to around half its original size, but as a result, its speed was drastically enhanced as it set off in pursuit of Han Li's duo.

"Yifan!"

An urgent look appeared in Nuo Qinglin's eyes as he turned to chase after his daughter, but Ulu raised an arm to stop him as he said, "I'm sure your daughter will be fine for now with that human cultivator protecting her, Chief Nuo. For now, we have to focus on the battle at hand."

Nuo Qinglin cast his gaze downward upon hearing this, and he was alarmed to discover that several massive centipedes that were no smaller than the gray-skinned giants had appeared in the Insect Race army.

Even though they were still quite a bit smaller than the giant Sand Beast, they were still extremely eye-catching on the battlefield.

These centipedes were a bright silver color, and their legs were extremely sharp. They were charging straight into the Beast Race army while releasing toxic yellow mist incessantly out of their mouths, and any Beast Race warrior that came into contact with this yellow mist instantly began to rapidly decompose.

Some of the weaker ones among them were even reduced to puddles of toxic blood that continued to corrode the ground beneath them.

With the giant centipedes leading the way, the Insect Race army had seized the momentum, and it was eagerly pressing its advantage.

The Beast Race warriors were defending with their lives, but they were still being steadily forced back.

Nuo Qinglin quickly sent a male Calm Dawn being with a scar on his face after Han Li, then joined all of the other tribal leaders in the sky above the Beast Race army.

The tide of the battle had completely turned, and the Beast Race army was plunged into a state of panic and chaos, particularly in the wake of the black platform's destruction. However, upon spotting Nuo Qinglin and the others, all of the Beast Race warriors were instantly instilled with a sense of relief and reassurance, and morale was significantly elevated.

At the same time, three Beast Race Golden Immortals, led by a young woman whose face was concealed behind a veil, flew forward before summoning a small bone drum, a bone flute, and a white bone flag, which began to circle around in the air in front of them.

The three of them began to chant an incantation, and a layer of cold white light emerged over the three treasures.

In the next instant, the ground beneath their feet began to rumble and sway, then abruptly split as a series of thick beast bones emerged from beneath the earth.

These beast bones were several thousand feet tall and there were thousands of them, arranged in a uniform line to form an impregnable barrier in the path of the Insect Race army.

There were countless bestial runes engraved onto the beast bones, and in contrast with normal array runes, these ones appeared rougher around the edges, but were giving off extremely formidable spiritual power fluctuations nonetheless.

All of a sudden, the veiled woman switched to a different hand seal, and a black badge flew out of the top of her head amid a flash of black light.

The badge was rather bumpy and crude, and it seemed to have been carved out of the skull of a demon beast.

A design of a beastly head was engraved onto the surface of the badge, and the veiled woman expelled a mouthful of blood essence, which vanished into the badge in a flash.

A layer of black light instantly emerged over its surface, and a peculiar aura began emanating out of the badge, immediately following which countless streaks of black light shot out from within it before vanishing into the giant beastly bones.

The spirit patterns on the bones instantly began to glow brightly, and the bones themselves began to tremble as if they had sprung to life.

A series of spherical bulges abruptly emerged over all of the beast bones, following which countless sharp bone spears flew out within before raining down upon the Insect Race army like a volley of arrows.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and the Insect Race warriors at the forefront of the army were instantly punched full of holes.

The giant centipedes were the veiled woman's main target, and countless bone spears were sent raining down upon them.

However, their exoskeletons were extremely sturdy, and the sharp bone spears only able to raise trails of sparks and leave some white marks on their bodies.

Even though these bone spears weren't able to harm the giant centipedes, they clearly didn't enjoy the barrage, and they were screeching incessantly as they scurried back in retreat.

Right at this moment, four streaks of light flew out of the Insect Race army at an alarming speed.

All four streaks of light were giving off Golden Immortal Stage auras, and the veiled woman's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this, following which she immediately cast an incantation seal into the white bone drum overhead.

The surface of the small drum flashed momentarily as a burst of deafening drumming rang out, and streaks of viscous white light shot out of the drum before also vanishing into the beast bones down below.

A string of loud cracks rang out as all of the beast bones shattered in unison, forming a vast expanse of liquid-like spiritual light, which then rapidly fused together to form an enormous white light barrier in front of the Beast Race army.

All types of bestial designs surfaced on the white light barrier, and bursts of white light were flowing over the light barrier like water. The light barrier didn't appear to be very sturdy at all, but it gave off an indestructible appearance.

The four Insect Race Golden Immortals arrived in front of the light barrier, following which the spiritual light around them faded to reveal a yellow-robed elderly man, a bald man with an intimidating physique, and two near-identical golden-robed women who appeared to be twins.

The four of them were all looking a little startled, clearly not expecting the white restriction to take shape so quickly.

However, the yellow-robed elderly man then immediately sprang into action, sweeping a sleeve through the air to release three streaks of golden light that crashed down heavily upon the white light barrier.

A series of ripples spread over the light barrier around the points where it was struck by the streaks of golden light, but the ripples quickly subsided.

Meanwhile, the golden light rapidly faded to reveal three strange insects with blade-like bodies.

These insects were a radiant golden color, and they were giving off an incredibly sharp aura, resembling three almighty golden swords.

The yellow-robed elderly man's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he cast his gaze toward the three bone treasures up above as he remarked with a cold sneer, "I've heard that the Heavenly Devil Spirit Drum, the Threefold Origin Bone Flute, and the All-encompassing White Bone Flag of the Calm Dawn Tribe were three treasures refined using three sets of High Zenith Stage true spirit remains. I'm curious to see if they can live up to their resounding reputation!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he swept a sleeve through the air once again, and several dozen golden insects shot forth before quickly converging toward a single point.

The other three golden insects also flew over to join them, and in the blink of an eye, they had combined together to form a shimmering golden flying sword.

The yellow-robed elderly man then expelled a mouthful of blood essence into the golden flying sword, and it instantly began to tremble, while the golden light radiating from it grew even brighter.

All of a sudden, it swelled to over 1,000 feet in size, giving off a peerlessly sharp aura as it came crashing down upon the white light barrier with devastating force.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as a long gash was sliced into the white light barrier, but the gash wasn't very deep.

The three Beast Race Golden Immortals remained completely unfazed as they continued to chant incantations while making hand seals.

The white drum instantly swelled slightly in size while emitting a pounding sound, and the bone flute also began to blow, while the bone flag flapped through the air while releasing bursts of white light.

Immediately thereafter, the bodies of the deceased warriors of both races on the battlefield suddenly began to tremble violently.

The flesh on those bodies quickly peeled away to reveal sets of bloodstained skeletons, and these skeletons flew through the air before rushing into the white light barrier, mending the long gash on its surface in the blink of an eye.

The four Insect Race Golden Immortals were all quite surprised to see this, but a cold look then resurfaced in the yellow-robed elderly man's eyes as he swung his golden sword down once again.

At the same time, the other three Insect Race Golden Immortal Stages also lashed out.

The bald man swept a hand through the air, and a ball of radiant white light appeared in front of him.

Through the white light, one could see a white object that resembled a ball of putty that was constantly squirming and changing shape, presenting a rather harrowing sight to behold.

Chapter 557: Miscalculation

The bald man from the Insect Race pointed a finger forward, and six semi-transparent wings abruptly sprang out of the clump of white putty-like substance, following which it began to fly toward the white light barrier.

As it turned out, the mass of putty-like substance appeared to be a strange spirit insect!

A series of corkscrew-shaped white ice crystals appeared in the space in its wake, indicating that it was giving off an almighty chill that seemed capable of freezing the very space itself.

At the same time, its body also swelled up like a balloon, quickly expanding to countless times its original size, and in the instant that it came into contact with the white light barrier, it exploded silently into a cloud of white mist that encompassed the entire light barrier.

A layer of white ice crystals instantly spread over the light barrier, causing the flow of white light over the light barrier to slow down significantly.

At the same time, the two golden-robed women swept their sleeves through the air in silence, releasing a pair of golden clouds that were actually two swarms of countless tiny golden insects.

These insects were only the size of ants, but they had wings on their backs, and their mouths were filled with blade-like sharp teeth.

As soon as they landed upon the layer of white ice crystals, they immediately began sinking their teeth into the white light barrier, and before long, countless holes had been bitten into the light barrier.

The white light barrier was still replenishing itself and mending those holes by absorbing the surrounding skeletons, but it was clearly doing so at a far slower rate than before.

Right at this moment, the yellow-robed elderly man's golden flying sword came crashing down with tremendous power once again, and an earth-shattering boom rang out as the sword clashed with the light barrier.

The latter was already severely ravaged, and several huge cracks instantly appeared on its surface, making it appear as if it could shatter at any moment.

The three Beast Race Golden Immortals' expressions changed drastically upon seeing this, and all of them threw up a mouthful of blood in unison from the backlash, but they had no time to tend to their own internal injuries as they hurriedly cast strings of incantation seals into the three bone treasures overhead.

The three treasures instantly began to glow brightly, while the white light that was moving sluggishly over the surface of the light barrier down below also sped up a little, but the three Golden Immortals knew that they weren't going to be able to last much longer.

......

Meanwhile, far away from the battlefield, the Sand Beast was still pursuing Han Li, with the former racing through the air as a yellow shadow, while Han Li was flashing through the sky as an arc of golden lightning.

At this point, the Sand Beast had shrunk down to less than a thousandth of its original size, and it was far faster than before.

Han Li had already summoned his Thunderstorm Wings and was unleashing his lightning movement technique with all his might, yet he was still unable to shake off the Sand Beast.

The main reason for this was because Nuo Yifan was by his side. With her essentially acting as dead weight, he was naturally bound to be slowed down significantly.

Right as the gap between them was closed to only several dozen kilometers, a ball of yellow light suddenly descended out of the sky toward Han Li. The ball of light was none other than the Sand Beast's spirit domain, and it was giving off tremendous law power fluctuations.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and the Thunderstorm Wings on his back instantly released a burst of golden lightning that enveloped his entire body.

A loud thunderclap rang out, and he and Nuo Yifan were only just barely able to evade the spirit domain, reappearing several hundred kilometers away.

Han Li didn't pause for even a single instant as he vanished into thin air amid another flash of golden lightning, then re-emerged in the sky above a forest.

Finally, he was able to temporarily open up some distance between himself and the Sand Beast, and he hurriedly said to Nuo Yifan, "Get away from here, Fellow Daoist Nuo. The Sand Beast's target is me, so it shouldn't go after you."

Immediately thereafter, he sped away as an arc of golden lightning.

"Look after yourself, Senior Li!"

At this moment, Nuo Yifan's face was still rather pale, but she remained calm and collected as she extended a grateful bow in Han Li's direction, then flew back toward the canyon as a streak of light.

The Sand Beast arrived onto the scene in a flash, and Nuo Yifan's complexion paled even further as she sensed its approaching aura.

The spiritual light around her instantly glowed even brighter as she accelerated in her escape.

The Sand Beast turned to take a glance in Han Li's direction, but didn't immediately set off in pursuit. Instead, it turned to pursue Nuo Yifan instead.

Nuo Yifan was naturally far slower than the Sand Beast, and the distance between them was quickly dwindling.

Several hundred kilometers away, Han Li's expression changed drastically upon sensing this, and he clearly hadn't anticipated that the Sand Beast would be so intelligent.

The reason why he had been unwilling to abandon Nuo Yifan earlier was because he still had to remain in this place, and if she were to be killed because of him, then he would most likely be forced to leave this place.

However, at this point, the two of them were very far away from each other, so it was impossible for him to save her.

All he could do was stop cold in his tracks, then turn back around to fly toward Nuo Yifan as quickly as possible.

Nuo Yifan's complexion had turned deathly pale as she sensed the rapidly approaching Sand Beast, and she hurriedly flipped a hand over to produce a white jade talisman, which she then instantly crushed.

A dull thump rang out as the ball of white spiritual light flew out of the jade talisman before vanishing into her body.

She immediately began to glow with radiant white light, and a pair of crane wings that were several dozen feet in size appeared on her back, instantly enhancing her speed by severalfold.

Even so, she was still slower than the Sand Beast, and the distance between the two was still constantly shrinking.

As the gap between them was whittled down to less than 100 kilometers, the Sand Beast opened its mouth to release a burst of yellow light that resembled a rope, and it swept directly toward Nuo Yifan.

Right at this moment, a thick bolt of silver lightning came crashing down upon the top of the Sand Beast's head.

A huge ball of silver lightning then emerged, enveloping the Sand Beast's head within it, and it was sending arcs of silver lightning flying in all directions.

Immediately thereafter, the scar-faced man from the Calm Dawn Tribe appeared beside Nuo Yifan amid a flash of silver lightning.

"Elder Katun!"

Nuo Yifan was ecstatic to see him.

"We have to get away from here, Young Mistress!"

The scar-faced man slung one arm around Nuo Yifan's waist while holding a silver lightning hammer in his other hand. There was a silver lightning mark engraved onto the head of the hammer, giving off bursts of lightning law power fluctuations, and it was releasing arcs of silver lightning that enveloped both of them.

However, right as they were about to make their escape, a ball of yellow light shot out of the ball of silver lightning behind them, then pierced straight through the scar-faced man's body at an incredible speed.

The ball of silver lightning rippled momentarily before quickly fading to reveal the giant Sand Beast, which was completely unscathed aside the fact that its head had been slightly charred black.

The ball of yellow light had been shot straight out of the Sand Beast's glabella, and the scar-faced man's expression stiffened as he looked down at the ball of yellow light embedded into his chest, which then abruptly exploded.

The scar-faced man's body also exploded into countless pieces that fell out of the sky, but at the same time, the silver lightning hammer in his hand shot forth directly toward the Sand Beast with a tiny nascent soul just barely visible within it.

The lightning hammer reached the Sand Beast in a flash, then exploded violently into a giant ball of silver light that was giving off tremendous energy fluctuations, causing the nearby space to tremble and quiver while gusts of fierce wind were sent sweeping in all directions.

The giant Sand Beast was completely inundated by the silver light, but its roar of alarm and fury could still be heard.

Nuo Yifan was sent flying far into the distance by the ferocious gusts of wind, and tears began to well up in her eyes as she turned to look at the ball of silver light, but in the next instant, a determined look appeared on her face as she sped away as a streak of white light.

A few seconds later, the Sand Beast flew out of the ball of silver light with its entire body riddled with injuries. In particular, its head had become entirely charred black, and it let loose a thunderous roar of fury before suddenly descending out of the sky.

A layer of yellow light emerged over its body as it burrowed into the ground like a fish plunging into water, then quickly re-emerged elsewhere, at which point all of its injuries had disappeared, but its aura had become a little weaker.

Immediately thereafter, it continued to pursue Nuo Yifan as a yellow shadow.

Meanwhile, Han Li emerged amid a flash of golden lightning, and a stunned look appeared in his eyes upon witnessing the Sand Beast's incredible regenerative powers.

He then quickly made a hand seal and vanished from the spot amid another flash of golden lightning.

......

At the entrance of the Dark Star Canyon, Nuo Qinglin turned around and descended onto the fortress behind him.

There were already two gray-robed grand elders waiting for him there, and as soon as he descended onto the fortress, the pair of grand elders instantly declared, "The preparations are complete, Chief Nuo."

Nuo Qinglin nodded in response with a solemn expression, then swept a sleeve through the air, and a loose-fitting purple robe with beautiful embroidered golden stars appeared over his body.

The three of them quickly made their way onto a spacious altar at the center of the fortress, then formed a triangular formation with another, following which each of them produced a wooden staff, which they tapped down onto the strange patterns on the ground.

The two grand elders remained silent, while Nuo Qinglin began to chant an incantation in the true spirit language to complement the tapping of their staves.

Moments later, he raised his staff before ramming its tip heavily down onto the ground, and the staff instantly pierced through the stone material of the altar.

The two grand elders did the same thing, immediately following which Nuo Qinglin raised an arm before swiping a finger across the palm of his hand, instantly inflicting a gash that was deep enough to reveal bone.

Glowing purple blood flowed out of the gash before dripping down onto the ground, but instead of splattering in all directions, the blood stayed together to form a tiny dark purple snake that began to extend forward.

Before long, the tiny snake had filled the entire array on the altar, and Nuo Qinglin's complexion had paled significantly as he gritted his teeth and rammed the bottom of his staff into the ground once again.

A faint buzzing sound rang out as a burst of radiant purple light erupted out of the entire altar, and a complex purple array projection emerged, within which were countless tiny specks of light that were dancing around like fireflies before converging to form a giant shadow the size of a small mountain.

Chapter 558: Suliu

The huge shadow was still for a moment before gradually rising up higher, and it was also taking on a more substantial form.

Even before the shadow's body had completely taken shape, a voice rang out from within the array. "What's wrong, kid? Is the state of the battle already so bad that you had to summon me?"

As the voice trailed off, the purple light within the array also gradually faded, revealing the giant shadow to be an enormous fox with azure fur, and it was seated with its legs crossed like a human cultivator.

The azure fox had a pair of thin and long eyebrows, and there was a symbol of a purple star on its glabella. There were also three long scars that ran parallel to each other over its right eye, looking as if they had been inflicted by the claws of some type of demon beast.

The azure fox was clad in a suit of extremely beautiful azure armor, and it had six massive tails that were dragging along behind it as it looked at Nuo Qinglin with a disdainful expression.

Nuo Qinglin hurriedly extended a deep bow as he said, "My sincerest apologies, Master Suliu, but I had to call upon you as Yifan is in grave danger!"

"What?! Who dares to pick on Yifan?"

The giant azure fox was enraged to hear this, and its six tails began to flail around in a display of fury.

"Right now, Yifan is being pursued by the Sand Beast raised by the chief of the Sand Eating Tribe. At the moment, all of our warriors are busy battling against the Insect Race army, so none of us can go and rescue her," Nuo Qinglin explained in an urgent and fearful voice.

Suliu immediately turned around to scour the battlefield in search of Nuo Yifan while grumbling in a thunderous voice, "What kind of father are you, Nuo Qinglin? Yifan is my pride and joy! You won't get away with it if something happens to her!"

As it was speaking, its gaze settled upon a certain spot on the distant horizon, where Nuo Yifan was being pursued by the Sand Beast.

"There she is..."

Suliu's eyes narrowed slightly as it sprang up into the sky like a flying mountain, then flew directly toward Nuo Yifan with its six massive tails flailing through the air behind it.

Fervent looks instantly appeared on the faces of all of the Calm Dawn Tribe warriors down below at the sight of Suliu, and they began to chant its name in reverence as they charged toward the Insect Race army with renewed vigor.

Meanwhile, Nuo Yifan was frantically fleeing from the Sand Beast, and in her haste to do so, she was getting further and further away from Han Li.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but all he could do was continue to fly after her in pursuit.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out, and the cliff face that Nuo Yifan was flying toward suddenly exploded.

The Sand Beast had burrowed into the ground, and it erupted out of the remnants of the collapsed cliff face before pouncing at Nuo Yifan with its mouth wide open, having already reverted back to its original size.

Nuo Yifan was very alarmed to see this, but to her credit, she remained composed as she swung around in mid-air, then stepped onto a giant falling rock, using it as a launch pad to propel herself away from the giant Sand Beast.

However, right at this moment, a dark red vortex abruptly emerged within the Sand Beast's mouth, and it was releasing a burst of tremendous suction force that was far too powerful for Nuo Yifan to withstand.

As a result, she wasn't able to get away at all before she found herself being sucked toward the Sand Beast's mouth.

Right as she was about to be devoured by the Sand Beast, Han Li hurriedly made a hand seal before pointing in a finger forward, and an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword reached Nuo Yifan in the blink of an eye, catching her during her rapid fall.

The sword was glowing brightly as it sent a burst of sword Qi erupting in all directions, counteracting the suction force surging out of the Sand Beast's mouth. Immediately thereafter, the sword flew away into the distance, carrying Nuo Yifan on top of it.

The Sand Beast's mouth was closed with tremendous power, but much to its fury and frustration, it had chomped down onto nothing more than empty air.

It shrank back a little while coiling itself like a spring, then shot up into the sky like a cannonball, hurtling directly toward Nuo Yifan.

Having only just barely escaped from the jaws of death, Nuo Yifan didn't even get a chance to catch her breath before her demise was once again imminent.

"Don't be scared, Yifan, I'll take care of this thing!"

Right at this moment, Suliu arrived on the scene, and it sprang through the sky, leaping over Nuo Yifan to pounce onto the giant Sand Beast that was pursuing her.

The two enormous beings clashed violently in mid-air, then came tumbling down to the ground together.

Meanwhile, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords swiveled around in the sky before carrying Nuo Yifan toward Han Li.

Nuo Yifan was still looking deathly pale, and after taking a moment to compose herself, she said, "Thank you for saving my life, Senior Li. I'll be sure to repay you for this."

Han Li merely nodded in response while making a beckoning motion to summon his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword back to himself.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out in the distance, and both of them turned to discover that the giant Sand Beast was currently stuck under Suliu, and despite its best efforts, it was unable to free itself.

Suliu was straddled atop the Sand Beast, and its tails were wrapped around the Sand Beast like six giant azure pythons, constricting tighter and tighter to crush its prey.

At the same time, it had also released its spirit domain, but not very far, only just enough to encompass the Sand Beast.

"What's that?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

"This is Master Suliu, the true spirit revered by our Calm Dawn Tribe. His cultivation base is comparable to that of early-High Zenith cultivators for you humans," Nuo Yifan explained.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression.

He had seen many different types of fox demons back in the Mortal Realm and the Spirit Realm, but most of them excelled in illusory and seductive techniques. It was the first time that he had seen a fox demon that possessed such immense physical prowess.

Having said that, given that the azure fox was a primordial true spirit, it had to have already been residing in the primordial land since time immemorial, so it naturally couldn't be compared with ordinary demons.

All of a sudden, Suliu made a grabbing motion with both hands, and a burst of black light converged to form an enormous black staff in his hands, one that was riddled with star patterns and glowing faintly.

Suliu let loose a thunderous roar, and the star patterns on the staff in his hands brightened significantly as a radiant vortex of starlight took shape on the tip of the staff before it was plunged down viciously toward the Sand Beast's head.

Even though the Sand Beast's body was temporarily immobilized, it was still able to swivel its head around, and it opened its cavernous mouth, then chomped down upon the black staff as a burst of dark red light emerged within its mouth.

A small section of the staff was plunged into the Sand Beast's mouth, and the starlight vortex clashed against the dark red light.

Bursts of formidable energy fluctuations erupted out of the Sand Beast's mouth as countless specks of starlight clashed against the vast expanse of dark red light, and it seemed that the two were evenly matched.

A hint of concern appeared in Nuo Yifan's eyes upon seeing this, but remained an observer as she knew that she would only become a hindrance by entering the fray.

"Don't worry, Senior Suliu's cultivation base is slightly superior to the Sand Beast's, so he'll be fine," Han Li consoled.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a series of golden ring patterns began to emerge over the Sand Beast's body, and it began to swell in size, gradually forcing Suliu's tails apart one by one until they were no longer able to trap it.

"You're not getting away!" Suliu sneered, and the starry design on his glabella suddenly began to glow with dazzling radiant, while his eyes turned pitch-black, following which an image of a starry night sky appeared within them.

Immediately thereafter, the aura that was emanating from his body also became as deep and vast as the night sky.

As Han Li looked into Suliu's eyes, he was momentarily dazed, and for an instant, he felt as if he really were standing in the boundlessly vast night sky among the stars, waiting for a baptism of starlight.

In the next instant, all of the star patterns on Suliu's staff lit up in unison, making it appear as if there were a starry night sky clinging to the staff, and it was releasing bursts of peculiar energy fluctuations that didn't seem to belong to this world.

At the same time, a burst of blinding starlight erupted forth, and all of the energy fluctuations condensed together before descending to clash violently against the dark red light in the Sand Beast's mouth.

Almost at the exact same moment, the Sand Beast finally struggled free from Sului's tails, and a series of radiant golden rings surged up toward its head from its tail, as if it were focusing all of its power into its mouth.

The two bursts of tremendous power clashed with an earth-shattering boom, and bursts of incredibly formidable shockwaves were sent sweeping through the air in all directions. The dark red light resembled the radiance of the dying sun, and it completely exploded amid the countless specks of descending starlight.

Immediately thereafter, the Sand Beast's enormous body exploded into countless grains of sand, resulting in an enormous sandstorm that erupted outward with immense power, completely pulverizing all of the mountains and trees in its path.

Chapter 559: Cockroach

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he swept a sleeve through the air to release several bursts of azure light, which intertwined to form an azure light barrier in front of himself and Nuo Yifan.

In the next instant, the violent sandstorm descended upon them with unstoppable force, and it was as if the azure light barrier were being barraged by countless arrows, but it remained as resolute as a mountain.

Gusts of yellow wind rapidly spread through an enormous surrounding area, hurling more sand up into the sky while countless trees were uprooted before being buried under the sand. In the blink of an eye, the entire area in a radius of tens of thousands of feet had been transformed into a sea of sand.

The battlefield between the Beast Race and the Insect Race was quite far away from where Suliu, and the Sand Beast were locked in combat, but even so, the gusts of fierce wind were still able to sweep over the entire battlefield, reducing visibility to near zero.

In fact, the weaker warriors on the battlefield found it extremely difficult just to remain still on the spot without being blown away, and as a result, the advance of the Insect Race army was slowed down significantly.

This was naturally good news for the Beast Race army, and in particular, the Golden Immortals of the Beast Race heaved a collective sigh of relief, then pounced on this opportunity to alter the army's formation and fortify its defensive line.

The Beast Race army had the home advantage on this battlefield, and during this brief window of respite, some of the tribes were able to unveil the defensive measures that they hadn't been able to reveal up to this point.

Shortly thereafter, the sandstorm subsided, and everything returned to normal.

The morale of the Beast Race army was lifted significantly upon witnessing their revered true spirit slay such a powerful enemy, and they quickly arranged a counterattack under the instructions of their chiefs before charging toward the Insect Race army.

Due to how aggressive the Insect Race army's attack had been, the Beast Race army had been caught slightly off guard, but now that they had been given a chance to regroup and launch an effective counterattack, it didn't take long before the advance of the Insect Race army was stopped cold in its tracks.

At the center of the sea of sand, the Sand Beast was nowhere to be seen, and all that remained was Suliu, who was holding onto his black staff with one hand, while clutched in his other hand was a large sand crystal.

This sand crystal was clearly of a far superior quality to the one that Han Li had obtained. Not only was it completely translucent, there were some golden threads inside that were giving off bursts of formidable spiritual power fluctuations.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to do away with the azure light barrier, and Nuo Yifan immediately rushed over to Suliu's side as she asked in an urgent voice, "Are you alright, Master Suliu?"

"Of course! I'm as fit as a..."

Suliu's voice abruptly cut off mid-sentence as he threw up a mouthful of blood.

Nuo Yifan immediately flew around Suliu until she was in front of him, and only then did she discover that there was a huge hole on his chest. A large section of the azure armor around the hole had been charred black, and at this moment, the wound was slowly healing while releasing wisps of white smoke.

Meanwhile, Han Li merely stood and observed from afar.

At the same time, Jin Tong was communicating to Han Li through his spiritual sense, trying to goad him into taking that sand crystal from Suliu.

Prior to this, she had been staying in Xiao Bai's belly. However, despite her incredible physical constitution, the internal space in Xiao Bai's body also proved to be quite extraordinary, and she was forced to re-emerge not long ago.

"Forget it. Right now, we're counting on the Beast Race to deal with the other Gold Devouring Immortal for you. If we try any funny business now, there's a very good chance that we'll be banished by the Beast Race, and we'll have to face the Insect Race army on our own," Han Li replied through voice transmission.

"Speaking of the other Gold Devouring Immortal, it seems to be getting closer and closer!" Jin Tong exclaimed. "I have to hide again. Open your mouth, Xiao Bai!"

"You can hide in my stomach, but please don't eat any more of my treasures. It's not been easy saving up those immortal treasures, and you've eaten a third of them in one go!" Xiao Bai protested.

"Why are you stingy, Xiao Bai? Uncle has more than enough immortal treasures for both of us to eat!" Jin Tong retorted with a displeased expression.

"Master..." Xiao Bai wailed.

"If we manage to survive this ordeal, I'll let you eat to your heart's content, but if we can't, then this might be the end for us," Han Li said in a grim voice as he cast his gaze toward a certain direction with blue light flashing through his eyes.

......

"I'm glad you're safe," Suliu said with a pleased nod after carefully examining Nuo Yifan.

"It's all thanks to you and Senior Li," Nuo Yifan replied.

"This is the human you were talking about?" Suliu asked as he turned to Han Li and rested the bottom of his staff against the ground.

"That's right. Senior Li has saved my life twice now," Nuo Yifan replied with a nod.

"Oh? You sound very grateful to him. Could it be that you're planning to repay him with your body?" Suliu jibed with a sly grin.

Nuo Yifan knew that Suliu was making fun of her, so she could only remain silent with a displeased pout on her face.

"Humans have always been very cunning, sometimes even more so than our Fox Tribe, so make sure you don't become too close with him," Suliu continued as a serious look appeared on his face.

"I understand, Master Suliu," Nuo Yifan replied with a nod.

Right as the two of them were conversing with one another, Suliu's expression abruptly changed drastically as he grabbed onto Nuo Yifan, then hurled her at Han Li as he yelled in the language of the immortal regions, "Take her away from here!"

Han Li seemed to have already detected that something was amiss, and in the instant that Suliu threw Nuo Yifan through the air, he had already vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, he appeared right in Nuo Yifan's path, then caught her by the waist before vanishing from the spot once again.

After hurling Nuo Yifan away, Suliu picked up his black staff, then thrust it into the space up ahead with tremendous force, and his attack was aimed in the exact same direction that Han Li had been observing just a moment ago.

The star patterns on the staff began to glow radiantly, and a burst of silver light emerged on the tip of the staff, then instantly expanded to form a radiant starry sky that was several thousand feet in size.

Immediately thereafter, a resplendent golden sun abruptly emerged in front of the starry sky out of nowhere.

The enormous ball of golden light crashed down upon the starry sky light barrier released by the black staff like a meteorite, and an earth-shattering boom rang out.

The starry night sky instantly exploded, and in the face of this ball of golden light, Suliu's staff was made to appear as fragile as a stick of sorghum, quickly shattering into countless pieces.

Ultimately, the countless stars were unable to contend against the single sun, and the entire starry sky exploded violently.

Suliu let loose an agonized roar as his giant body was sent flying back like a rucksack, plowing an extremely deep trench into the ground before he crashed heavily into a cliff face.

Countless loose rocks came tumbling down from the cliff face, instantly burying half of his entire body.

A trail of black blood began to trickle down from the corner of his lips, and he gritted his teeth as he glowered intently at the ball of golden light, within which was a golden beetle that was over 10,000 feet in size.

Its entire body was giving off an indescribably fearsome aura, and even Han Li was fleeing toward the canyon with his back facing the golden beetle, he knew that it was none other than the Gold Devouring Immortal that Jin Tong had been referring to.

Even though it was virtually identical to Jin Tong in appearance, its aura was at the late-High Zenith Stage!

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon sensing the golden beetle's aura, but he didn't slow down at all. Instead, he began racing away even faster than before.

"Master Insect Spirit!"

The Insect Race army was struggling to ward off the aggressive assault of the Beast Race army, but all of the Insect Race warriors instantly erupted into thunderous cheers at the sight of the Gold Devouring Immortal.

All of the spirit insects that were being controlled by the Insect Race warriors were also reinvigorated, and they began rushing at the Beast Race army with renewed effort and bloodlust, restoring both armies to even footing once again.

At this point, Nuo Qinglin had already returned to the battlefield, and an alarmed look appeared on his face at the sight of the Gold Devouring Immortal, following which he hurriedly cast his gaze toward Suliu in search for his daughter.

However, as he began to search for Nuo Yifan's aura, he discovered that she had already been brought back to the canyon by Han Li.

"Hand it over!" the golden beetle said in a cold and thunderous voice that rumbled over the entire battlefield.

"Just like Father said, you're as resilient as a cockroach! If you're not killed, then you'll only come back stronger, but I didn't think you would've already become this powerful since the last war..." Suliu jeered as he coughed up another mouthful of blood.

"Don't make me repeat myself," the golden beetle said in a cold voice, then crossed its two front legs before sweeping them both violently through the air, releasing two streaks of translucent light that resembled a pair of massive cicada wings, which then instantly vanished in a flash.

However, Suliu seemed to have already been prepared for the attack, and he immediately sprang up from the ground, jumping up several thousand feet to evade the two streaks of translucent light just in the nick of time.

Han Li was closely observing the golden beetle from afar with blue light flashing in his eyes, and he was astonished by what he saw.

As it turned out, even the dust particles and rays of light in the path of the two streaks of translucent light had been cleaved into two.

After Suliu dodged the attack, the cliff face behind him was struck by the two streaks of translucent light, and the entire cliff face was severed like tofu, unable to pose any resistance.

Suliu hovered high up in the sky, looking very much worse for wear as he yelled, "Father, this cockroach is picking on me!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, a vast expanse of radiant starlight appeared in the sky, and an even more massive figure emerged from within.

Chapter 560: King

This was another azure fox that was over twice the size of Suliu.

It was wearing a suit of beautiful golden armor that was riddled with countless flashing silver runes, and there were nine massive tails trailing along behind it, giving it a very majestic appearance.

The nine-tailed fox also had a set of long and thin eyebrows, and there was also a radiant star design on its glabella.

At the same time, it was giving off an enormous aura that was slightly superior even to that of the golden beetle.

"Our king!"

Fervent looks appeared on the faces of all of the Beast Race Golden Immortals at the sight of the nine-tailed fox, while the Beast Race army down below enjoyed another significant morale boost.

"Father!"

Suliu immediately flew over to the nine-tailed fox's side, but the golden beetle wasn't paying any attention to Suliu or the nine-tailed fox. Instead, its golden eyes were roaming over its surroundings, seemingly searching for something.

Han Li was rather apprehensive at the sight of the golden beetle's searching gaze, and he couldn't be certain if Jin Tong really would be able to escape its detection by hiding in Xiao Bai's stomach.

Thankfully, the golden beetle's gaze swept over him without pause, and that came as quite a relief to him, but he still didn't dare to let down his guard.

The nine-tailed fox gave Suliu a stern glare, then raised a front paw to send a burst of azure light flying into Suliu's body.

With this injection of azure light, most of Suliu's injuries were instantly healed, and a wide smile appeared on his face as he said, "Thank you, Fa..."

"Stand down," the nine-tailed fox instructed, cutting him off in a serious voice.

Suliu nodded in response, then flew away into the distance.

"Leave this place right now, Insect Spirit. Otherwise, you leave me with no choice but to strike you down!" the nine-tailed fox declared in a thunderous voice.

Only then did the golden beetle finally turn its gaze to the nine-tailed fox for the first time.

In the next instant, it abruptly transformed into a golden shadow, appearing behind the nine-tailed fox in a flash before opening its mouth to release a thick pillar of translucent golden light, which pierced straight through the nine-tailed fox's body in the blink of an eye.

The nine-tailed fox remained completely still on the spot, seemingly having failed to react, but in the next instant, he abruptly vanished, revealing that body to have only been an afterimage.

The golden beetle faltered slightly upon seeing this, and it stopped cold in its tracks.

Immediately thereafter, the nine-tailed fox appeared behind it out of thin air amid a flash of azure light, following which its nine tails shot out like lightning to ensnare the golden beetle while also releasing an azure spirit domain.

At the same time, a layer of black spiritual light emerged over its nine tails, and starlight was flashing incessantly over the tails as they rapidly constricted, tightening around the golden beetle's body like nine black pythons.

The nine-tailed fox then opened his mouth to release a pillar of black flames that struck the golden beetle before erupting into a sea of fire, and all of this had taken place in the blink of an eye.

The sea of fire was giving off bursts of incredibly scorching heat that caused the nearby space to warp and tremble violently, and even though Han Li was quite a distance away from the sea of fire, even he had to fly into the distance, unable to bear the heat.

Suliu had also retreated into the distance as a pleased look appeared in his eyes.

Meanwhile, the nine-tailed fox continued its barrage of attacks, and a beam of starlight abruptly shot out of the star design on his glabella.

The beam of starlight was formed by countless black starlight runes, and they were plunged into the sea of black flames while giving off tremendous law power fluctuations.

As a result, the sea of fire reared up significantly, and the black flames quickly became lighter in color, but the heat that they were giving off only continued to elevate.

The nearby space was tainted a black color, and it also began warping far more violently than before, making it appear as if the very space were about to be set alight.

The golden beetle was completely inundated by the sea of fire, and it seemed that it had already been incinerated into ashes.

Suliu was ecstatic to see this, as were all of the Beast Race Golden Immortals, while all of the Insect Race Golden Immortals were looking on in horror and despair.

However, in the next instant, the sea of fire suddenly began to churn violently, and a rapidly expanding vortex appeared within it, following which a burst of golden light emerged within the vortex.

Before the nine-tailed fox had a chance to do anything, the vortex abruptly swelled in size, while the golden light inside also brightened significantly, and all of the black flames were instantly sucked into the vortex.

As a result, the golden beetle was revealed, and it was still ensnared within the nine tails, but there was golden light radiating from its mouth as it devoured the final wisp of black fire.

The cheering from the Beast Race army instantly subsided, and the entire battlefield fell still for a moment, while Suliu was also looking on with his mouth agape in shock.

"How has the insect spirit become so powerful? It stood no chance against Master Yohu during the last war..." Nuo Yifan murmured to herself with a stunned expression.

"Is this your king?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. Master Yohu is the king that's worshiped by all of our Beast Race tribes, and he's also the father of our tribe's true spirit, Suliu," Nuo Yifan replied with a nod.

"It sounds like this isn't the first battle between your king and the insect spirit. How does the insect spirit match up against your kind? Does it have any weaknesses?" Han Li asked.

"The insect spirit has an incredibly sturdy body and can devour almost all attacks, so I can't think of any physical weaknesses. I recall that Master Yohu had only been able to force it into retreat last time by using some type of spiritual attack," Nuo Yifan replied.

Han Li nodded in response.

He knew better than anyone else just how incredible the physical prowess of Gold Devouring Beetles were. However, compared with their near-indestructible bodies, their souls were indeed far more fragile.

Right as Han Li and Nuo Yifan were conversing with each other, the golden beetle suddenly turned his gaze to the nine tails around its body, following which two thin streaks of translucent golden light erupted out of its front limbs toward the tails.

The nine-tailed fox immediately withdrew its tails as quickly as it could while also fleeing into the distance, and even though it had reacted very quickly, two of its tails were still struck by the streaks of golden light.

Those two tails were instantly severed, and blood came gushing out of the wounds.

The nine-tailed fox drew to a halt close to 10 kilometers away, and a furious look appeared in its eyes at the sight of its severed tails.

It thrust its two front paws forward, and two resounding thumps rang out as a pair of giant beastly paw projections, one azure and one black, emerged above the golden beetle.

The paw projections were giving off a faint azure glow, within which were countless dancing azure runes, following which an image of a starry night sky emerged on the paw projections.

The two projections drew back slightly, then came crashing down upon the golden beetle with tremendous power.

The golden beetle gave a disdainful sneer, following which two bursts of golden light that resembled pythons shot out of its body, then pierced through the pair of paw projections with ease before winding themselves around the projections and constricting viciously.

A burst of terrifying power instantly began acting upon the pair of paw projections, instantly shattering them into countless specks of azure and black spiritual light, which spread through the entire surrounding area in a radius of close to 10 kilometers.

The nine-tailed fox raised its two front paws before drawing a pair of semi-circles in mid-air, and the scattered specks of azure and black light suddenly began to flash before fusing together to form countless black and azure threads of light that wound themselves around the golden beetle.

The golden beetle was clearly a little taken aback by this, but it remained completely unfazed as countless streaks of translucent golden light erupted out of its body to strike the black and azure threads of light.

These threads of light didn't appear to be all that remarkable, but they were incredibly sturdy, and only less than half of them were severed, while the rest remained firmly in place.

A hint of surprise flashed through the golden beetle's eyes upon seeing this, and right at this moment, the nine-tailed fox appeared directly above its head.

Black light flashed from the nine-tailed fox's front paws, and two sets of scythe-like black claws that each around 10 feet in length sprang forth.

The nine-tailed fox then swooped down with radiant starlight emanating from its claws, which scratched down viciously upon the golden beetle's back to send sparks flying in all directions.

A burst of tremendous energy fluctuations erupted in all directions as the golden and black light clashed with immense power, and all of the claws on the nine-tailed fox's front paws were snapped, while only a series of white marks had appeared on the golden beetle's back.

The claws hadn't even been able to draw any blood, and the nine-tailed fox's expression instantly darkened significantly upon seeing this.

All of a sudden, the golden light radiating from the golden beetle's body abruptly brightened significantly, and translucent threads of golden light could be seen within it, giving off a burst of tremendous suction force.

The black light was instantly sucked into the golden light on contact, while the golden light continued to surge toward the nine-tailed fox.

The nine-tailed fox was clearly very wary of this golden light, and he immediately sprang away into the distance as an azure shadow.

However, right at this moment, the golden light around the golden beetle brightened even further, giving it the appearance of an incandescent golden sun.

The radiant golden light rapidly spread outward in all directions to form an enormous golden spirit domain, within which streaks of golden light were swirling around incessantly to form a series of vortexes of different sizes.

The nine-tailed fox wasn't able to get very far away at all before it was caught within the golden spirit domain, upon which its speed was significantly hampered.

At this point, the threads of azure and black light around the golden beetle's body had already vanished, and it cast a cold gaze toward the nine-tailed fox before opening its mouth to release around a dozen golden law threads.

As soon as these law threads shot out of its mouth, they immediately swelled drastically in size while radiating dazzling golden light with countless golden runes flashing within it.

Immediately thereafter, the dozen or so enlarged law threads intertwined to form an extremely lifelike golden wyrm that was several thousand feet in length.

Chapter 561: Forced Intervention

The golden wyrm was radiating dazzling golden light as it flew through the air with tremendous power and astonishing speed, reaching the nine-tailed fox in the blink of an eye.

The nine-tailed fox threw back its head and let loose an almighty roar upon seeing this, and all of the spiritual light within the azure spirit domain converged toward him before forming six azure light barriers in front of him.

Countless bursts of worm-like spiritual light were flashing and squirming incessantly over the light barriers, giving off tremendous law power fluctuations.

The azure light barriers had only just taken shape when the golden wyrm arrived before crashing into the azure light barriers, which were shattered one after another in rapid succession.

However, the golden wyrm had also been whittled down significantly, having been reduced to around half of its original size, but it hadn't slowed down in the slightest.

A stunned look appeared in the nine-tailed fox's eyes upon seeing this, and he opened his mouth to release two bursts of light, one black and one azure.

The two bursts of light then intertwined to form a massive black and azure arrow, which crashed into the golden wyrm.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as a giant ball of golden light emerged, encompassing everything within a radius of several dozen kilometers within it, including the nine-tailed fox.

Black and azure lights were interspersed throughout the golden light, but they were clearly being overwhelmed.

The entire battlefield was instantly illuminated as a burst of unfathomably enormous spiritual pressure erupted throughout the surrounding area, sweeping up ferocious gusts of wind in all directions.

Some of the weaker Insect Race and Beast Race warriors were sent flying by the fierce gusts of wind, and they didn't even get a chance to cry out before they were completely dismembered.

Right at this moment, a streak of azure light shot out of the ball of golden light, then faded to reveal the nine-tailed fox.

At this moment, he was looking quite disheveled, with several long gashes on his body. There was also a large hole on his lower abdomen, and the spiritual light around his body had also dimmed significantly, making it very apparent that he had suffered very severe injuries.

"Father!" Suliu exclaimed as he hurriedly arrived by the nine-tailed fox's side, and all of the Beast Race warriors down below were looking on in despair.

Right at this moment, a sharp whistling sound rang out as the golden beetle arrived on the scene as a ball of golden light.

Even though the nine-tailed fox was very severely injured, it still stood up straight to face the enemy, while Suliu was also prepared for battle.

Right at this moment, a giant white archway abruptly appeared in the sky above the ball of golden light, then crashed down upon the golden beetle.

There was a series of ring-shaped designs engraved onto the archway, and they were giving off tremendous spiritual power fluctuations, indicating that this was a very formidable immortal treasure.

All of a sudden, the white archway began to glow with intense white radiance, which formed a giant halo that restricted the golden beetle's body within it.

Following the emergence of the white halo, the golden beetle was instantly stopped cold in its tracks, much to the surprise of the two azure foxes.

"I didn't think that a primordial true spirit like yourself would sink as low as to turn to a wretched human for help!" the golden beetle sneered as it swept its front limbs through the air, releasing a vast expanse of translucent golden light that instantly converged to form a streak of light that was several thousand feet in length before crashing into the white archway.

A resounding boom rang out as the streak of golden light shattered, and a deep gash was also sliced into the white archway, but it remained intact.

The white halo released by the white archway also shrank down significantly, but the golden beetle was very surprised to see that its attack had failed to destroy the target.

Right at this moment, a purplish-golden giant that was several hundred feet tall and had three heads and six arms appeared above the white archway.

It was none other than Han Li after adopting his Holy Nirvana Physique, and there was a determined look on his face as he swung his arms through the air with immense power.

Three streaks of light, one golden, one black, and one white shot out of his hands, and they contained a golden net, a black wooden ruler, and a sheet of white paper, all of which were spoils that he had reaped from the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor.

The golden net swelled drastically in size before descending upon the golden beetle, while the black ruler also expanded rapidly before striking the beetle.

At the same time, countless huge black runes appeared on its surface, then converged to form a black array that encompassed the golden beetle within it.

Meanwhile, the sheet of paper transformed into a vast white mountain in the blink of an eye before crashing down violently.

Bursts of white light surged out of the mountain to form a hemispherical white light barrier, which also encompassed the golden beetle.

Thanks to the support from the three immortal treasures, the white archway was stabilized, and the four immortal treasures were temporarily able to trap the golden beetle.

However, Han Li didn't let down his guard in the slightest upon seeing this, and he began to chant a rapid incantation.

He hadn't decided to enter the fray out of the kindness of his heart. Instead, the problem was that Jin Tong wasn't going to be able to hide in Xiao Bai's body for long, and if Yohu were to be defeated, then he would be forced to face this High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal on his own once Jin Tong inevitably emerged from Xiao Bai's belly.

With that in mind, Han Li was casting a rapid string of incantation seals into the four immortal treasures with four of his hands, while his other two hands were swept through the air to release Feng Tiandu's full set of 36 Origin Separation Law Chains, which he had obtained in the wake of Feng Tiandu's demise.

However, he still hadn't been able to completely refine them, but even so, they had served as Feng Tiandu's bonded treasure, so they naturally contained tremendous law powers, and they were particularly effective in sealing a target's soul.

All three of Han Li's heads were chanting an urgent incantation, and the 36 Origin Separation Law Chains instantly sprang to life as countless tiny black runes surged out of them, giving off bursts of astonishing law power fluctuations.

The golden beetle was very alarmed upon sensing the aura of the Origin Separation Law Chains, and it let loose a furious roar as all of the golden light around it abruptly surged back into its body, forming a series of flashing golden spots that resembled countless eyes all over its exoskeleton.

A loud shrieking sound rang out as a streak of translucent golden light shot out of each of those golden eyes before striking the four immortal treasures.

The golden net began to tremble violently, and it was the first one to be torn apart. After that, the black array formed by the wooden ruler was only able to last a few seconds before it was also destroyed, immediately following which the giant black ruler shattered into countless pieces.

The countless streaks of translucent golden light then struck white archway and the white mountain in a devastating barrage, but the pair of immortal treasures proved to be surprisingly resilient, managing to hold themselves together, much to Han Li's relief.

Both the archway and the sheet of white paper were immortal treasures that had been crafted out of jade materials, and just as he had anticipated, such materials were more adept at warding off attacks from Gold Devouring Immortals.

He began to cycle through his hands seals even more urgently as all six of his eyes began to glow brightly, and a translucent sword projection suddenly shot out of the glabella of his central head, then reached the golden beetle in a flash.

The golden beetle immediately lashed out at the sword projections with its front limbs at an astonishing speed, but before they were able to intercept the sword projection, it had already pierced straight into the golden beetle's head.

A pained look instantly appeared on the golden beetle's face, and its massive body began to tremble uncontrollably as it let loose an agonized cry.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, and he opened his mouth to release a ball of purplish-golden blood essence, which transformed into a cloud of purplish-golden mist that fused into the 36 Origin Separation Law Chains.

After absorbing Han Li's blood essence, the runes on the Origin Separation Law Chains began to glow even brighter, while the law powers that they released were also further enhanced.

As Han Li made one final hand seal, the 36 Origin Separation Law Chains abruptly vanished from the spot before reappearing in front of the golden beetle and attempting to burrow their way into its body.

Even though the golden beetle was still trembling uncontrollably, it was still able to remain lucid and conscious, and it released a burst of golden light with great difficulty, within which were 30 to 40 radiant golden law threads.

The golden law threads began to revolve on the spot, forming a golden vortex that swept up the 36 Origin Separation Law Chains to suck them in.

An alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he hurriedly began to make hand seals with all six of his hands, doing everything in his power to stabilize the Origin Separation Law Chains.

At the same time, another translucent sword projection shot out of his glabella before piercing into the golden beetle's head in a flash.

The golden beetle wailed in agony once again, and the golden vortex shuddered slightly, but it remained intact and was continuing to suck in the Origin Separation Law Chains.

An urgent look appeared on Han Li's face, yet before he had a chance to do anything else, an azure spirit domain abruptly appeared around the golden beetle before rapidly spreading outward in all directions.

Han Li immediately turned to discover Yohu flying to him.

At the same time, a series of azure law threads emerged around the golden vortex, and there were also around 30 to 40 of them.

The azure law threads flew into the golden vortex in a flash to impede the golden law threads, and the speed of revolution of the golden vortex was instantly significantly slowed.

Yohu then opened his mouth to release a burst of black and azure light, which formed another giant arrow, and it shrieked through the air before piercing into the golden vortex in a flash.

The golden vortex instantly began to bulge before exploding violently, freeing the 36 Origin Separation Law Chains, which instantly burrowed their way into the golden beetle's body.

Chapter 562: Forced Into Retreat

An alarmed look appeared in the golden beetle's eyes, and the golden light around its body was fading at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye before vanishing altogether.

Immediately thereafter, its enormous aura also completely faded, and it began to plummet out of the sky like a dead weight.

The white archway and the giant mountain had already been severely damaged by the golden beetle's resistance, and finally, both of them exploded in the face of the shockwaves resulting from the clash between the two High Zenith Stage Jade Immortals.

The golden beetle was extremely alarmed to discover that its nascent soul had somehow been sealed, rendering it completely unable to draw upon any of its immortal spiritual power.

Yohu could also sense what was happening within the golden beetle's body, and he took a surprised glance at Han Li while sweeping his front paws through the air.

Several black and azure arrow projections instantly emerged before striking the golden beetle in a flash, and upon being struck by the arrows, the golden beetle's fall was drastically accelerated, sending it crashing into the ground to create an enormous crater.

Yohu was just about to give chase when he grimaced in pain, and the azure light emanating from his body quickly faded, immediately followed by his azure spirit domain.

"Father!"

Suliu hurriedly flew over to Yohu to support him while also releasing two bursts of azure light out of the palms of his paws into Yohu's body.

Only then was Yohu's aura somewhat stabilized.

Right at this moment a streak of golden light suddenly erupted out of the giant crater down below, and the golden beetle was flying rapidly into the distance.

The exoskeleton on its back had split open and was functioning as a pair of wings.

Even though its immortal spiritual power had been sealed, it still possessed its physical prowess, and even with just its wings alone, it was still able to fly at an astonishing speed.

"You're not getting away!" Suliu roared as he prepared to set off in pursuit.

"Let it go," Yohu said. "Even though the insect spirit's immortal spiritual power has been sealed, its physical prowess is still tremendous. With your powers, even if you manage to catch up to it, you won't be able to kill it anyway."

Suliu stopped sheepishly in his tracks upon hearing this.

Yohu then turned to look at Han Li, who had also refrained from setting off in pursuit of the golden beetle.

At this point, he had already reverted back to his human form, and his face was quite pale, while blood was trickling down from the corner of his lips.

Even though he had only fought briefly in the battle, he had unleashed virtually all of his trump cards, and he only less than 10% of his immortal spiritual power left.

Even with pills and Immortal Origin Stones to replenish himself, he most likely wouldn't have been able to hold on had the Gold Devouring Immortal just lasted a few more seconds.

"Thank you for your assistance, Fellow Daoist," Yohu said to Han Li.

"You're far too kind. If that insect spirit had come out on top, I would've been in quite a terrible situation," Han Li replied as he wiped the blood from his lips.

Yohu looked at Han Li for a moment longer, then began to fly toward the Dark Star Canyon.

Suliu was just about to follow along when Yohu instructed, "You stay here."

A displeased look appeared on Suliu's face upon hearing this, but he still obliged in the end, and he turned to take a glance at Han Li as he said, "You've got some tricks up your sleeve, kid. Let's have a fight once you're recovered from your injuries."

After that, he flew down toward the battlefield below without waiting for a response.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he promptly swallowed a pill.

In the wake of the golden beetle fleeing the battlefield, the Insect Race army's morale was instantly completely crushed, and Suliu was able to tear through their ranks without equal.

Before long, the Insect Race army had been comprehensively defeated and began to retreat.

......

Deep within the Dark Star Canyon, there was a massive waterfall crashing down between two mountains, producing a vast cloud of water vapor that reflected a dazzling rainbow under the light of the sun.

The waterfall was gushing into an enormous pool, and waves were rippling incessantly over the surface of the water in the pool.

Right at the center of the pool stood a tall and majestic black stone palace, and at this moment, there was a huge lit brazier at the center of the palace, illuminating the entire space.

Around the brazier were a series of large chairs, upon which were seated the chiefs of all of the Beast Race tribes.

The chair that was directly opposite the gate of the stone palace was occupied by none other than Nuo Qinglin, and to his left were Ulu and the others, while the chairs on his right were vacant for now.

Several other Calm Dawn beings were standing behind Nuo Qinglin, one of whom was his daughter, Nuo Yifan.

"Has there been any news from the Azure Boar, Menace Lion, and Night Owl Tribes? When will they be able to get here?" Nuo Qinglin asked with a solemn expression.

One of the older Calm Dawn beings stepped forward and reported, "The Azure Boar Tribe sent word two days ago, stating that they'll be here in three months, while the Menace Lion and Night Owl Tribes will arrive a little later, but they should be here within half a year."

"Send out some Azure Jade Pigeons right away to inform them of what happened today and urge them to get here faster," Nuo Qinglin instructed.

"Yes, Chief," the Calm Dawn being replied, then immediately departed to carry out the order.

Following his departure, the palace fell silent again, and the atmosphere was a little tense.

During the prior battle, the insect spirit had put on an extremely formidable display, and the Beast Race army had also been clearly at a disadvantage against the Insect Race army, so even though they had won the battle, morale was still very low.

"This attack from the Insect Race was very strange in quite a few ways, and it's already quite commendable that we were able to ward them off on such short notice, so don't be too hard on yourselves. Right now, we need to be on our guard in case they suddenly turn around for a second attack. Once all of our tribes are united, it'll be time for us to retaliate!" Nuo Qinglin declared.

It wasn't clear if everyone in the palace had actually been encouraged by his words, but they still all gave affirmative responses.

Following the departure of the other tribal leaders, the chiefs of the Violent Bear Tribe and the Monohorn Tribe remained seated with Nuo Qinglin.

"Where is that human right now?" Ulu asked with a hesitant expression.

"According to the people that I have keeping an eye on him, he's already returned to the cave abode I've arranged for him," Nuo Qinglin replied.

"His performance during the battle was extraordinary! Even our king wasn't able to force back the insect spirit, yet he was able to do it on his own, and I don't think he's even shown us his full power. How about we give him a more detailed map and get him to leave as soon as possible?" the chief of the Monohorn Tribe proposed.

"I'm just worried that it won't be so easy to get him to leave," Ulu mused with a concerned expression.

"I think your concerns are unnecessary. If he truly harbored sinister intentions against our Beast Race, then he wouldn't have faced off against the insect spirit. Instead, he would've taken the opportunity to turn on us. On top of that, I've already instructed my people to keep a close eye on him, and I'll immediately be informed as soon as he does anything," Nuo Qinglin said.

"I certainly hope you're right... I just can't shake the feeling that there's something strange about the attack from the Insect Race. No matter how I look at it, it just doesn't make sense for the Insect Race to launch such a large-scale attack at a time like this," Ulu said.

"If I recall correctly, it sounded like the insect spirit was searching for something..." the chief of the Monohorn Tribe mused.

"I also recall hearing it demanding that we hand something over," Ulu chimed in with furrowed brows.

"This is the territory of our Calm Dawn Tribe! Regardless of what it's looking for, we won't let it get its way!" Nuo Qinglin declared.

"Chief Nuo is right. The honor of our Beast Race is not to be violated! Once all of our tribes are assembled, we must exact vengeance upon the Insect Race!" Ulu declared.

The chief of the Monohorn Tribe didn't say anything, but he also nodded in agreement.

Following the departure of the two chiefs, Nuo Qinglin and Nuo Yifan were the only ones left in the palace.

"Father..."

As soon as Nuo Yifan opened her mouth to speak, Nuo Qinglin immediately raised a hand to stop her.

"I know what you want to say. You feel guilty because we're being so wary of someone who's just saved our Beast Race, right?" Nuo Qinglin asked.

Nuo Yifan nodded in response.

"Humans are even more cunning and vicious than the Insect Race, so I have no choice but to be on my guard," Nuo Qinglin sighed.

"Wasn't Mother also a human? Clearly, there are good people in all races and tribes," Nuo Qinglin argued.

A reminiscent look appeared on Nuo Qinglin's face upon hearing this, and he replied, "Your mother was indeed an exception. Otherwise, I wouldn't have taken her as my wife despite the objections of the entire tribe. However, it was exactly because she was too kind and pure and that she was killed by her own race."

Back when Nuo Yifan was still a child, her mother had been killed by human cultivators. Even though Nuo Qinglin had gone on to avenge her, his hatred for humans had become very deep-rooted in the wake of that incident.

"Don't worry, as long as he doesn't harm the interests of our Beast Race, I won't do anything to him. Instead, once he decides to leave, not only will I give him the maps that I promised, I'll also present him with other gifts to thank him for what he did for us," Nuo Qinglin said in a gentle voice as he gently stroked his daughter's hair, and only then did a faint smile appear on Nuo Yifan's face.

Meanwhile, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed on the stone bed in the inner room of his cave abode, and he was resting with his eyes closed, while his entire body enshrouded within a layer of azure light.

Jin Tong was laying on the bed beside him, looking up at him with her eyes wide open.

Some time later, Han Li exhaled as he slowly opened his eyes, and Jin Tong immediately asked, "How are you feeling, Uncle?"

"I'm alright. I just need to take some pills, then rest for a while longer, and I'll be perfectly fine," Han Li replied.

"That's good to hear," Jin Tong said with a relieved expression.

"How are you feeling? Are you afraid to have such a powerful Gold Devouring Immortal coming after you?" Han Li jibed with a faint smile.

Chapter 563: Secret Plan

"When have I ever been afraid of anyone! That thing is just... a little stronger than I am... Even if I can't eat it for now, I'll definitely be able to cripple it, and if I can't do that... Well, I still have you, don't I?" Jin Tong's voice became quieter and quieter as she spoke, and by the end, it was nothing more than a whimper.

"Right now, I'm definitely no match for it. If Yohu hadn't been on that battlefield, we would've been in a great deal of trouble," Han Li sighed.

"Before we ran into that thing, I only had a vague sense of it, but after being in such close proximity to it,' it's already completely locked onto my aura, so we won't be able to get away from it unless we leave the primordial land altogether," Jin Tong said with a dejected expression.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh and shook his head upon hearing this.

In the face of a Gold Devouring Immortal that was far more powerful than herself, Jin Tong instinctively wanted to devour them, but she also instinctively feared being devoured herself.

Jin Tong tugged on the corner of Han Li's robe in an uneasy manner, hoping to get some reassurance, and Han Li sighed, "We're in a pretty bad situation right now... We haven't received the maps of the primordial land from Chief Nuo yet, so even if we leave this place, we'll just get lost right away, and even if we do receive the maps, there's no way we'll be able to get out of the primordial land in a short time."

"What do we do then?" Jin Tong asked with a concerned expression.

"Even though I was able to temporarily seal that thing's nascent soul, given its powers, it won't be long before it manages to undo the seal. The next time it attacks, even if Yohu and I join forces, we still may not be able to defeat it.

“Prior to that, I have to work harder in my cultivation to see if I can make some more progress, and at the same time, I'll do my best to recover the power of my Mantra Treasured Axis. That way, we should have some chance of victory," Han Li mused with tightly furrowed brows.

"I knew you would have a way, Uncle!" Jin Tong exclaimed as her eyes lit up. "What are our chances of victory?"

"I'd say about 10%," Han Li replied.

Jing Tong's face immediately fell upon hearing this. "That's terrible!"

"Even then, that's a very optimistic estimate. 10% is already quite high," Han Li said with a wry smile.

Jin Tong was silent for a moment, following which a thought suddenly occurred to her as she asked, "Uncle, do you have any other treasures like that cauldron from before? If you could get me a few of those to eat, maybe I'll be able to beat that thing after I take a nap!"

"Those types of treasures are extremely rare. Besides, I didn't even get to examine it before you ate it, so I don't even know what type of treasure it is," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

At this point, Jin Tong was desperate, and she turned to Xiao Bai as she urged, "Xiao Bai, try and sniff out some treasures nearby!"

Xiao Bai merely rolled its eyes in response.

......

Several months later.

In a large palace at the foot of the waterfall in the Dark Star Canyon were dozens of large chairs placed around a bonfire, several of which were currently occupied by foreign beings.

While there weren't many of them present, all of them were chiefs of some of the largest tribes in the entire Beast Race, making them the most powerful figures in the Beast Race with the exception of the true spirits.

"Chief Nuo, you made a decision to summon our king on your own without waiting for all of the tribes to assemble. How are you going to explain yourself?" a purple-skinned man asked as he turned to Nuo Qinglin.

"What explanation do you require from me, Chief Deng Gui? What would you have done if the insect spirit had suddenly stormed onto the territory of your Night Owl Tribe with such a formidable army?" Nuo Qinglin countered.

"Don't pin the blame on Chief Nuo, it was Master Suliu who summoned our king," Ulu chimed in as he took a displeased look at the purple-skinned man.

"Let's not descend into senseless bickering. There's no way the insect spirit will just give up, so we have to devise a plan for retaliation."

This time, it was a white-robed woman with a near-transparent body that had spoken.

Her facial features were quite similar to those of a human, and there were faint azure patterns around her eyes, which were extremely large and shimmering with a peculiar, seductive light.

"Chief Yin Mei is right, let's have a constructive discussion. Chief Nuo, I heard that a human played a major role in forcing the insect spirit into retreat. Is that true?" a man who resembled a humanoid boar with sharp black spikes all over his body asked.

While he had a hideous appearance, he possessed the highest cultivation base out of everyone present, and everyone immediately turned to Nuo Qinglin upon hearing this.

"That's right. He saved my daughter and the Longneck Tribe back on Bright Deer Hill, then escorted them back to the Dark Star Canyon, so I allowed him to stay in the canyon," Nuo Qinglin explained.

"Have you gone senile, Chief Nuo? I can't believe you would accept another human into your ranks," the purple-skinned man sneered.

"I've already issued orders for him to be placed under tight surveillance. All he wants are some maps of the primordial land, and once I've compiled them and given them to him, he'll be on his way," Nuo Qinglin replied in a cold voice.

"How was a mid-Golden Immortal cultivator able to play such a major role in forcing the insect spirit into retreat?" the boar-like man asked with a perplexed expression.

"Have you considered how much of a coincidence it was that the insect spirit attacked right after he came to the Dark Star Canyon? Perhaps they agreed on this plan in advance to put on an act, and once we're all here in the Dark Star Canyon, the insect spirit will return to wipe us all out," Deng Gui speculated as he raised an eyebrow.

His speculation wasn't backed with any evidence, but it immediately sowed a seed of doubt in everyone's hearts, and all of them turned to Nuo Qinglin for an answer.

"He's not just an ordinary mid-Golden Immortal cultivator. He has a spirit pet that possesses the aura of a primordial true spirit, and there are also many types of true spirit bloodlines in his body. Do you think the insect spirit would be willing to work with a human that possesses beastly true spirit bloodlines?" Nuo Qinglin retorted.

"He possesses true spirit bloodlines?" Deng Gui exclaimed with a surprised expression.

"I wouldn't have allowed him to set foot in my Dark Star Canyon otherwise," Nuo Qinglin replied with an indifferent expression.

"What do you think of this, Chief Ze Wushi?" Yin Mei asked as he turned to the boar-like man.

"If he possesses true spirit bloodlines, then there's no way that he could be working with the Insect Race. However, there's no way that we can trust a human. If he can be used, then we'll use him, but if he can't, then we have to make him leave as soon as possible," the boar-like man mused.

Yin Mei nodded as she agreed, "Given his powers and his cultivation base, it would be best not to make an enemy out of him."

"I have no objections," Deng Gui agreed with a shrug.

"In that case..."

"Hold on a second," an elderly voice interjected before Nuo Qinglin had a chance to finish his sentence.

Everyone immediately turned to the chair that was directly facing Ze Wushi's, and an elderly man with a head of white hair and wrinkles all over his face leaned forward slightly before standing up from his chair.

At first glance he appeared to be no different in appearance for a human, but upon closer inspection, one would discover that there were eight or nine fist-sized lion heads growing around his face.

While everyone had been in discussion earlier, he had been leaning back against his chair with his eyes closed, looking as if he had fallen asleep and had only just woken up a moment earlier.

"What do you think, Senior Yin Shen?" Nuo Qinglin asked.

This man was the previous chief of the Menace Lion Tribe, so he was a very senior figure in the Beast Race. He had already passed down his position to his only son so that he could focus on cultivation, but his son was killed during a conflict with some human primordial hunters.

He had immediately stormed out of seclusion in a fit of rage and pursued those human cultivators for millions of kilometers, chasing them all the way to the northern city wall of Primordial Origin City, where he finally slew the final primordial hunter. After that, he had returned with several hundred human heads and piled them all up in front of his son's grave before assuming the role of chief again.

"As I'm sure you're all aware, the insect spirit's physical prowess and regenerative abilities are even superior to those of our king. Not only was our Dark Star Canyon not prepared for this attack, the Insect Race also wasn't able to draw upon all of its power on such short notice.

“Once it makes a recovery and attacks again with the Insect Race army, our king most likely still won't have recovered from his injuries, so how will we be able to stop it?" Yin Shen asked in an expressionless manner.

Everyone fell silent upon hearing this.

"Don't try to build suspense, Chief Yin Shen. If you have a solution, then lay it out for us."

The person who had spoken was a wizened elderly woman with a head of white hair. Her ears were extraordinarily large, and her nose was elongated into a trunk.

She was comparable to Yin Shen when it came to seniority, and she was the chief of the Divine Elephant Tribe.

"Indeed, Senior Yin Shen. Please tell us your plan," Ze Wushi also urged.

"Seeing as that human possesses true spirit bloodlines, I don't think I need to tell all of you how we can maximize his usefulness to us," Yin Shen said as he took a glance at Nuo Qinglin.

Deng Gui's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this. "You're suggesting that we refine the true spirit bloodlines out of his body to speed up the recovery of our king?"

"We can't do that! He may be a human, but he's helped our Beast Race on several occasions, we can't repay his kindness with such atrocities!" Nuo Qinglin immediately exclaimed with tightly furrowed brows.

"Have you forgotten how your wife met her demise, Chief Nuo? You must be insane if you think humans are deserving of any trust or empathy!" Deng Gui scoffed.

"We're weighing up the life of a single human and the existence of our entire race here. Surely you know what choice must be made, Chief Nuo," Ze Wushi said.

"Our king was only able to force back the insect spirit with his help, so there's no way that our king would agree to this," Nuo Qinglin protested.

"That's where you're wrong. I wasn't actually sleeping just now. Instead, I was communicating with our king, and he agreed to this plan," Yin Shen said with a smile.

Nuo Qinglin was silent for a moment, then sighed, "In that case, I have no objections."

"Alright, let's discuss how we're going to trap and kill him..."

Chapter 564: Meeting Between the Eight Spirits

While this discussion was taking place between the tribal leaders, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed on the stone bed in the inner room of his cave abode. His eyes were tightly shut, and there was a layer of azure light swirling around him.

Neither Jin Tong nor Xiao Bai were currently with him, and it was unclear whether they had been stowed away.

He was still completely oblivious to the sinister plot that the Beast Race was hatching against him, and he was wholeheartedly focused on preparing for the battle that was to come.

Compared with his status as a wanted fugitive of the Heavenly Court, this situation was an even more difficult one to contend with, and it could be said that this was the biggest crisis that he had faced since coming to the True Immortal Realm.

By some strokes of luck, he had been able to kill a High Zenith Stage Immortal Envoy of the Heavenly Court, but in this case, he was facing a formidable foe that was far more powerful than even Gongshu Jiu.

Even though the chances of overcoming this ordeal were extremely slim, he naturally wasn't going to just give up.

Time slowly passed by, and after a while, Han Li opened his eyes, while the azure light swirling around him also faded.

He cast an expressionless gaze toward the outer room, then slowly closed his eyes once again.

At the same time, a figure was racing through the sky near the valley that Han Li was staying in, and they arrived on the scene as a streak of azure light before drawing to an abrupt halt in mid-air.

It was none other than the white-robed Nuo Qinglin, and he extended a hand forward as he instructed, "Come with me."

A slender hand reached out of thin air to remove the hood of a cloak, and Nuo Yifan suddenly appeared amid a flash of gray light.

"Father, Senior Li has shown us nothing but kindness, how can we..."

"This is not what I want to see, either, but the decision was arrived at by all of our tribes, and I cannot go against it," Nuo Qinglin interjected before she had a chance to finish.

"But it's the wrong decision! Father, you've always denounced humans as an honorless and treacherous race, but how are we any different from them with what we're doing right now?" Nuo Yifan protested with tightly furrowed brows.

"This is a decision made by our king, what else can I do?" Nuo Qinglin sighed.

A disappointed look appeared on Nuo Yifan's face upon hearing this, and she fell silent as she turned to look at the mountain face in the distance.

At this point, all of the Calm Dawn beings within a radius of several hundred kilometers had already been evacuated, and the entire area had been surrounded by an elite army of several thousand Beast Race warriors, led by dozens of grand elders from various tribes.

All of the chiefs of the eight holy tribes aside from Nuo Qinglin were also all hovering in the sky above the mountain face, staring intently at Han Li's cave abode.

Chief Yin Shen of the Menace Lion Tribe swept a hand through the air, and a small yellow flag appeared in his grasp before he waved it at the dozens of grand elders in the distance.

The grand elders raised the bone staves in their hands in unison upon seeing this, and they also began to chant a strange incantation.

As soon as their incantation rang out, the river that was flowing through the Dark Star Canyon instantly became extremely violent and turbulent, while bursts of azure and purple light emerged from the vines draped over the nearby mountain faces, forming a series of fox head totems.

As these fox heads emerged, the canyon suddenly began to turn dark, and before long, it was as if day had transitioned into night.

At the same time, specks of starlight rose up from all directions, forming a radiant river of starlight that descended straight down from the night sky, filling the entire canyon with a strange and profound power.

As the chanting from the grand elders continued, all of the thousands of elite Beast Race warriors began performing what appeared to be a ceremonial dance.

Before long, streaks of light had converged to form a massive restrictive array around the mountain face, completely surrounding the entire mountain face and the cave abode upon it.

"Please come out, Fellow Daoist Li. The tribes of our Beast Race have something to discuss with you," Yin Shen declared in a thunderous voice, and his voice was echoing incessantly within the canyon.

There was no response.

"Please come out to see us, Fellow Daoist Li," Yin Shen repeated.

He could clearly sense that Han Li's aura was still in the cave abode, so he wasn't worried that Han Li had snuck away.

Many of the Beast Race warriors present had witnessed Han Li's battle against the insect spirit, so even though they didn't want to admit it, deep down, they were quite fearful of Han Li.

Not only was that the case for them, even the likes of Ulu and Nuo Qinglin were extremely wary of him, but they had no choice but to do this for the survival of their race.

After calling out for a third time, all of the Beast Race warriors present finally began to develop a sense that something wasn't quite right.

"Is there something wrong?" Ulu asked with tightly furrowed brows, while the other chiefs were just as perplexed.

"He's just playing mind games with us. I'll force him to come out!" Deng Gui of the Night Owl Tribe harrumphed coldly, then swooped down toward the mountain face like a bird of prey.

However, before he was able to descend upon the cave abode, a resounding boom suddenly rang out from the mountain face, and the cave abode abruptly exploded violently, sending powerful shockwaves sweeping through the air in all directions.

Deng Gui's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly flew back in retreat, hovering in mid-air a safe distance away from the mountain face.

All of the other Beast Race warriors also began staring at the mountain face with apprehensive looks on their faces.

From the wreckage of the cave abode emerged an azure-robed man, who looked up at the Beast Race chiefs with a calm and composed expression.

Aside from a few of the chiefs present, none of them dared to meet his gaze. It was as if the proud Beast Race had lowered its head in the face of a human.

Among these few chiefs were Yin Shen, Nuo Qinglin, and the chief of the Divine Elephant Tribe.

At this moment, Nuo Qinglin was looking at Han Li with a complex combination of sympathy, apology, and resignation in his eyes.

Meanwhile, Han Li remained silent and composed, and he refrained from releasing his mid-Golden Immortal Stage aura. Even so, there was still a sense of immense pressure emanating from his body, and all of the Beast Race warriors were becoming more and more uneasy by the second.

The entire area had descended into a strange silence, but right at this moment, Yin Shen roared, "Attack!"

As soon as this order was issued, all of the grand elders immediately began waving their bone staves through the air while chanting an incantation, and blood began to flow out of the palms of their hand before trickling down onto their bone staves, staining them a bright red.

At the same time, a giant true spirit projection began to emerge above the array that surrounded the entire mountain face, and it was gradually taking on a more and more substantial appearance.

Bursts of tremendous pressure also came crashing down from the sky, striking all of the Beast Race warriors present with a sense of asphyxiation.

Before long, the first true spirit descended upon the mountain face. It was none other than the armor-clad six-tailed fox, Suliu.

Immediately after him came a giant rhinoceros the size of a mountain and a huge falcon with feathers that resembled dark metal.

Bursts of tremendous energy fluctuations surged through the air as all eight of the true spirits revered by the Beast Race emerged one after another, and all of them were glowering at the azure-robed man down below.

Even in the face of the eight true spirits, Han Li continued to stand in silence with his hands clasped behind his back.

Suliu stared at Han Li for a moment longer, following which his brows suddenly furrowed slightly, and he swooped down from above with tremendous force before swinging one of his tails at Han Li.

A resounding boom rang out as the entire mountain face collapsed, and Han Li was buried beneath the rubble.

Everyone else was quite dumbfounded to see this, unable to comprehend what they were witnessing.

"You idiots! He's already run away long ago!" Suliu exclaimed as he turned to all of the tribal leaders present with a furious expression.

As he lifted his tail, Han Li was nowhere to be seen. Instead, all that remained in his place was a dark yellow bean and an azure horse mask, both of which were glowing faintly amid the wreckage.

Shortly thereafter, the bean fell dark after exhausting the final hint of spiritual energy within it.

Nuo Qinglin arrived on the scene, and Yin Shen turned to him as he asked, "How did this happen? How was that human tipped off in advance?"

A hint of fury welled up in Nuo Qinglin's heart at Yin Shen's accusatory tone, and he asked in a furious voice, "How would I know? Are you suspecting me?"

"I heard that your daughter was quite close with that human..." Deng Gui mused in a suggestive manner.

"Shut your mouth!" Nuo Qinglin snapped. "Yifan has been sealed in her room ever since we decided on this plan!"

Suliu also turned to Deng Gui with a menacing expression as he asked, "What did you say about Yifan?"

Deng Gui immediately lowered his head upon hearing this, not daring to say anything further.

Suliu wasn't particularly powerful among all of the true spirits worshiped by the Beast Race, but he was the son of the king of the true spirits, Yohu, so it was certainly not a good idea for anyone in the Beast Race to get on his bad side.

Ulu and Marlon exchanged a glance with each other, and each of them could see their own schadenfreude mirrored in one another's eyes. Everyone knew that Suliu was extremely fond of Yifan, yet it seemed that Deng Gui had a death wish.

One of the main reasons why the Calm Dawn Tribe was one of the eight holy tribes was because the true spirit that they worshiped was Suliu, and the other important factor was how fond Suliu was of Nuo Yifan.

The black hawk was the true spirit revered by the Night Owl Tribe, and it also gave Deng Gui a cold, reprimanding glare. Sweat immediately began to bead up on Deng Gui's forehead as he fell into a fearful silence.

Chapter 565: Venturing Deep Into the Primordial Land

"Don't go around blaming women all the time for your own incompetence," Suliu scoffed, then gradually faded away into nothingness.

As for the other true spirits, they chatted briefly with one another, then departed as well.

In the sky above the rubble that used to be the mountain face, the members of the eight holy tribes were all looking on with tightly furrowed brows.

Several thousand feet away, Nuo Yifan was also observing what was happening in the distance while concealed in her gray cloak, and she was very relieved by what she saw.

......

On a lone peak that was tens of thousands of kilometers away from the Dark Star Canyon, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed under an enormous tree. His eyes were closed, and his entire body was enshrouded within a layer of golden light.

Right at this moment, his eyes suddenly sprang open as a mocking sneer appeared on his face.

"Why are you smiling like that, Uncle?" Jin Tong asked with a perplexed expression.

"The Beast Race has decided to attack me," Han Li replied.

A hint of disappointment appeared on Jin Tong's face upon hearing this, and she turned with tightly furrowed brows to face Xiao Bai, who was grinning from ear to ear.

In the face of Jin Tong's cold glare, Xiao Bai hurriedly wiped the smile from its own face as it said in a careful manner, "I win the bet this time, so..."

Jin Tong harrumphed coldly as she raised a hand to toss a crystal that was brimming with spiritual qi toward Xiao Bai.

"These Beast Race bastards are nothing more than a bunch of ungrateful dogs!" she cursed in a furious voice, making sure to put heavy emphasis on the words "ungrateful dogs", and Xiao Bai was just about to swallow the crystal, but he almost choked on it upon hearing this.

All of a sudden, it was beginning to regret making a bet against Jin Tong on whether the Beast Race would target Han Li.

"I possess several true spirit bloodlines, and I'm accompanied by a Pixiu that's yet to reach full maturity, both of which will be immensely beneficial for their king's recovery. On top of that, they resent humans no less than they do the Insect Race, so it would've been very unwise to stay there," Han Li said with a smile.

"Your wisdom and foresight are truly astounding!" Xiao Bai praised after swallowing the crystal.

"Since when did you become such a suck-up, Xiao Bai?" Jin Tong asked as she raised an eyebrow.

"Ever since I began following Master, my life has really taken a turn for the better. Not only do I have treasures to eat every day, I also get to enjoy the protection of someone as brave and powerful as yourself! This is something that I wouldn't even have dared to imagine in the past," Xiao Bai replied while putting on an earnest facade.

Jin Tong was very satisfied with this response, and she nodded with a pleased expression. "I can definitely agree with that!"

"By the way, that substitution method that you used was incredible, Master! With that Dao Warrior dressed in your clothes and disguised with that mask, as well as the substitution talisman in its body, it would've been enough to fool anyone!" Xiao Bai praised.

"Alright, stop trying to flatter me. Now that we've left the Beast Race, we'll no longer be able to use their true spirits to deal with that Gold Devouring Immortal, so we're in an even worse situation than before," Han Li said as he rose to his feet.

"Uncle, I can sense that that thing is slowly recovering its power," Jin Tong said in a concerned voice.

"I didn't refine the Origin Separation Law Chains myself, so I definitely wouldn't have been able to use them as effectively as Feng Tiandu. On top of that, given how powerful the Gold Devouring Immortal is, we can't expect the chains to seal it for long, so I'm sure it'll come after us again before too long," Han Li sighed.

"What should we do then?" Jin Tong hurriedly asked in an urgent voice.

"At this point, we've already received some maps of the Beast Race's territory, so we'll just have to take things one step at a time. If we can buy enough time for me to recover all of my Time Dao Runes, then we'll have some chances of taking it by surprise and severely wounding it before fleeing the primordial land," Han Li replied.

Jin Tong nodded in response, then asked, "Where do we go now?"

Han Li didn't immediately reply. Instead, he flipped a hand over to produce a map, then examined it for a moment before musing, "According to the map, the area inhabited by the Beast Race and the Insect Race is still only on the outskirts of the primordial land, so we'll be getting deeper into the primordial land if we travel southward. In any case, let's get out of this area as quickly as possible."

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air to summon the green jade flying carriage, and after the three of them had all flown onto the carriage, it set off as a streak of green light.

Close to half a day later.

Han Li was standing at the front of the carriage, and immortal spiritual power was flowing incessantly into the carriage from the bottom of his feet to support its flight.

The spiritual patterns on the flying carriage were flashing incessantly, releasing strands of green spiritual light that formed a light barrier around the carriage.

The carriage was flying so quickly that the surrounding scenery had become very blurry and impossible to discern, but at this moment, Han Li's brows remained tightly furrowed.

While the carriage was flying at an incredible speed, he knew that this was far from its limit. In fact, he had most likely only unleashed 20% to 30% of its power. The former owner of this treasure was a High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal, so it only made sense that a mid-Golden Immortal cultivator like him wouldn't be able to unleash its full power.

This level of speed was sufficient for normal purposes, but it was rather lacking given the current circumstances.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he raised a hand to summon Daoist Xie amid a flash of golden lightning.

"Pilot the carriage for me," Han Li instructed, then took a few steps backward before sitting down.

Daoist Xie's immortal spiritual power was far inferior to Han Li's, and after it took over from him, the spiritual light radiating from the carriage instantly dimmed a little, while its speed was also noticeably reduced.

Han Li paid no heed to this as he flipped a hand over to summon his Dragon 5 mask before putting it on, then conjured up a crimson light screen in front of himself.

Aside from the additional Earthly List included on the crimson light screen, it was no different from the screens of light conjured up using other Transient Guild masks.

From there, Han Li released a mission, searching for a way for Golden Immortal cultivators to use High Zenith Stage immortal treasures, and he was offering quite a handsome reward.

After that, he turned his gaze to the exchange section on the light screen before carefully combing through it.

Moments later, a stack of yellow array tools, a white umbrella immortal treasure, and a green jade lock appeared on the ground beside him, all of which were giving off formidable spiritual power fluctuations.

Jin Tong's eyes immediately lit up at the sight of these treasures, but it was clear that they were useful to Han Li, so she could only suppress her own desires and wrench her gaze away from the treasures.

Close to a day quickly flew by.

The crimson light screen rippled momentarily before fading away, following which Han Li removed his mask before stowing it away.

Jin Tong immediately approached him while riding atop Xiao Bai, then asked with a curious expression, "You spent a lot of Immortal Origin Stones, Uncle! What did you end up buying?"

"Those things are all useful to me, so I can't let you eat them," Han Li replied as he swept a sleeve through the air, stowing away all of the items laid out on the ground in front of him.

A displeased pout appeared on Jin Tong's face.

"Can you sense anything from that Gold Devouring Immortal?" Han Li asked.

A grim look immediately appeared in Jin Tong's eyes as she replied, "It seems to be recovering its power at a faster rate than before, but the good news is that it still hasn't come after us yet."

"How long can you stay in Xiao Bai's stomach for?" Han Li asked with a solemn expression.

"There's a special type of power in the internal space in Xiao Bai's stomach, and even though it can't digest my body, it does affect my soul, so I can only stay in there for an hour at a time at most before having to come back out," Jin Tong replied as she patted Xiao Bai on the head.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

While inside Xiao Bai's internal space, Jin Tong was able to escape the detection of the Gold Devouring Immortal, and that was very useful, but an hour was simply too short a timeframe to make a substantial difference.

Essentially, this meant that the Gold Devouring Immortal would be able to lock onto them once every hour.

"Is there any way for you to extend the duration that Jin Tong can remain in your body?" Han Li asked as he turned to Xiao Bai.

"My internal space is an innate ability of our Pixiu Tribe, but unfortunately, I still haven't reached full maturity yet, so I'm unable to completely control everything within this space. An hour is already the best that I can do. If we want to extend that duration, then we'll have to think of something else," Xiao Bai replied with a shake of its head.

"In that case, as long as we can fortify your soul, you should be able to stay longer in Xiao Bai's body. That's something that's easily achievable," Han Li said as he summoned his Reincarnation Palace mask before putting it on again, and the crimson light screen was conjured up a second time.

He turned to the exchange section once again, and after some searching, he quickly spotted what he was looking for.

"Soul Armor Talisman? What's that?" Jin Tong asked with a curious expression.

"Give it a try, it might be useful for you," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

In order to deal with the backlash from the Spirit Refinement Technique, Han Li had searched extensively for items that had effects on one's soul, and during his search, he had seen these Soul Armor Talismans.

As the name suggested, this was a special talisman that could enhance the defenses of the soul. It was very effective, but also extremely expensive, costing 500 Immortal Origin Stones per talisman, and each one could only last a short time.

Han Li immediately purchased one such talisman, and it quickly emerged before him in a teleportation array amid a flash of white light.

There were some cloud designs etched onto the talisman's surface, and it was giving off a peculiar aura alongside a burst of formidable spiritual power fluctuations.

Chapter 566: The Third Option

"Jin Tong, give this a try to see if you can stay in Xiao Bai's body for a bit longer," Han Li said as he handed the talisman to Jin Tong.

Jin Tong accepted the talisman before adhering it to her own body, and it immediately vanished into her body as a ball of gentle white light.

A series of radiant white spirit patterns then appeared on her forehead, forming the same cloud-like designs that had been on the talisman.

A peculiar look appeared on Jin Tong's face, following which she instructed Xiao Bai to open its mouth before flying toward it as a streak of golden light.

Xiao Bai hurriedly obliged, swallowing the streak of golden light.

An hour quickly flew by, but Jin Tong still hadn't come out, and Xiao Bai was growing a little anxious, pacing around the carriage in a concerned fashion.

Han Li was very encouraged to see this, and he continued to wait.

Another hour passed by before Xiao Bai's expression suddenly changed slightly, and it opened its mouth, upon which Jin Tong flew out as a streak of golden light.

The white spirit patterns on her forehead had already vanished, and her complexion was looking a little pale.

Han Li didn't immediately ask how she felt. Instead, he flipped a hand over to produce a green jade ruler before handing it to her.

Jin Tong immediately grabbed onto the ruler, then quickly crunched it down in just a few bites as if she were eating a stick of hard candy.

After that, a layer of azure light emerged over her face before quickly fading away, but her complexion was left looking a little better.

"How did it go?" Han Li asked.

"The talisman worked, Uncle! Before I had the talisman, I always felt really drowzy while inside Xiao Bai's stomach, but the talisman made me feel a lot better," Jin Tong replied with a smile.

"How much longer do you think you'll be able to stay in there if you had enough of these talismans at your disposal?" Han Li asked.

"Even with enough talismans, I feel like I'll only be able to stay another hour in there at most," Jin Tong replied.

Han Li gave a contemplative nod upon hearing this.

It seemed that even with these Soul Armor Talismans enhancing her soul, she couldn't stay in Xiao Bai's stomach for very long. At the very most, she would only be able to stay in there for three hours at a time at the cost of two of these talismans.

This wasn't a very long time, but it was already far better than before.

With that in mind, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to produce several more spirit treasures for Jin Tong to eat, then returned to the exchange section in the Reincarnation Palace interface to purchase over 100 Soul Armor Talismans.

This was a dire situation, so he wasn't being stingy with his Immortal Origin Stones at all.

Right as he was about to withdraw the crimson light barrier, an elated look suddenly appeared on his face.

As it turned out, someone had already responded to the mission that he had just released.

He immediately cast an incantation seal onto the light screen, and a burst of red light emerged from within, then transformed into a blurry red figure with indistinguishable facial features.

However, the words "Phoenix 19" could be clearly seen etched on the figure's mask.

"Given that you've responded to this mission, I presume you must have a way for Golden Immortals to use High Zenith Stage immortal treasures, right, Fellow Daoist?" Han Li said, wasting no time with small talk.

"Before I answer that question, I want to ask what type of immortal treasure you wish to use," Phoenix 19 replied.

The voice sounded like it belonged to a man, but it was surprisingly a little high-pitched.

"A flying immortal treasure," Han Li repiled.

"I see. Generally speaking, the immortal spiritual power requirements of flying immortal treasures aren't very high, so this will be a relatively easy case. Having said that, I'll need you to tell me about the restrictions in the treasure," Phoenix 19 said.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but he offered no response.

"Are you under the impression that I'm trying to glean the secrets of your immortal treasure? The problem is that if I'm not aware of the restrictions in the flying treasure, then I can't decide on the best way to use it," Phoenix 19 said.

Han Li continued to stare at Phoenix 19 in silence.

The flying carriage had once belonged to Gongshu Jiu, and the Heavenly Court had members all over the entire True Immortal Realm, so he had to be extremely careful not to expose himself as Gongshu Jiu's killer.

However, Phoenix 19 was also telling the truth.

After some contemplation, Han Li ultimately decided to give Phoenix 19 a rough description fo the restrictions in the flying carriage.

After hearing what Han Li had to say, Phoenix 19 replied, "You've found yourself a truly exceptional flying treasure, Fellow Daoist! The restrictions used are quite advanced, but thankfully, they're right in my wheelhouse. There are three ways that can allow you to tap into over 80% of the carriage's power, but each of them have their own pros and cons."

Han Li was quite encouraged to hear this, and he urged, "Please enlighten me, Fellow Daoist."

"Well... All three of those methods are closely guarded secrets, and the compensation you're offering is a little insufficient," Phoenix 19 chuckled.

"Rest assured, if the methods that you lay out are truly effective, then I'm happy to compensate you accordingly, but if you're only bluffing..."

Han Li's voice trailed off there, but the implications were very apparent.

Phoenix 19 seemed to have been slightly irked by Han Li's skepticism, and they said in a cold voice, "Don't look down on me, Fellow Daoist! All of my methods are secret techniques passed down from Hundred Creations Mountain, so you can rest assured of their efficacy!"

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing the term "Hundred Creations Mountain".

This was something that he had heard the Stemborer Queen mention while back in the Spirit Realm. It was a sect in the Immortal Realm, and the Hundred Meridian Refinement Mantra that he had cultivated in the past was also a secret technique from Hundred Creations Mountain. [1]

Judging from what Phoenix 19 had just said, it seemed like this Hundred Creations Mountain was no ordinary sect.

Phoenix 19 seemed to have realized that he had lost his composure a little, and he cleared his throat before continuing, "These are the three methods and the compensation that I require. As for exactly which one you choose, that'll be up to you."

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air to release three specks of light, which swelled to form three light screens in mid-air, all of which were filled with tiny text.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the first light screen to discover that it contained a special secret technique that could forcibly stimulate the spiritual power within the flying carriage to make up for the subpar immortal spirit power of a Golden Immortal, and this method could tap into over 90% of the carriage's power.

At the end, a price tag of 5,000 Immortal Origin Stones was displayed.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he turned his gaze to the next light screen.

According to the first light screen, the enclosed method didn't require much preparation, and it could be used as long as one knew the secret technique, but it was very harmful to the flying carriage, and it wouldn't take long before the carriage's spiritual power was completely exhausted.

This would be a suitable method to use on a short-term basis, but he was going to have to rely on the flying carriage on this entire journey through the primordial land, so it clearly wasn't going to work.

As Han Li read through the content of the second light barrier, his eyes began to light up a little.

The second light screen contained an alternative secret technique that could temporarily fuse the immortal spiritual power of several Golden Immortals into one to reach the High Zenith Stage, and this was also the most effective of the three methods, able to tap into virtually all of the flying carriage's power.

The price tag for this method was 10,000 Immortal Origin Stones.

However, Han Li quickly realized that this was a unfeasible method, not because of the steep price, but instead because the minimum personnel requirement to unleash this secret technique was a lineup of at least three late-Golden Immortal cultivators or at least eight mid-Golden Immortal cultivators.

The lineup of Han Li, Daoist Xie, Xiao Bai, and Jin Tong was still far from reaching this minimum requirement, by his estimates, they would only be able to tap into around 60% of the carriage's power using this secret technique, which was an improvement, for sure, but still far from ideal.

With that in mind, Han Li heard an internal sigh before turning his attention to the third light screen, which laid out an array-based secret technique that was similar in principle to the second method, also involving combining multiple sources of immortal spiritual power into one to elevate the combined immortal spiritual power to the High Zenith Stage.

However, this array drew upon the immortal spiritual power of the Immortal Origin Stones rather than cultivators, and as long as one had sufficient Immortal Origin Stones, they could theoretically tap into the flying carriage's full power.

Of course, the number of Immortal Origin Stones required to sustain High Zenith Stage immortal spiritual power was downright astronomical, and it was far too steep a price for most Golden Immortals.

Perhaps it was because of this that the third method only had a price tag of 1,000 Immortal Origin Stones. It was clear that Phoenix 19 didn't recommend this method, and he had only included it to highlight the first two methods as superior options.

"Have you made your decision yet, Fellow Daoist?" Phoenix 19 asked.

"I have. I'll take the third method," Han Li replied.

Phoenix 19 was very much taken aback to hear this.

The third method was the cheapest of the three, but its flaws were very apparent. It seemed to Phoenix 19 that Han Li was quite a prudent character, so it was very surprising to him that Han Li had chosen this method.

"Are you sure, Fellow Daoist?" Phoenix 19 asked.

"I am," Han Li replied with a nod.

Phoenix 19 didn't ask any further questions, and the exchange quickly took place.

Moments later, a white jade slip emerged from the teleportation array at the center of the crimson light screen.

Han Li immediately grabbed the jade slip before injecting his spiritual sense into it, and only after a full hour had passed did he withdraw his spiritual sense, upon which a hint of admiration appeared on his face.

The secret technique laid out in the jade slip was definitely a viable one, and it was also perfectly catered to Han Li's flying carriage, indicating that it had been modified by Phoenix 19 to suit this particular case.

The fact that he was able to do this in such a short time indicated that his expertise in this field far exceeded Han Li's.

With that in mind, Han Li made sure to keep a mental note of Phoenix 19's name so that he could seek him out if he had encountered any other problems in this field in the future.

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a bunch of materials required to set up the array before getting to work.

[1]. For more information on the Hundred Meridian Refinement Mantra, please refer to RMJI Chapter 1351: Hundred Meridian Refinement Mantra.

[Back]

Chapter 567: Pursuit

Han Li busied himself for three days and three nights, constructing a hexagonal array at the center of the flying carriage.

The array wasn't overly complex, but all of the lines and runes intertwining with one another on its surface were still enough to strike the beholder with a sense of disorientation.

On each node of the hexagonal array was a hole about the same thickness of a thumb, and there were dozens of these holes littered throughout the entire array.

Han Li swept his gaze over the array momentarily, then took a deep breath before pulling out a series of Immortal Origin Stones and slotting them into these holes.

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air to release an incantation seal, and the entire array instantly lit up amid a faint buzzing sound.

The Immortal Origin Stones embedded into the array began to tremble slightly while releasing bursts of spiritual light, which flowed through the lines on the array like blood before converging to a connective point at the center of the array.

A ball of radiant white light that was giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations emerged over that point on the array, and these spiritual power fluctuations were at the High Zenith Stage!

Han Li finally heaved a sigh of relief upon seeing this.

The array fully lived up to the description that Phoenix 19 had provided, and it was worth all of the resources and effort that he had poured into it. However, as expected, it was burning through immortal spiritual power at an extraordinary rate, and Han Li could sense the immortal spiritual power in the Immortal Origin Stones in the array rapidly seeping away.

It was clear that this set of several dozen Immortal Origin Stones wasn't going to be able to last very long.

Unfortunately, there were no other feasible options available to Han Li, and he stowed Daoist Xie away before chanting an incantation while making a hand seal.

The ball of white light at the center of the array instantly began to elongate, transforming into a pillar of white light that infused itself into the flying carriage.

The spirit patterns on the flying carriage immediately began to glow several times more radiantly than they had back when Han Li was piloting the carriage, and the green light barrier around the carriage also began to churn violently before transforming into a radiant green cloud.

The speed of the flying carriage was enhanced by severalfold, and it lurched forward at a terrifying speed while trembling uncontrollably.

This was because the flying carriage was traveling so quickly that Han Li was no longer able to fully control it.

The abrupt onset of turbulence gave both Jin Tong and Xiao Bai a huge fright, and they were snapped awake from their naps before hurriedly stabilizing themselves for fear of being thrown off the carriage.

Han Li wore a solemn expression as he made a rapid string of hand seals, doing everything in his power to control the flying carriage.

As time slowly passed, he gradually grew accustomed to the carriage's newfound speed, and only then did he relax a little.

The speed of the flying carriage had instilled him with some confidence that they would be able to escape from the Gold Devouring Immortal that was pursuing them.

"Jin Tong, from now on, stay in Xiao Bai's stomach as much as possible to minimize the duration that the Gold Devouring Beetle can detect you. As for the Soul Armor Talismans, save those for when we encounter some real danger," Han Li instructed.

Jin Tong was aware of the gravity of the situation, so she obediently obliged without raising a fuss, flying into Xiao Bai's mouth as a streak of golden light.

Meanwhile, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed, piloting the flying carriage with a contemplative look on his face.

Even though Jin Tong now had the resources to remain in Xiao Bai's stomach for a longer duration of time, and the flying carriage's speed had also been greatly enhanced, he was still feeling very concerned at the prospect of having to face a late-High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal.

The only way he could ensure that they would be able to survive this ordeal would be if he could also become a Jade Immortal, but that was clearly impossible.

Even though he had a huge supply of all types of pills, it was virtually impossible to even reach the late-Golden Immortal Stage in a short time, let alone the High Zenith Stage.

With that in mind, Han Li's brows became tightly furrowed with concern.

However, a thought then suddenly occurred to him, and he flipped a hand over to produce a green gourd amid a flash of green light. It was the Profound Heavenly Treasure that he had taken from Qu Ling.

After leaving the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, he had constantly been busy with various affairs, and he had almost forgotten about this treasure.

He looked at the green gourd in his hand for a moment, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a series of streaks of azure light, which revealed themselves to be a set of array flags that landed near Xiao Bai.

An azure light barrier then abruptly appeared, encompassing the startled Xiao Bai within it.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li raised his hand, and the green gourd immediately rose up to hover in mid-air while giving off bursts of gentle green light.

Han Li injected his spiritual sense into the green space within the gourd, and it was no different from how it had been in the past.

The green space was still filled with green light that was slowly revolving to form a massive green vortex, at the center of which was a small azure sword and a miniature three-story pavilion.

These were the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword and the pavilion immortal treasure that he had placed in the gourd to test out its powers.

At this moment, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword in the vortex was releasing waves of gentle azure light, and the enormous spiritual power within it had become far purer and more restrained, as was the case with the miniature pavilion treasure.

Some time later, Han Li withdrew his spiritual sense from the gourd as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

Given how the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword and the pavilion treasure were both still unharmed after spending so much time in the gourd, it was clear that immortal treasures could be stored in the gourd without any problems.

With that in mind, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, summoning three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords while pointing a finger at the gourd.

A burst of green light flashed over the surface of the gourd, and it released a streak of green light out of its opening to sweep up the three flying swords before sucking them in.

He repeated this process over and over again, sending his other Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords into the gourd in batches, then placed the gourd down onto the ground in front of him.

Enhancing his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords wasn't actually the primary reason behind why he had summoned the gourd.

As a Profound Heavenly Treasure, this gourd was one of his most precious treasures, second only to his Heaven Controlling Vial.

Even though it didn't seem to be an offensive Profound Heavenly Treasure, it would surely still be a great help against the Gold Devouring Immortal if he could fully refine it.

With that in mind, Han Li turned his gaze to the opening of the gourd to discover that the coloration of the gourd there was slightly lighter than it was elsewhere, indicating that it had been picked prior to reaching full maturity.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he pulled out his Heaven Controlling Vial, and there was a drop of faintly glowing green liquid rolling around inside.

Han Li gently tipped the vial forward, and the drop of green liquid immediately flowed onto the opening of the gourd where the lighter coloration was.

In the next instant, the green light radiating from the gourd abruptly brightened by severalfold, and countless green runes emerged within the light before dancing and churning violently like boiling water.

A burst of formidable law power fluctuations erupted out of the gourd before spreading outward, and the nearby world's origin qi was also stirred up into a frenzy, forming balls of spiritual light of different colors.

At the moment, the flying carriage was still racing along, and these balls of spiritual light were instantly left behind, forming a dazzling wave of rainbow light behind the carriage.

Han Li paid no heed to this as he stared intently at the gourd.

The drop of green liquid quivered momentarily on the surface of the gourd, then slowly seeped into it, following which the churning runes around the gourd slowly subsided.

He carefully inspected the gourd to find that its outward appearance hadn't changed at all, nor had any changes taken place within its internal space.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he wasn't overly disheartened.

Back when he infused his Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword with the green spirit liquid, it had taken a very long time for the effects to manifest themselves, so he had to be patient.

With that in mind, Han Li rose to his feet and made his way over to a corner of the flying carriage, where he set up a miniature array before placing the Heaven Controlling Vial into it.

After that, he returned to his original spot and sat back down, then opened his mouth to release a burst of azure light, which swept up the green gourd before sucking it back into his body.

A month passed by in a flash.

Under the starry night sky, the green flying carriage was racing along like a green shooting star, continuing to travel at an extraordinary speed.

Down below was a vast mountain range, and at this point, they were already far away from the Dark Star Canyon.

Han Li was currently looking down at the mountain range below with tightly furrowed brows.

Over the past month, he had constantly been keeping tabs on the High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal through Jin Tong, and according to Jin Tong, it had been rapidly recovering its power of late, indicating that it had most likely already freed itself from the Origin Separation Law Chains.

Han Li took a glance up at the sky, then strode over the corner of the flying carriage before picking up the Heaven Controlling Vial and dripping the drop of green liquid inside onto the green gourd.

The green gourd began to glow brightly once again while releasing bursts of formidable law power fluctuations, but just like last time, the gourd returned to normal shortly thereafter.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, and he was jut about to set the Heaven Controlling Vial down onto its original spot when he suddenly raised an eyebrow, then stowed the vial away before rushing over to Xiao Bai.

There was a concerned look on Xiao Bai's face as it said, "Master, Jin Tong says..."

"Is it coming after us?" Han Li asked in a grim voice.

"Yes. According to Jin Tong, it's coming after us at an even faster speed than our carriage is currently traveling at," Xiao Bai replied.

"Faster by how much?" Han Li asked.

Xiao Bai was silent for a moment, then replied with a fearful expression, "About twice as fast..."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he flipped a hand over to produce the Soul Armor Talismans that he had purchased earlier, then tossed all of them into Xiao Bai's mouth as he instructed, "Jin Tong, stay in there for as long as you can."

After that, he turned and began casting a string of incantation seals into the flying carriage and the hexagonal array on the ground.

The flying carriage immediately began to glow even brighter as it abruptly swiveled around and set off in a different direction.

Chapter 568: Life on the Run

Meanwhile.

Countless kilometers behind Han Li, a ball of radiant golden light that was around an acre in size was racing through the air at an extraordinary speed amid a deafening rumbling noise.

Encompassed within the ball of golden light was an enormous golden beetle that was flapping its wings with all its might.

This was none other than the High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal, and at this moment, there was a hint of surprise on its face.

It could sense that its target was only at the Golden Immortal Stage, but they were extremely fast. Granted, it was still faster, but its target was somehow traveling at speeds superior even to what the average High Zenith Stage true spirit was capable of reaching.

Immediately thereafter, it stopped cold in its tracks as a perplexed look appeared on its face.

All of a sudden, it was no longer able to sense its target anymore!

This was the exact same thing that had happened last time back at the Dark Star Canyon, and while it had been recovering from its injuries, there were also several occasions where its target's aura had disappeared, just like what had happened just now.

After a brief moment of contemplation, it continued to travel in the same direction as before.

Around three hours later, its target's aura reappeared, but this time, it was in another direction, and it was quite a bit further away.

The High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal gave a cold harrumph upon sensing this, but it wasn't overly concerned as it turned to set off in that direction.

......

In the sky above a mountain range, the green flying carriage was racing along.

Jin Tong seemed to have just come out of Xiao Bai's body, and her complexion was quite pale, while her breathing was also a little ragged. As for Xiao Bai, it was hanging its head in a glum fashion.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of Jin Tong's terrible condition, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a pile of spirit treasures, all of which seemed to be of quite a high caliber.

Jin Tong sat down on the flying carriage in silence, then picked up a spirit treasure before stuffing it into her mouth.

Xiao Bai really wanted to join in on the feast as well, but it knew that Jin Tong needed the sustenance more than right now, so it suppressed its appetite and laid down onto the carriage.

Right at this moment, a golden storage ring fell onto the ground in front of it, and Han Li's voice rang out beside its ears.

"Xiao Bai, you have something to eat as well."

"Thank you, Master!" Xiao Bai immediately rose up onto its haunches before gulping down the storage bracelet, while Han Li sat down with his legs crossed once again to focus on piloting the carriage.

Now that Jin Tong was no longer concealed, he didn't bother to change directions and merely continued onward at full speed.

Over two hours later, Jin Tong rose to her feet and her complexion had already completely recovered at this point.

Han Li immediately instructed Jin Tong to hide in Xiao Bai's stomach once again before changing directions a second time.

The High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal was furious to discover that its target's aura had disappeared again.

Whenever this happened, its target would be able to open up some distance between them, and that was naturally very frustrating to the Gold Devouring Immortal, but it had no choice but to keep going.

Three hours later, Jin Tong's aura reappeared, and sure enough, she had changed directions and was once again very far away, ensuring that she was constantly out of reach.

However, the Gold Devouring Immortal had already calmed down at this point.

It had become apparent to it that its target was somehow able to periodically conceal their aura at set intervals, but as long as its target couldn't do this for extended periods of time, they would never be able to get out of its sensory range.

Sure enough, over the next few months, the Gold Devouring Immortal was still unable to catch its target, but nor was its target able to shake it off their trail.

Just like before, its target's aura would periodically disappear, and by the time it re-emerged, it would be in another direction, quite far away.

As a result, even though the Gold Devouring Immortal was far faster than its target, it was being led on a wild goose chase, rendering it completely passive, which was naturally very infuriating, but there wasn't anything that it could do.

......

The green flying carriage was racing through the sky above a lush forest, and Han Li was looking a little more relaxed as he piloted the carriage.

As long as he could maintain the status quo, the Gold Devouring Immortal wouldn't be able to catch them. Even though this was very taxing on his Immortal Origin Stone reserves, fortunately, he was extremely wealthy at this point, and theoretically, he could keep this up for about three more decades.

In his mind, surely the Gold Devouring Immortal was bound to give up at some point.

The only problem was that as they ventured deeper into the primordial land, everything was very unfamiliar to them, and they had already been attacked by primordial beasts on countless occasions. Even though they had managed to weather all of those storms, this was clearly not a sustainable strategy.

The deeper they ventured into the primordial land, the more at risk they would be.

At this moment, Jin Tong was crunching on a spirit treasure, while Xiao Bai was resting off the side with its eyes closed.

Right at this moment, a hideous screeching sound rang out from the dense forest down below, and just that sound alone was enough to send a burst of sharp pain spearing into Han Li's soul.

He hurriedly rose to his feet, just in time to see a massive gray shadow rising up from the forest down below, and it wasn't much slower than the carriage.

Han Li immediately activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, upon which he was able to identify the gray shadow as an enormous gray bird with a fleshy black comb on its head. As opposed to feathers, the bird had a layer of short gray fur clinging tightly to its skin, giving it an unsightly appearance.

At the same time, it was giving off a tremendous aura that indicated that it was at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage.

Han Li had no interest in getting caught up in a battle against such a formidable primordial beast, and he immediately swept a sleeve through the air to release a small white flag, which swelled to several thousand feet in size before unfurling itself to reveal a sea of clouds.

This was one of the immortal treasures that Han Li had secured from Gongshu Jiu.

The sea of clouds etched onto the flag began to glow with spiritual light, and a boundless expanse of white mist instantly surged out of the flag before descending toward the gray bird.

The giant gray bird screeched as the comb on its head lit up with dazzling gray radiance, following which it flapped its wings vigorously, releasing a gust of gray wind that transformed into a formidable gray tornado.

The gray tornado was giving off hints of law power fluctuations, it tore through the sea of clouds with ease, then swept directly toward the flying carriage.

At the same time, countless massive blades of gray wind appeared within the tornado, and it was clear that these were no ordinary blades of wind.

Han Li hurriedly made a hand seal to bring the flying carriage to halt, then swept a sleeve through the air to release three yellow badges, which appeared in front, to the left, and to the right of the flying carriage.

Waves of yellow light surged out of the three badges, forming a thick yellow light barrier around the flying carriage.

As soon as the yellow light barrier took shape, it was instantly ravaged by the barrage of countless gray blades of wind, causing it to ripple incessantly, but ultimately, it was able to keep the blades of wind at bay.

Not only that, but the yellow light barrier was even able to repel some of the blades of wind, sending them hurtling back toward the gray bird, which immediately took evasive measures, seemingly quite wary of the blades of wind.

At the same time, Han Li opened his mouth to release a burst of azure light that flew into the white flag, and another cloud of mist instantly surged out of the flag before taking on the form of seven or eight dragons that wrapped themselves around the giant gray bird in a flash.

These misty dragons were imbued with a great deal of immortal spiritual power from Han Li, and they were able to temporarily restrain the gray bird.

However, instead of taking advantage of this opportunity to try and slay the bird, Han Li immediately made a hand seal to send the flying carriage racing around the giant gray bird as a streak of green light.

A few moments later, a loud thump rang out from behind the carriage, and the gray bird had struggled free from the misty dragons before setting off in pursuit of the carriage once again.

Han Li paid no heed to it as he continued to pilot the carriage onward, and it didn't take long before the gray bird was left far behind.

After shaking off the gray bird, Han Li heaved a faint sigh of relief, then stowed the white flag and yellow badges away.

No more than two hours later, a burst of buzzing rang out from up ahead, and a massive purple cloud erupted out of the forest down below before sweeping toward the flying carriage.

Han Li focused his gaze on the purple cloud to discover that it was a swarm of countless purple hornets, each of which was the size of a millstone.

They had sword-like hooked stingers that were glowing blue trailing along behind them clearly indicating that they were filled with extremely potent poison.

Han Li summoned those three yellow badges to protect the flying carriage once again upon seeing this.

At the same time, he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a large crimson flag, which released a vast expanse of flames to create a sea of fire around the carriage, which continued to speed directly toward the swarm of purple hornets without pause.

In the end, the carriage was only able to fly out of the swarm of hornets after a struggle that lasted close to two hours.

At this point, Han Li was growing more and more concerned.

As they continued onward, they encountered more and more obstacles, to the point that they had to endure up to several dozen attacks from primordial beasts and various primordial tribes every single day.

Fortunately, Han Li was very well prepared, so he was able to weather those storms just fine, but their speed had been significantly hampered by these obstructions.

What was even more concerning to him was that the Gold Devouring Immortal didn't seem to be having the same problem. According to Jin Tong, no primordial beasts or tribes dared to attack it thanks to its tremendous power and formidable aura.

There wasn't anything that Han Li could do aside from continue to forge ahead, but despite his best efforts, the distance between them and the Gold Devouring Immortal was only continuing to shrink.

Chapter 569: Repaying Treachery With Treachery

Two months later.

A green jade flying carriage was racing over an ancient forest, leaving an extremely long trail of green light behind it.

All of a sudden, it drew to an abrupt halt, and Han Li began adding a new batch of Immortal Origin Stones onto the array on the carriage.

The array had been burning through his Immortal Origin Stones at a rapid rate, but it was a necessary sacrifice if they were to have any hope of keeping the Gold Devouring Immortal at arm's length.

At this moment, Jin Tong was seated with her legs crossed on the carriage with a sullen look on her face, while Xiao Bai was laying on the ground with an absentminded expression.

"Uncle, if we get to a point where we're no longer able to get away from that thing, are you going to abandon me and run away on your own?" Jin Tong suddenly asked with a concerned expression.

A weary look flashed through Han Li's eyes as he chuckled, "If you have the time to be pondering nonsense like this, you should focus on recovering as quickly as possible, then get back into Xiao Bai's stomach."

"That thing's coming after us faster and faster, I have to spend almost all of my time in Xiao Bai's stomach now! It would be terrible if I were to die from asphyxiation in Xiao Bai's stomach before that thing even has a chance to get to me!" Jin Tong sighed with a dejected expression.

"You're one to complain! With you coming in and out of my stomach so much, I've been feeling really nauseous lately, yet you don't hear me whining! The next time the Gold Devouring Immortal comes chasing after us, I'm not sure I'll be able to resist the urge to throw you back up!" Xiao Bai groaned.

"If you don't want me to stay in your stomach, then you can stay in mine! Given how much natural treasures and immortal treasures you've eaten, perhaps eating you will allow me to make a breakthrough just like that pill cauldron did! When that time comes, the tables will be turned, and I'll be the hunter instead of the prey!" Jin Tong countered as her eyes roamed over Xiao Bai in a sinister fashion.

Xiao Bai immediately turned away in a fearful manner upon hearing this.

Jin Tong was just about to tease Xiao Bai a little more when her smile suddenly stiffened, and she turned to Han Li with an urgent expression as she yelled, "Quick, Uncle! It's coming again!"

"Get back in Xiao Bai's stomach," Han Li instructed as an anxious look appeared on his face.

Immediately thereafter, the flying carriage began racing through the air at his behest.

At the same time, Jin Tong pulled out a Soul Armor Talisman before adhering it onto her own body, then flew into Xiao Bai's mouth as a tiny golden beetle, while Xiao Bai transformed into a white jade pendant that was stowed away into Han Li's storage pouch.

"Uncle, I can sense that it's coming even faster than before. Can we go any faster?" Jin Tong asked through voice transmission.

"This is as fast as we can go for now. By your estimates, how much longer will it take for it to catch up to us?" Han Li asked.

"If it can maintain its current speed, then it'll definitely be able to catch up to us within one and a half months," Jin Tong immediately replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly upon hearing this.

Moments later, he swept a sleeve through the air to produce the map that he had received from the Beast Race, then examined it for a moment before bringing the carriage to an abrupt halt.

You betrayed my trust first, so don't blame me for this...

All of a sudden, the flying carriage swiveled around and raced away in another direction.

Over a month flew by in a flash.

The flying carriage was darting over a vast mountain range, and by following the map, Han Li was able to pilot the carriage to a red valley.

As they approached the entrance of the valley, Han Li stopped the carriage, then cast his gaze toward the valley's entrance from afar. There was a giant humanoid lion engraved into each of the two mountain faces on either side of the valley, and one of them had its arms crossed over its chest as if it were conducting a prayer, while the other was wielding a huge ax.

In between the mountain faces was an enormous arched stone bridge, which was being patrolled by many foreign beings clad in suits of bone armor.

These foreign beings were each twice the size of the average human and possessed extremely imposing physiques. Their faces were similar in appearance to humans, each of them had a circle of roughly five or six lion heads growing around their faces.

This place was called the Red Spiral Valley, and it was where the Menace Lion Tribe, one of the Beast Race's eight holy tribes, resided.

Beneath the arched stone bridge were three giant semi-circular caves, and vast volumes of water were gushing out of those caves, sending vast clouds of water vapor erupting into the air.

While checking the map over a month ago, Han Li had discovered that they weren't very far away from the settlement of the Menace Lion Tribe, so he had changed directions to travel to this valley.

Along the way, Jin Tong would continue to periodically hide in Xiao Bai's stomach, but the Gold Devouring Beetle was coming after them faster and faster, so the distance between them was gradually shrinking, to the point that over the past few days, Han Li was able to sense the Gold Devouring Immortal through his spiritual sense without even requiring any alerts from Jin Tong.

Han Li inspected the valley momentarily, then made a hand seal while chanting an incantation, and his aura was instantly suppressed to the point that it was virtually completely undetectable.

Immediately thereafter, he swooped down from above, then descended into the murky river down below.

A dull thump rang out as Han Li plunged into the river with a tiny splash, then commenced a rapid descent.

Upon landing on the riverbed, he began to trudge his way upstream over the soft and loamy river soil, all the while doing his best not to use any immortal spiritual power.

The terrain of the riverbed was extremely complex, and there were extremely powerful eddies and whirlpools at ever turn, some of which were no less powerful than attacks from treasures, but thankfully, Han Li's physical constitution was so tremendous that he was able to make his way smoothly over the riverbed even without the use of immortal spiritual power.

Before long, he had already arrived at the foot of the giant arched bridge by scaling up the gradually elevating riverbed.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly noticed bursts of irregular energy fluctuations surging through the water up ahead, and several hundred giant black fish that were each around 10 feet in length came swimming directly toward him.

These black fish were covered in hard black scales that gave off a metallic sheen, and it was clear that these scales had been hardened and polished from being buffeted by the river sand that was being thrown up by the rapid currents. They opened their mouths to reveal rows of sharp teeth, clearly intending to intimidate Han Li, whose brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

After some deliberation, he could only heave an internal sigh before unleashing his Reversal True Axis ability, allowing him to slip through the school of giant black fish in the blink of an eye.

Over the past few months, some of his Time Dao Runes had already recovered, so he was able to use his Mantra Treasured Axis.

Sure enough, the guards of the Menace Lion Tribe patrolling the bridge up above immediately detected the faint spiritual power fluctuations released through the use of Han Li's Reversal True Axis ability, and they all turned to look into the river.

"Go and raise the alarm, this could be an enemy attack from the Insect Race!" the leader of the group of guards immediately instructed.

"Given how minor those energy fluctuations were, it's most likely a demon beast that inadvertently stumbled into the river. The Black Scale Fish should be able to take care of it," another one of the guards said.

"Our chief isn't here right now, so we must be on our guard. In these sensitive times, even the most minor abnormalities must be accounted for. Go and raise the alarm," the leader of the guards reiterated.

The other guard immediately gave an affirmative response before rushing over to the right side of the valley, and it didn't take long before the sound of a horn rang out across the entire valley.

Even on the riverbed, Han Li was still able to clearly hear the sound.

Immediately thereafter, the sound of one horn after another rang out, progressively getting deeper and deeper into the valley.

Armor-clad Menace Lion beings immediately began flying out of the caves on the mountain faces on either side of the valley, and they were arranged into teams to scour the river for any enemy presence.

At the same time, a series of massive wooden arcuballistas on either side of the valley were all aimed into the river, and the giant arrows in the arcuballistas were shimmering a faint green glow, indicating that they were smeared with lethal poison.

Han Li made his way to a large rock in the river, then drew to a halt as he communicated through voice transmission, "You can come out and draw the Gold Devouring Immortal here now."

"Alright, you can count on me, Uncle!" Jin Tong replied with a sly grin.

Immediately thereafter, a streak of golden light flew out of Han Li's sleeve, and Jin Tong appeared right beside him.

After getting some stable footing on the riverbed, she closed her eyes before releasing her aura without any restraint.

There was a Menace Lion being dressed in red elder robes standing on an altar to the left of the valley, and he was astonished to sense Jin Tong's immense aura.

"Grand Elder Yin Tong, this aura... It seems to belong to that insect spirit!" he exclaimed to an early-Golden Immortal Stage grand elder beside him with an incredulous expression.

The grand elder by the name of Yin Tong was just as incredulous to hear this. "How is that possible? We just received word from our chief not long ago that we're facing off against the Insect Race army at the Dark Star Canyon, how could the insect spirit have suddenly come here? There must be a mistake..."

"Hold on, this aura seems to be different. It..."

Before the elder had a chance to finish his sentence, his voice abruptly cut off, and he was rooted to the spot in shock and horror.

"What is it?" Grand Elder Yin Tong hurriedly asked.

"Th... There's another one coming..." the elder murmured in a shell-shocked manner as he turned to the entrance of the valley.

"What do you mean by that? Explain!" Yin Tong urged in a frustrated manner.

"There's another insect spirit... And this one seems to be at the High Zenith Stage..." the elderly explained as he turned to Yin Tong with an ashen complexion.

Chapter 570: Massacre

Yin Tong could hardly believe his own ears. After a brief moment of stunned silence, he suddenly turned and yelled, "Yin Liang, go and send a message to our chief! Yin Feng, evacuate all of the children, women, and elderly! Everyone else, prepare for battle!"

There were seven or eight Menace Lion Tribe elders ranging from the late-True Immortal Stage and the early-Golden Immortal Stage on the altar, and all of them immediately sprang into action.

Below the giant rock on the riverbed, Han Li could clearly sense the Gold Devouring Immortal's enormous aura rapidly approaching them, and through its aura, he could even sense that it was currently extremely furious.

"What did you do, Jin Tong? I can sense that it's aura is very unstable, like it's extremely angry about something," Han Li asked.

"All I did was ask it how it feels to be able to see me but not eat me," Jin Tong replied with a smile.

"You can communicate directly with it?" Han Li asked with a stunned expression.

"I can only sense it from far away, but now that we're so close, it's kind of like... we can communicate through voice transmission. I don't know exactly how to explain it, it's like we're connected by an invisible thread, and neither one is able to shake off the other," Jin Tong replied with a shrug.

Han Li wanted to ask more questions, but before he had a chance to do so, a deafening boom rang out in the distance, immediately following which a burst of tremendous shockwaves swept through the valley, causing the entire river to rear up like a reverse waterfall.

At the same time, the arched stone bridge exploded down the middle, and the Menace Lion beings standing on the remnants of the bridge were all looking on with furious expressions.

These were all of the warriors of the Menace Lion Tribe that hadn't been sent to participate in the battle at the Dark Star Canyon and weren't assigned with the task of evacuating the women, children, and elderly, and there were only around 4,000 to 5,000 of them.

Yin Shen rose up into the sky above the ruined stone bridge, then asked in a scathing voice, "Why is an almighty insect spirit like yourself attacking our Menace Lion Tribe instead of facing our Beast Race army?"

The enormous Gold Devouring Immortal was hovering in mid-air tens of thousands of feet away, and its flapping wings were producing a deafening noise.

It paid no heed to Yin Shen as it scoured the valley back and forth with a pair of cold and furious eyes, then suddenly roared, "Come out!"

Its voice was like rumbling thunder as it echoed throughout the valley, producing such powerful soundwaves that the remnants of the stone bridge quickly fell away chunk by chunk.

Yin Shen was only just barely able to steady himself, and a perplexed look appeared on his face as he asked, "Who are you looking for?"

However, the Gold Devouring Immortal continued to ignore him as it crashed down toward the entrance of the valley like a golden mountain.

"Warriors of the Menace Lion Tribe, it's time to fight!" Yin Tong declared.

However, the Gold Devouring Immortal completely ignored all of the Menace Lion Tribe warriors as it continued to crash down toward the entrance of the valley with tremendous power.

All of the Menace Lion Tribe warriors hurriedly rose up into the air before retreating into the valley, and at the same time, several hundred enormous griffin-like demon beasts rose up within the valley tens of thousands of feet away, then opened their beaks before producing a strange sound akin to the weeping of infants.

In doing so, they were releasing bursts of peculiar soundwaves that were further enhanced as they traveled through the horn-shaped valley, becoming progressively more formidable as they surged toward the Gold Devouring Immortal.

Even though Han Li and Jin Tong weren't within the area that the soundwaves were traveling through, he was still struck by a burst of sharp pain in his head, following which came a rush of dizziness and nausea.

He hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a spherical light barrier that encompassed both himself and Jin Tong, and only then did the sense of discomfort subside.

The rest of the valley was quite wide and spacious, but it abruptly tapered to an extremely narrow area at the entrance of the valley.

After being enhanced by the tapered terrain of the valley, the soundwaves had become countless times more powerful than before, and the Gold Devouring Immortal rushed headfirst into them as it swooped into the valley.

Waves upon waves of invisible soundwaves exploded violently, and it was as if something invisible were shattering into countless pieces, sending shrapnel flying in all directions.

The Gold Devouring Immortal was instantly rooted to the spot, while its previously lucid eyes became glazed over, and it was as if its spiritual sense had been destroyed by these soundwaves.

"Looks like the Menace Lion Tribe has some impressive tricks up its sleeve, Uncle! I can sense that its soul has been severely wounded, and it'll most likely be in this disoriented state for quite some time. Should we take advantage of this opportunity to kill it?" Jin Tong asked as her eyes lit up with excitement.

Han Li was silent for a moment upon hearing this, then analyzed, "These shockwaves can indeed harm the soul, but I feel like they're more so intended for physical damage. While it's true that even I was affected, even if I had been in the direct path of these soundwaves, I would've only been disoriented for three seconds at most. With that in mind, does it really make sense that these soundwaves could incapacitate it so completely?"

"You're saying that it's putting on an act to try and lure us out?" Jin Tong asked with a stunned expression.

"There's no need for us to speculate, someone else will find out for us," Han Li replied.

Sure enough, in the valley above, Yin Tong was observing the Gold Devouring Immortal with a hesitant expression, but ultimately, he gritted his teeth and ordered, "Attack!"

In the sky above the valley's entrance, an elder immediately sliced open his own hand, shedding his blood onto his staff while chanting an incantation in the language of the true spirits.

As he began his incantation, an extremely strange aura arose within the entire valley, and a layer of crimson mist emerged, enshrouding the entirety of the valley within it.

Within the crimson mist, the eyes of all of the Menace Lion Tribe warriors also turned a crimson color, while dark red light began to glow from their cheeks as a lion-like demon beast totem appeared on each of their faces.

With the emergence of these totems, the Menace Lion Tribe warriors underwent drastic transformations, swelling to several hundred feet tall. At the same time, the lion heads around their faces disappeared, and their humanoid faces turned into lion faces.

Immediately thereafter, all of the Menace Lion Tribe warriors sprang up into the sky to surround the Gold Devouring Immortal before attacking it all at once.

Even though they had swelled drastically in size, they were still downright diminutive in comparison with the Gold Devouring Immortal, and all of them began tearing at the Gold Devouring Immortal's body with their sharp claws.

A string of loud clangs rang out incessantly, but the Gold Devouring Immortal remained completely unscathed.

"We have to find the weak points on its body!" Yin Tong yelled as he charged toward the Gold Devouring Immortal's eyes.

Meanwhile, all of the other Menace Lion Tribe warriors charged toward the Gold Devouring Immortal's joints, the bases of its wings, and other perceived weak points, led by the tribe's elders.

As he approached the Gold Devouring Immortal's right eye, the crimson totem on Yin Tong's face glowed even brighter, and bursts of formidable spiritual power fluctuations surged through his meridians, converging toward the claws on his right hand.

His arm swelled drastically in size while glowing with radiant red light, looking rather cumbersome and disproportionate compared with the rest of his body, but the explosive power that it contained was certainly not to be scoffed at.

Let's see if you can keep pretending now!

Even though Han Li was unable to see the battle from the riverbed, he could roughly guess what was happening based on the spiritual power fluctuations that he was sensing.

Yin Tong was injecting all of his power into this single strike, and he was already right in front of the Gold Devouring Immortal's eye. In fact, he was so close that his claws could be seen reflected within the eye that he was attacking.

However, right at this moment, the disoriented look in the Gold Devouring Immortal's eyes abruptly faded, and it turned its gaze to Yin Tong in a cold and completely lucid fashion.

As soon as Yin Tong saw this, he immediately felt as if his entire body had been plunged into a glacial pit, but at this point, it was too late to turn back.

All he could do was yell for everyone to retreat while he continued to thrust his claws toward the Gold Devouring Immortal's eye.

A sharp clang rang out, and a flurry of sparks flew in all directions as a gash that was over 100 feet in length was scratched into the Gold Devouring Immortal's closed eyelid, following which semi-transparent liquid that appeared to be blood began flowing out of the gash.

The Gold Devouring Immortal's eyelid shuddered momentarily before springing open again, and it swept its front limbs through the air like lightning.

A series of crescent-shaped streaks of translucent golden light erupted forth, sweeping through the air in all directions like scythes designed to harvest lives.

Aside from the several hundred Menace Lion Tribe warriors who were able to retreat in time after hearing Yin Tong's warning, everyone else, including Yin Tong himself, had been sliced into two.

The Gold Devouring Immortal had clearly been truly infuriated, and it flapped its wings vigorously as its enormous body began to revolve rapidly on the spot, quickly transforming into an enormous golden storm that erupted through the air in all directions.

All of the dismembered Menace Lion Tribe warriors instantly had their bodies and nascent souls destroyed within the golden storm, and even their blood had been reduced to the tiniest of particles that rained down from above.

The remaining Menace Lion Tribe warriors fled back into the valley, and the only remaining elder looked up at the sky with an expression of fury and despair.

"The children, women, and elderly are still in the valley, so we cannot afford to retreat any further," the elder sighed.

A determined look then appeared on his face as he roared with all his might, "I offer up my blood and my body to Master Jiu Ling! Please descend upon us!"

Immediately thereafter, he closed his eyes and plunged his staff right into his own heart.

Chapter 571: Redirecting Trouble

As the elder plunged his staff into his own heart, the other Menace Lion Tribe warriors were also chanting the same thing as they pierced their claws into their own hearts, sending blood spilling all over the entire altar they were standing on.

With the staff pierced through his chest, the elder's vitality was rapidly fading as if it were being sucked away by the staff, but his eyes were only glowing brighter and brighter.

As the chanting continued, a layer of dark red light began to emerge over the bloodstained altar, and before long, the layer of light had risen up to form a pillar of dark red light that was over 10,000 feet tall.

An enormous beastly projection appeared within the pillar of light, and it gradually took on a substantial form. It was a mountainous primordial true spirit with nine lion heads growing on its neck.

Its fur was a dark purple color, and the mane around its neck was glowing purple while rippling slightly like a clump of seaweed, resembling a dark purple flame.

A furious look appeared in the true spirit's eyes at the sight of the horrific scenes in the valley, and all nine of its heads let loose a thunderous roar of fury in unison.

In contrast with the relationship between the other Beast Race tribes and the true spirits that they worshiped, the Menace Lion Tribe were true descendants of the true spirit, thereby inheriting its bloodline. As a result, the bond between them was more intimate.

"How dare you!" Jiu Ling roared, following which one of its nine heads abruptly made an inhaling motion, releasing a burst of tremendous suction force.

The blood of the Menace Lion Tribe warriors that was permeating throughout the area converged from all directions before being sucked into its mouth, and at the same time, all of the altars littered throughout the valley suddenly lit up on their own.

The totems engraved upon them began to glow brightly, and a series of lit purple braziers rose up from their centers.

There were specks of faint purple light within these braziers that were drifting out like fireflies before surging into Jiu Ling's mouth alongside the blood of its descendants, and it let loose a low roar as its muscles began to bulge outward.

At the same time, a layer of dark red scales emerged over its body, and the mane around its neck also grew to twice its original length, while its aura began to rapidly approach the mid-High Zenith Stage.

On the riverbed, a hint of surprise appeared on Han Li's face upon sensing this, and he remarked, "It seems like the Menace Lion Tribe shares a different relationship with their true spirit than the other Beast Race tribes.

“It's a little similar to the Ancestral God system of the Black Wind Sea. Through the sustenance of their bloodline and the power of faith imbued within the altar, perhaps this true spirit really will be able to put up a fight against the Gold Devouring Immortal."

"Really?" Jin Tong asked with a skeptical expression.

"Setting aside the bloodline sustenance from the Menace Lion Tribe warriors, no one knows just how much power of faith has accumulated in these totems. It definitely won't be able to defeat the Gold Devouring Immortal, it's just a matter of how much of a fight it can put up," Han Li said.

A hint of intrigue appeared on Jin Tong's face upon hearing this, and she was suddenly struck by the urge to spectate the battle, but there was no time for that.

Han Li gave her a pat on the head as he said, "We have to go."

Jin Tong faltered slightly upon hearing this, then flipped a hand over to produce a Soul Armor Talisman that she applied to her own forehead.

Han Li also swept a sleeve through the air to summon Xiao Bai, which immediately swallowed Jin Tong.

Moments later, a massive wave suddenly erupted out of the river, and a green jade flying carriage emerged before speeding away into the distance as a streak of green light, vanishing out of sight.

Outside the river, the Gold Devouring Immortal could sense that Jin Tong's aura had vanished once again, and as it looked up into the sky, a cold gleam flashed through its eyes as it set off in pursuit of the flying carriage.

However, right at this moment, a vast expanse of purple light suddenly emerged in front of it, and bursts of purple flames surged directly toward it, forming a scorching sea of fire in its path.

The Gold Devouring Immortal turned to discover Jiu Ling's central head with its mouth wide open, releasing a torrent for purple flames.

At the same time, the four heads on its left also had their mouths open to release gusts of white wind that swept the flames into a massive vortex, trapping the Gold Devouring Immortal within. Simultaneously, its remaining four heads were releasing vast waves of purple lightning that were injected into the fiery vortex.

Hundreds of enormous fiery vortexes were conjured up, all of which were connected by the purple lightning to form an extremely powerful suction force, transforming the entire surrounding valley into a restricted area.

Anyone within this area would be made to feel as if their bodies and souls were being restricted by this burst of suction force, rendering them completely unable to get away. All they could do was watch helplessly as the fiery vortexes were drawn closer and closer to them by the purple lightning until they were incinerated into nothingness.

At the same time, the hundreds of griffin-like demon beasts that had appeared in the valley earlier also emerged to surround the sea of purple flames while releasing the same screeching sound as before, sending powerful shockwaves sweeping directly toward the Gold Devouring Immortal.

A serious look finally appeared in the Gold Devouring Immortal's eyes, and it flapped its wings vigorously to release a burst of peculiar energy fluctuations...

Inside the Dark Star Canyon.

The chiefs of the eight holy tribes were seated next to each on the large chairs inside the palace next to the waterfall, while the chiefs of the smaller tribes were seated around them. At the center of the palace was a bonfire that was popping and crackling incessantly.

"Rest assured, everyone, our king has already made a full recovery," Nuo Qinglin declared.

"That is indeed a very good thing, but what I don't understand is why the insect spirit hasn't taken advantage of this opportunity to attack us all this time. Could it be that that human was able to inflict so much harm upon it that it's still yet to recover?" Ze Wushi asked with a perplexed expression.

"That's not very likely. If that human really were that powerful, then he wouldn't have snuck out of our Dark Star Canyon and only left that substitute behind," Yin Mei said with a shake of her head.

"I agree. If he really had the power to do that, then he wouldn't have feared a battle against us while our king was still injured," Nuo Qinglin chimed in with a nod.

"Have we still not been able to track down that human, Chief Nuo?" Yin Shen of the Menace Lion Tribe suddenly asked.

"Even though the insect spirit hasn't attacked us again, our two armies are still locked in a very tense confrontation. Hence, the number of people I can send out to search for him is very limited, and I doubt we'll be able to track him down anytime soon," Nuo Qinglin said.

A hint of displeasure appeared on Yin Shen's face upon hearing this, and he was just about to say something when his expression abruptly stiffened, following which he pulled out a palm-sized white bone badge.

He slit his fingertip open before dripping a drop of blood onto the badge, and a layer of concealed runes and a totem symbol immediately emerged on its surface.

Yin Shen then raised the bone badge to his own forehead with both hands, looking as if he were conducting a prayer.

Moments later, his expression changed drastically as he abruptly sprang to his feet, doing so with such force that the large chair beneath him was completely pulverized.

"What's wrong, Chief Yin Shen?"

Nuo Qinglin knew that something extremely important had to have happened for Yin Shen to display such a strong reaction.

"The insect spirit attacked my Red Spiral Valley..." Yin Shen murmured in a stunned voice, seemingly struggling to come to terms with this information himself.

"What? It led the Insect Race army to the Red Spiral Valley?" Ze Wushi asked with a surprised expression.

"No. It traveled to the Red Spiral Valley on its own, killing everyone there with the exception of the women, children, and elderly. Even Master Jiu Ling was..."

Yin Shen's voice trailed off there as a grief-stricken look appeared on his face.

"No wonder the Insect Race army hasn't attacked us since the initial attack..." Yin Mei mused.

"Does that mean that insect spirit currently isn't among the Insect Race army outside the Dark Star Canyon?" Deng Gui suddenly asked as his eyes immediately lit up.

It was clear that he wanted to take advantage of this opportunity to send out the Beast Race army in retaliation and wipe out the Insect Race army once and for all.

Yin Shen turned to Deng Gui with a furious expression upon hearing this, and only after a long while was he able to spit out the words: "I'm afraid my Menace Lion Tribe won't be able to continue playing a part in this battle..."

"Don't make any rash decisions, Chief Yin Shen. The Red Spiral Valley is clearly already beyond saving, so it makes no difference whether you go back or not. Instead, you should stay here and help us vanquish the Insect Race army to avenge your brethren! I'm sure that's what everyone else present is also thinking, right?" Deng Gui declared.

No one in the palace responded, and the atmosphere had become rather awkward.

While it was true that this was what everyone was thinking, no one was willing to directly articulate this thought.

"This is a completely unexpected tragedy, so I can understand Chief Yin Shen's desire to return to the Red Spiral Valley as soon as possible. Don't worry about the battle taking place here, and if you need any help with anything, feel free to speak up, our Calm Dawn Tribe will be sure to assist you in any way that we can," Nuo Qingling said with an earnest expression as he rose to his feet.

Yin Shen's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he extended a parting salute toward Nuo Qinglin as he said, "Master Jiu Ling is extremely severely wounded, so he's no longer able to provide protection for our Menace Lion Tribe. We won't be able to contribute much by remaining here anyway, so I'll be returning to the Red Spiral Valley."

"Rest assured, Chief Yin Shen, I'll inform Master Suliu and our King of what happened. I'm sure they'll be able to understand," Nuo Qinglin promised.

"You have my thanks, Chief Nuo."

At this point, Yin Shen's heart was no longer here, and he hurriedly expressed his gratitude to Nuo Qinglin before leaving the palace.

Following his departure, all of the tribal chiefs contacted their respective tribes through the use of secret techniques, and they were all very relieved to confirm that their tribes hadn't been attacked by the insect spirit.

Chapter 572: Impending Crisis

"What do you think of this, everyone?" Nuo Qinglin asked as he turned to all of the other chiefs in the palace.

"The Insect Race spent several decades to assemble this elite army consisting of several hundred tribes, yet after a single defeat, the inspect spirit abandoned the army to attack the Red Spiral Valley on its own... It just doesn't make sense..." Ulu mused with a perplexed expression.

"Indeed. Not only does it not make sense, it goes against the insect spirit's personality as well," Marlon chimed in.

After some discussion, none of them were able to make heads or tails of the situation. Meanwhile, Nuo Yifan was standing in the palace as well, and a thought had occurred to her.

Back when Senior Li was at the Dark Star Canyon, the insect spirit led the Insect Race army on an excessively aggressive attack, and now that Senior Li has left the Dark Star Canyon, the insect spirit has inexplicably attacked the Menace Lion Tribe... Is there really no correlation between these two events?

She recalled that back when she first met Han Li, there had been a strange golden beetle accompanying him, and its aura had been rather similar to that of the insect spirit. However, it had slain the Gray Toad beings without any hesitation, so she had regarded it as an ally, but thinking back now, she realized that something wasn't quite right.

It was said that some Insect Race tribes liked to engage in cannibalism. With that in mind, could it be that the insect race had attacked the Dark Star Canyon for the sake of Han Li's golden beetle?

A chill immediately ran down Nuo Yifan's spine at this thought. If that were the case, then she was completely to blame for drawing the Insect Race army to the Dark Star Canyon!

Her face instantly turned deathly pale as she lowered her head, not daring to share this theory with everyone.

It wasn't that she was afraid that her father or someone else would be reprimanded for this. Instead, she was worried that revealing something like this would draw ire from the other tribes toward the Calm Dawn Tribe, a consequence that was too much for her to bear.

......

Several more months passed by in a flash.

Even though the Gold Devouring Immortal had managed to severely wound True Spirit Jiu Ling of the Menace Lion Tribe, it had also been significantly worn down during that battle, so it was unable to pursue Jin Tong with the same level of intensity as before. Hence, Han Li was able to enjoy a rare period of peace.

However, that was only relative to the dire situation that they had previously been in.

As they ventured deeper and deeper into the primordial land, the environment was becoming more and more complex, and they encountered many primordial beasts that were even more formidable than Han Li and Jin Tong themselves.

Fortunately, at this point, they had begun to develop an understanding of the complex environment of the primordial land, and thanks to his enormous spiritual sense, Han Li was able to pre-emptively avoid these formidable creatures instead of inadvertently encroaching upon their territory.

Even so, they were still unable to avoid being attacked by some primordial beasts, and regardless of whether they posed a threat or not, Han Li was unwilling to engage in battle against them for fear of being slowed down.

Despite this, they were still inevitably slowed down quite a bit by these regular attacks.

One night, Daoist Xie was piloting the flying carriage over a vast plain.

As for Han Li, he was seated inside the cabin of the carriage, gently massaging a black jade slip in his hand.

His brows were tightly furrowed as if he were contemplating something, and he seemed to be quite hesitant.

After some time, he took a deep breath before pressing the jade slip against his own glabella.

The jade slip contained the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique. After obtaining this jade slip, he had cultivated it briefly to resolve the earlier issue of backlash, but he had never fully mastered it, and he was planning to resume his cultivation once he crossed the primordial land and found a safe place to cultivate.

However, in this situation, he was forced to scrap those plans.

In the face of an opponent as formidable as the Gold Devouring Immortal, he had to elevate his own powers as much as possible. It was too difficult to advance in his cultivation base in a short time, but perhaps there was a chance that he would be able to make some progress in the Spirit Refinement Technique, which was also perfect as the Gold Devouring Immortal's soul was its main weakness.

As the jade slip lit up, Han Li gradually entered a state of immersive meditation.

Meanwhile, Jin Tong was sitting on the edge of the flying carriage with her feet dangling over the side, and she was gently swinging them back and forth.

Seeing as Jin Tong would always reappear in a different direction after spending time in Xiao Bai's stomach, the Gold Devouring Immortal had changed its strategy. Whenever Jin Tong's aura disappeared, it would simply stop and wait, then continue its pursuit once Jin Tong re-emerged. Hence, Han Li was no longer making Jin Tong spend as much time in Xiao Bai's stomach as possible. Instead, he only resorted to this in some critical junctures.

As a result, she was able to stay on the outside for longer than before.

At this moment, her face was devoid of its usual smile, and it was as if she had suddenly become a lot more mature and quiet.

It was certainly not a pleasant experience to be on the run from such a formidable enemy for so long.

She looked down at the winding river on the plain below, and it resembled a shimmering white vein on the earth under the moonlight. She suddenly recalled that there was a similarly shimmering white crystal that she was still yet to finish, and she hurriedly summoned it before sinking her teeth into it as a blissful look appeared on her little face.

There were no clouds in the sky, so the moon was made to appear particularly bright.

Han Li was basked in a layer of faint white moonlight, making the lines of his face appear softer and more gentle.

However, at this moment, his body was trembling slightly, and what appeared to be an eye had opened up on his glabella, while numerous translucent threads were flying in and out of the eye, presenting a peculiar sight to behold.

Daoist Xie couldn't help but turn around to take a glance at Han Li upon sensing these strange energy fluctuations, and its brows furrowed ever so slightly with concern.

At this moment, Han Li's spiritual sense fluctuations were rather unstable. It was like a bubble that was constantly expanding and shrinking, and that was indeed what Han Li felt like was happening in his consciousness.

All of the spiritual sense in his consciousness was ebbing and flowing back and forth like the tide, the fluctuations were becoming more and more pronounced, until they transformed into enormous waves.

Some time later, his eyes abruptly sprang open, and he immediately began gasping for air.

Jin Tong was very startled to hear this, and she hurriedly rose to her feet and rushed over to his side before asking, "Are you alright, Uncle?"

Han Li offered no response, merely stowing his black jade slip away with a slightly weary look on his face. He then swallowed a pill and wiped the sweat from his forehead as he replied, "I'm fine. I was just trying to rush a little in my cultivation earlier, and something almost went wrong."

The fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique was quite easy to understand, but the more he progressed, the more risk presented itself, and even the slightest lapse in concentration could lead to qi deviation.

"You really scared me just now," Jin Tong said with a relieved expression.

"Is the Gold Devouring Immortal doing anything new?" Han Li asked.

"Not really, it's still just following us like usual. Right now, it should be..."

Jin Tong began to examine what the Gold Devouring Immortal was doing through their spiritual connection as she spoke, and a grim look suddenly appeared on her face.

"Is it close?" Han Li hurriedly asked with an alarmed expression.

"No, but it's suddenly accelerated," Jin Tong replied.

"How many days will it take for it to catch up to us?" Han Li asked.

"I don't think we have days left, Uncle. At this rate, it'll catch up to us in just a few hours," Jin Tong replied with a sullen expression.

"Brother Xie, you take a rest, I'll pilot the flying carriage," Han Li said as he turned to Daoist Xie.

Daoist Xie nodded in response, then flew up Han Li's sleeve as a streak of golden light.

Han Li took a glance at the Immortal Origin Stones embedded into the array on the carriage, and he could tell that they didn't need to be replaced for now, so he focused on piloting the carriage, sending it racing forward at full speed.

"Don't worry, go back into Xiao Bai's stomach for now. After that, I'll change directions a few more times to see if we can buy ourselves some time," Han Li consoled as he turned to Jin Tong.

Jin Tong nodded in response, then pulled out a Soul Armor Talisman, yet right as she was about to press it to her own forehead, her expression abruptly stiffened as she exclaimed, "It's sped up once again! It's burning through its own essential power! Has it gone insane? At this rate, it'll catch up to us in just three hours!"

"Looks like it's run out of patience," Han Li mused with tightly furrowed brows.

All of a sudden, the green jade flying carriage drew to an abrupt halt at his behest.

"Why did you stop, Uncle?" Jin Tong asked with a perplexed expression.

"This isn't going to work. It'll inevitably be able to catch up to us sooner or later," Han Li replied as he cast his gaze into the night sky.

"But Uncle, your Time Dao Runes still haven't fully recovered yet, so we have no chance against it in a battle," Jin Tong exclaimed.

"Who told you we're going to engage it in battle? I'm just switching to a different strategy. Put on the Soul Armor Talisman and go into Xiao Bai's stomach for now," Han Li said as a faint smile appeared on his face.

Jin Tong immediately obliged, doing as she was told, while Han Li summoned Xiao Bai before swallowing her.

After stowing Xiao Bai away, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he murmured to himself, "It sure is coming fast..."

The Gold Devouring Immortal had already entered Han Li's spiritual sensory range, so he no longer required any updates on its location from Jin Tong.

Han Li stowed the flying carriage away with a sweep of his sleeve, following which flashes of silver lightning appeared in his eyes as he began making a string of hand seals.

Before long, the arcs of silver lightning around him had swelled to form a silver lightning array, and he abruptly vanished from within the array amid a bright flash of lightning.

Chapter 573: Intense Pursuit

Not long after Han Li vanished from the spot, a loud whooshing sound rang out in the distant sky, following which a speck of golden light appeared before rapidly expanding as it approached.

The ball of golden light was as blinding as a second sun, and none of the living creatures nearby dared to gaze upon it.

The edge of the golden light was as sharp as a blade, and all of the space in its wake was rippling incessantly, as if it were about to be torn apart.

Finally, the ball of golden light drew to a halt where Han Li had been just a moment ago.

As the golden light faded, a massive golden beetle was revealed, and it was none other than the High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal.

It was clearly a little smaller than before, perhaps because it had burned through some of its essential power, or perhaps because it was still yet to make a full recovery from its battle against Jiu Ling. However, the fury in its eyes was burning brighter than ever.

Not long ago, it had just received word from the Insect Race army that the Beast Race army had suddenly retaliated in full force, led by King Yohu and all of the true spirits, and the Insect Race army had suffered a catastrophic defeat and extremely severe casualties.

What remained of the Insect Race army had already begun a full retreat, and it was inevitable that the Beast Race was going to be claiming a lot of territory in the wake of this battle. The Insect Race had been in prime position to win the war, but the tables had been completely turned.

Even so, the Gold Devouring Beetle still had no intention of returning to the Insect Race.

In other words, the survival of the Insect Race wasn't as important in its eyes as the hunt for the other Gold Devouring Immortal.

After sensing the residual lightning aura in the air, the Gold Devouring Immortal stopped in its tracks and took some time to rest. In its past experience, it was a far better course of action to continue its pursuit once its target reappeared, as opposed to going in the wrong direction and having to double back.

On top of that, it was confident that this type of spatial teleportation technique couldn't be used for long, and eventually, it was going to be able to capture its target.

......

At the same time.

A burst of violent spatial fluctuations suddenly erupted forth in the sky above a certain mountain, and countless arcs of lightning sprang out of thin air to form a massive silver lightning array.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li appeared within the array, and after taking a moment to compose himself, he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a beast hide map, which he began inspecting carefully.

Moments later, he stowed the map away, then pulled out another map before closely inspecting it as well.

After inspecting several maps in a row, he began inspecting his surroundings with a contemplative look on his face.

Shortly thereafter, he seemed to have decided on the direction that he wanted to go in, and he summoned his flying carriage once again before setting off as a streak of green light.

Around an hour later, the flying carriage drew to a halt, following which he summoned Xiao Bai amid a flash of white light, and Jin Tong soon came flying out of its mouth.

Her complexion was a little pale, and she looked around to discover that she was currently hovering in the air above a snowy mountain, upon which she hurriedly asked, "Where are we right now, Uncle?"

"This area is no longer on the map given to us by the Beast Race, so we've most likely ventured so deep into the primordial land that we're already very far away from the Beast Race and Insect Race territories," Han Li replied.

After a brief pause, he continued, "My spiritual sense is unable to detect the Gold Devouring Immortal at all now. Can you try and see if you can determine its location?"

Jin Tong immediately closed her eyes and obliged, and some time later, her eyes suddenly sprang open as an elated look appeared on her face.

"It's really far away now! I can still sense it, but the connection between us is far weaker than before."

"That's good to hear, but we can't let our guards down. It doesn't seem like it's planning to give up at all. Xiao Bai, do you recognize this place?" Han Li asked as he turned to the Pixiu.

"I feel like I came here once a very, very long time ago, but I can't remember clearly. The primordial land is enormous, and there are many places with similar terrains. Having said that, if we really have already left the territories of the Beast Race and the Insect Race, then we are indeed already deep in the primordial land," Xiao Bai replied.

"It looks like things will only get more dangerous from here onward, but at this point, turning back is no longer an option, so we can only keep advancing. By my estimates, we should be going in the right direction, so as long as we keep going, we'll eventually reach the Black Mountain Immortal Region.

“Jin Tong, stay out of Xiao Bai's stomach for now and make sure to keep constant tabs on the Gold Devouring Immortal. If it begins burning through its essential power again, notify me right away," Han Li instructed,

"You can count on me, Uncle!" Jin Tong vowed in a confident manner.

Han Li then swept a sleeve through the air to summon Daoist Xie as he said, "I'm going to resume my cultivation of the Spirit Refinement Technique now. In the meantime, I'll have to trouble you to pilot the carriage for me in my stead, Brother Xie."

Daoist Xie naturally had no objections to this, and with that, Han Li made his way into the cabin of the carriage, then swallowed a pill before sitting down with his legs crossed.

......

Close to a month passed by in a flash.

At this moment, Han Li was piloting the flying carriage, which was racing over an enormous ancient forest.

All of a sudden, he spotted a series of huge stone buildings peeking through the gaps in the trees down below through his peripheral vision.

Out of curiosity, he brought the flying carriage to a halt, and upon closer inspection, he discovered that there was a massive stone city down below.

The construction style of the city was completely different from anything that he had seen in the immortal region and in the Beast Race settlements. It was constructed from countless giant stone blocks, upon which were engraved all types of peculiar beastly designs, none of which were identifiable to Han Li.

However, most of these buildings were covered in thick layers of green moss, and many areas had already collapsed. There weren't any spiritual power fluctuations in the area, nor did there seem to be any living beings nearby, and the entire area was eerily quiet.

After inspecting the ancient city for a moment, Han Li decided that it was best to continue onward rather than waste time inspecting these ruins.

However, the white jade pendant hanging from his waist suddenly transformed into Xiao Bai amid a flash of white light, and it said, "Master, there's an extremely valuable treasure under those ruins! I can smell it!"

Jin Tong was sitting at the back of the carriage with a bored expression, but she was immediately intrigued to hear this, and she sprang to her feet as she yelled, "There's a treasure here? Where?"

"The treasure is hidden underground beneath the city, and it's concealed by special restrictions, so I can't determine its exact location, nor exactly what it is. However, the special energy fluctuations that it's releasing indicates that it's definitely no ordinary treasure!" Xiao Bai replied in an excited manner.

"You can't tell what it is just because there are some restrictions in the way? Why are you so useless? Try harder! Is it something of the same caliber as the pill cauldron that I ate before?" Jin Tong asked in an urgent voice.

"Regardless of what it is, we don't have time to go after it. If we trigger the restrictions in the city and end up getting trapped here or delayed until the Gold Devouring Immortal gets here, we won't be able to get away," Han Li said with a grim expression.

Xiao Bai and Jin Tong were both very disappointed to hear this, particularly Xiao Bai.

"Even though we haven't encountered much trouble of late, we still have to be on our guard. We can come back to explore this place another time, but for now, we have to keep going," Han Li continued.

"I finally get a chance to make myself useful, yet it's all in vain. Master, if you let me enter that city, I'll be able to ascertain the exact location of the treasure in an hour at most, and perhaps I can even find a shortcut to the treasure! Can you just let me give it a try?" Xiao Bai implored as it stood on the edge of the flying carriage and looked down at the ancient city below with intense longing in its eyes.

Han Li was a little moved upon hearing this.

There wasn't a single cultivator in the world who didn't love treasures, and it was clear that this had to be an extraordinary treasure, given how desperate Xiao Bai was to obtain it, but this was simply not the time to go treasure-hunting.

Right as he was about to say something, Jin Tong's expression suddenly changed drastically as she yelled, "We have to get out of here, Uncle!"

"What's wrong?" Han Li hurriedly asked.

"That thing's burning through its essential power again, and it's coming after us way faster than before!" Jin Tong replied in an urgent voice.

"Alright, go hide in Xiao Bai's stomach," Han Li immediately instructed without any hesitation.

Jin Tong nodded in response, then put on a Soul Armor Talisman in a well-rehearsed fashion before flying into Xiao Bai's mouth as a golden beetle.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li stowed both Xiao Bai and the flying carriage away, then conjured up another giant lightning array to teleport himself away.

Chapter 574: Nearing the Limits

In the sky above an enormous canyon, long arcs of silver lightning sprang forth amid violent spatial fluctuations, forming a lightning array in mid-air, and Han Li appeared at the center of the array amid a rumbling thunderclap.

He looked around momentarily before summoning his flying carriage, which immediately began racing forward as a green shadow at his behest.

After that, he summoned Daoist Xie and instructed it to pilot the carriage in his stead, then sat down with his legs crossed to continue cultivating the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Countless kilometers away from Han Li, the Gold Devouring Immortal was giving off blinding golden radiance as it flew through the air at an astonishing speed.

Compared with how infuriated it had been in the past, it was now a lot calmer.

Clearly, it had already grown accustomed to its target's strategy of periodically disappearing before reappearing elsewhere, and its strategy in response was just to keep pursuing its target without pause.

Given its cultivation base and the incredible physical constitutions of all Gold Devouring Immortals, it could easily keep this up indefinitely.

......

Close to a month later.

As the Gold Devouring Immortal began approaching once again, Han Li had no choice but to flee again using his lightning teleportation array.

......

Half a year later, the flying carriage was racing through a boundless sea of gray mist.

The mist was churning like turbulent waves, significantly hampering the speed of the flying carriage.

There were around a dozen gray lizard-like primordial beasts pursuing the carriage, every single one of which was at the Golden Immortal Stage, while one of them was around twice the size of the others and giving off a High Zenith Stage aura.

The lizard-like demon beasts were roaring with excitement as pillars of gray light erupted out of their mouths toward the flying carriage up ahead.

Meanwhile, Han Li was piloting the carriage with a grim look on his face, doing his best to avoid the pillars of gray light, while Jin Tong, Xiao Bai, and Daoist Xie were at the back fo the carriage, warding off the pillars of gray light that he wasn't able to evade.

All the while, the Gold Devouring Immortal continued to stalk them from several million kilometers away.

......

Two years later.

On the boundless yellow desert, gusts of ferocious wind were howling incessantly, and the landscape was riddled with enormous tornados that stood like pillars between heaven and earth.

There were bursts of yellow light flashing within the tornados, and they were giving off a tremendous rumbling noise that caused the surrounding space to tremble as waves of spatial fluctuations swept outward in all directions.

Occasionally, two of these giant tornados would crash into one another, and countless spatial rifts would instantly appear as a result.

A ball of green light and a ball of golden light were flying through the desert one after another, and both of them were doing their best to avoid the tornados while forging ahead with great difficulty.

The ball of golden light was clearly much faster than the ball of green light in front of it, and the distance between the two was rapidly shrinking.

All of a sudden, arcs of silver lightning erupted out of the ball of green light, instantly forming a silver lightning array, following which the ball of green light vanished amid a rumbling thunderclap.

......

Over a decade flew by in a flash.

At this moment, a ball of green light was racing through the sky above a boundless swamp.

The ball of light was green in color, but not a uniform green throughout. Instead, it was an amalgamation of all types of different shades of green.

Despite so many shades of green being mixed together, the ball of light was somehow very nondescript, and it was able to camouflage itself against the surrounding space, making it very difficult to spot.

With the ball of light was the flying carriage that Han Li and the others were on.

The color of the flying carriage was far different from what it had been in the past. Previously, the carriage had looked as if it had been carved out of a single chunk of green jade, yet at this moment, it was a hideous patchy green color, as if something had been smeared over it.

While the flying carriage was looking far more unsightly than before, this patchy green light that it was giving off was able to conceal all of its spiritual power fluctuations, as well as the spiritual power fluctuations emanating from the hexagonal array on the carriage.

This green substance was a type of spirit tree sap that Han Li had obtained by chance while passing through a primordial tribe, and it had spared him a lot of trouble.

At this moment, there was a rather grim look on his face as he piloted the flying carriage, while a pale-faced Jin Tong was sitting beside him, nibbling on a spirit treasure.

Xiao Bai was laying on the ground on his other side, and it was clear that it was also taking some time to recover.

"It's less than 100,000 kilometers away now," Jin Tong suddenly reported.

Han Li took a glance behind the carriage, and a hint of blue light flashed through his eyes, following which he turned back around to face forward again before making a string of hand seals.

Arcs of silver lightning erupted out of his body, forming a lightning array around the flying carriage with countless lightning runes dancing within it.

A rumbling thunderclap rang out as the lightning array lit up, following which the flying carriage vanished in a flash.

Mere moments after the flying carriage disappeared, a ball of golden light shot forth from afar, then drew to a halt where the flying carriage had just disappeared.

The golden light faded to reveal the Gold Devouring Immortal, and it inspected its surroundings momentarily, then continued onward with a cold sneer on its face.

At the same time, a burst of spatial fluctuations erupted in the air above a lush forest countless kilometers away, and a ball of golden lightning appeared before rapidly spreading outward to form a golden lightning array, at the center of which Han Li and the green flying carriage emerged.

Han Li cast an incantation seal into the flying carriage, and it immediately continued onward while releasing the same patchy green light as before.

Even though he had managed to open up some distance on the Gold Devouring Immortal once again, he didn't relax in the slightest. Instead, he seemed to have only grown more concerned.

He had been fleeing from the Gold Devouring Immortal for over a decade up to this point, and during this time, he had encountered countless crises.

Not only had they been attacked by all types of primordial beasts, they were occasionally even targeted by frighteningly powerful primordial true spirits, and that wasn't even to mention all the types that they had stumbled into different perilous regions.

If it weren't for his immense spiritual sense, time law powers, and the large collection of powerful treasures and allies at his disposal, he would've most likely already perished in the primordial land even before the Gold Devouring Immortal caught up to them.

Of course, out of all of this, the Gold Devouring Immortal still remained the most potent threat.

Up to this point, he had pulled out all the stops, including even the Lightning Restraining Wood teleportation array that could facilitate ultra long-distance teleportation, and he had also attempted to lure the Gold Devouring Immortal into some perilous areas in the hope that it would be slowed down.

However, the Gold Devouring Immortal was extremely formidable, and not only were the primordial beasts that it encountered completely unable to pose a threat to it, it was also able to navigate all of Han Li's traps with ease.

Whenever the situation became truly dire, Han Li would use his lightning teleportation array to get away just in the nick of time.

He possessed the Lightning Bird bloodline in his body, and he also had the Divine Devilbane Lightning of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and the assistance of Daoist Xie, so as long as he didn't run out of Immortal Origin Stones, he would be able to replenish his lightning power reserves indefinitely, but eventually, his resources were going to be exhausted.

Even though Han Li did everything in his power to speed up his own recovery after unleashing his lightning teleportation array, the process of conversion from immortal spiritual power to lightning power was a very time-consuming one, so it was certainly not sustainable.

In particular, the Gold Devouring Immortal seemed to have recently realized the sticky situation that Han Li was in, and it was exerting even more pressure in its pursuit. As a result, Han Li's lightning power reserves were being quickly whittled down, and he was going to run out before too long.

With that in mind, he heaved a faint sigh as he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis.

Most of the Time Dao Runes on its surface had already recovered, and that was a very encouraging sight.

With these Time Dao Runes recovered, even if the Gold Devouring Immortal were to catch up to them, he had some confidence in his ability to deal with it.

Right at this moment, Jin Tong suddenly stood up as she declared, "I'm ready to go, Uncle."

Daoist Xie immediately took over piloting the carriage from Han Li upon hearing this, while Han Li made his way over to Jin Tong's side before sitting down with his legs crossed.

He then pressed a hand over her glabella while chanting an incantation, and a layer of translucent light emerged over his glabella.

As the incantation continued, the burst of translucent light grew brighter and brighter, and it flowed out of his body before surging into Jin Tong's head through the palm of his hand.

A series of translucent spirit patterns instantly appeared on her forehead, and they were giving off faint spiritual power fluctuations.

The cloud-like patterns that had appeared on Jin Tong's forehead were very similar to the ones imparted by Soul Armor Talismans.

Certain rare materials were required to craft Soul Armor Talismans, thereby making them very expensive, and even with Han Li's enormous wealth, the expenditure was too much for him to maintain over a long period of time. Hence, he began to study the talisman, and he discovered that it worked by converting one's spiritual sense into a substantial form before transforming it into a protective barrier that was infused into the talisman for others to use.

After figuring out the inner workings of the talisman, he immediately attempted to replicate it.

On top of that, he had been cultivating the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique with every spare moment that he had.

It was unclear whether he was truly really suited to cultivating the Spirit Refinement Technique, or whether his latent potential had been brought to the fore by the constant danger that he was in. In any case, he had been making rapid progress in the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique. At this point, he had almost fully mastered it, and his spiritual sense had been enhanced by around twofold.

With his enhanced spiritual sense, Han Li was better equipped to replicate the Soul Armor Talismans, and even though he wasn't able to craft them due to a lack of materials, he was able to reference them to cast a layer of protection over Jin Tong's soul.

Jin Tong opened her eyes, then flew into Xiao Bai's body as a streak of golden light.

Meanwhile, Han Li took over from Daoist Xie again, then immediately changed directions before flying onward.

Once again, the Gold Devouring Immortal found itself unable to detect Jin Tong's presence, and it gave a cold harrumph, but it wasn't concerned at all.

It could sense that its target was already nearing their limits, and they wouldn't be able to run away for much longer.

With that in mind, the golden light radiating from its body grew even brighter as it raced forward at an even faster speed than before.

Chapter 575: Dire Straits

Several more months passed by in the blink of an eye.

In the sky above a primordial desert, a flying carriage was racing along like a bolt of green lightning, only appearing for an instant before vanishing into the distant horizon.

On the flying carriage, Han Li wore a grim expression as he made a rapid string of hand seals.

Daoist Xie and Xiao Bai were situated on either side of him, releasing a burst of yellow light and white light, respectively, into his body.

Han Li's expression didn't betray his emotions, but internally, he was feeling rather frustrated.

Over the past month, the Gold Devouring Immortal had been pursuing them like mad, and somehow, it had managed to speed up significantly, exerting immense pressure upon Han Li.

He was forced to use his lightning teleportation array on many occasions in succession in a short time, and at this point, the lightning power reserves in his body had completely run dry.

At this point, the Gold Devouring Immortal was only several hundred thousand kilometers away. Jin Tong was currently inside Xiao Bai's stomach, so they weren't in any danger for now, but once she came out, the Gold Devouring Immortal would be able to catch up to them in a very short time,and it had already been over an hour since Jin Tong had entered Xiao Bai’s stomach.

This meant that it wasn't going to be long before he had to directly face an enemy far more formidable than himself.

Even in this dire situation, Han Li remained calm and collected. At this moment, he was releasing his spiritual sense to constantly keep tabs on his surroundings, and at the same time, his mind was racing as he tried to think of a way out of this predicament.

All of a sudden, something caught his attention, and he looked down in a certain direction.

At this point, the flying carriage had already emerged from the desert, and down below as a vast azure mountain range. The ground and all of the rocks on the mountains were all azure in color, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

Additionally, the world's origin qi here was far more abundant than it was elsewhere.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

According to past experience, certain powerful beings had to be residing in a place with such abundant spiritual qi. Perhaps there were even some powerful primordial tribes in this mountain range, and that could present an opportunity for him to save himself.

With that in mind, he immediately activated his Spirit Refinement Technique to release his spiritual sense with all his might.

Right at this moment, Xiao Bai suddenly opened its mouth, and Jin Tong flew out from within.

At this moment, her complexion was deathly pale, and her aura was also in a state of disarray, clearly indicating that she had only come out after reaching her absolute limits.

"I can't stay in there any longer, Uncle..." Jin Tong said in a feeble voice.

A hint of sympathy appeared in Han Li's eyes at the sight of her terrible condition, and he summoned a pile of spirit treasures for her as he said, "That's fine. Take a rest, I'll think of a way to save us."

Jin Tong nodded feebly in response, then sat down before picking up a spirit treasure and stuffing it into her own mouth.

Han Li took a deep breath as he continued to pilot the flying carriage forward while scouring his surroundings with his spiritual sense.

Even though the azure mountain range was very abundant in spiritual qi, there were no perilous terrains that could be used to his advantage, nor any signs of settlement from powerful primordial tribes.

As he continued to fly onward, his heart slowly began to sink.

......

Several hundred thousand kilometers away, the Gold Devouring Immortal was racing through the air with cold killing intent flashing in its eyes.

The golden light radiating from its body was glowing brighter and brighter, resembling a scorching golden flame, and it sped up even further.

It could clearly sense that the distance between itself and its target was rapidly shrinking.

Right at this moment, a burst of azure light flashed over a mountain face deep in the azure mountain range, and the rock face began to warp, transforming into a giant face that cast its gaze toward the Gold Devouring Immortal.

The Gold Devouring Immortal paid no heed to this. Its only objective was to capture its target, so it merely ignored anything else that didn't actively get in its way.

It continued to accelerate as it flew past the mountain face without pause, and as time passed, it spotted a speck of green light on the distant horizon up ahead.

The ball of green light was flying away from the Gold Devouring Immortal, but at a far slower speed.

The Gold Devouring Immortal's eyes instantly lit up with excitement upon seeing this, and it let loose a piercing screech as it sped up even further.

Just a few seconds later, it appeared directly behind the ball of green light, which contained the flying carriage that Han Li was on.

Han Li and others were all very alarmed and panicked at the sight of the Gold Devouring Immortal, and upon spotting the panicked expressions on their faces, a sense of immense joy welled up in the Gold Devouring Immortal's heart.

It opened its mouth to release a thick pillar of golden light, which appeared behind the flying carriage in a flash before crashing down with tremendous power.

Standing on the carriage, the spiritual light around Han Li's body brightened significantly, as did the green light emanating from the flying carriage, and it moved several kilometers horizontally in the blink of an eye, allowing it to just barely evade the pillar of golden light.

However, the pillar of golden light then suddenly exploded into countless thin rays of golden light, which resembled countless golden flying swords that hurtled directly toward the flying carriage.

A resounding boom rang out as the flying carriage exploded into a ball of radiant green light, following which a streak of azure light shot out from within before fleeing into the distance.

A cold sneer appeared on the Gold Devouring Immortal's face as it lashed out with one of its front limbs, unleashing a massive blade of golden light that was close to 10,000 feet in length.

The blade of light was curved to resemble the blade of a scythe, and there was a layer of rippling golden light over its surface as it swept through the air with tremendous power.

Bursts of immense invisible force were erupting out of the blade, causing the entire space within a radius of several dozen kilometers to compress forcefully toward the streak of azure light from all directions.

The streak of azure light was instantly slowed down significantly as a result.

Right at this moment, a thunderous roar rang out from within the streak of azure light, and a giant furry golden fist abruptly emerged amid a flash of golden light. There were countless golden runes surging around the fist, and it was crashing toward the giant golden blade up above with unstoppable might.

At the same time, a piercing screech rang out as a huge streak of translucent golden light erupted forth, transforming into a golden sword projection that was over 10,000 feet in length before sweeping toward the giant golden blade as well.

The golden sword projection was extremely fast, leaving a trail of afterimages in its wake, yet as soon as it clashed against the giant golden blade, it was instantly sliced into two.

However, the golden light radiating from the giant golden blade also shuddered unsteadily, while its downward momentum was also somewhat arrested.

Right at this moment, the golden fist struck the golden blade with tremendous power.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as a burst of blinding golden light erupted in all directions alongside waves of immense power that eradicated the restrictive force in the surrounding space.

The giant fist was almost sliced into two, and blood immediately came gushing out of the wound, but the golden blade had also been destroyed.

A massive golden ape stumbled unsteadily out of the golden light, and it was panting heavily, while large sections of its fur were stained red with blood.

On one shoulder of the golden ape stood Jin Tong in her beetle form, while standing on his other shoulder were Xiao Bai and Daoist Xie, both of which had rather unsteady auras, indicating that they had been injured when the flying carriage was destroyed.

Furthermore, Daoist Xie's left arm was nowhere to be seen, while Xiao Bai was carrying a massive gash on its back.

Jin Tong cast a vicious gaze toward the Gold Devouring Immortal, but the fear deep in her eyes was very apparent.

The Gold Devouring Immortal paid no heed to Han Li and the others as it focused its gaze solely on Jin Tong, and a hint of greed flashed through its eyes.

In the next instant, it abruptly vanished from the spot.

The giant golden ape immediately sprang into action upon seeing this, darting away to the side as a massive golden shadow.

However, right at this moment, an even faster streak of golden light emerged before flashing past the golden ape, instantly inflicting a deep wound that began bleeding profusely.

The golden ape flew away into the distance before drawing to a halt, and it was revealed that a massive gash had been sliced into its body from its chest to its lower abdomen, and the wound was so deep that bone was visible through it.

At the same time, one of Jin Tong's front limbs had also been severed, and there was a pained look on her face.

Meanwhile, the streak of golden light drew to a halt not far away, then faded to reveal the Gold Devouring Immortal, which was holding Jin Tong's severed front limb in its mouth.

A burst of golden light flew out to sweep up the limb before sucking it into its mouth, and a blissful look appeared on its face, as if it were savoring the finest delicacy in the world.

The giant golden ape hurriedly pressed a hand over the huge gash that had been sliced into body, and a layer of green light flashed over the palm of its hand, upon which the massive gash quickly sealed, while the bleeding also ceased.

Immediately thereafter, it sprang through the air before taking on Han Li's Azure Luan Bird form amid a flash of azure light, then began flying away as quickly as it could.

At the same time, bursts of golden light emerged from the Azure Luan Bird's body, and the faint projection of a rapidly revolving golden wheel could be seen within the golden light.

All of a sudden, around a dozen identical golden and azure projections emerged from the Azure Luan Bird's body, all of which were also giving off identical auras as they shot forth in different directions, and they were no slower than the Gold Devouring Immortal.

A hint of surprise flashed through the Gold Devouring Immortal's eyes as it sensed the time law aura emanating from the golden wheel, and it lashed out with both of its front limbs in unison.

Violent spatial fluctuations instantly swept through the surrounding area in a radius of several hundred kilometers, and countless bursts of radiant golden light erupted out of thin air, instantly forming a golden spirit domain that encompassed all of the Azure Luan Bird projections, slowing them down significantly.

Chapter 576: Karma

The Gold Devouring Immortal opened its mouth to release a thick pillar of golden light, which flashed through the air like a bolt of lightning, and within it were numerous translucent golden threads that were giving off a terrifying destructive aura.

In the next instant, a resounding boom rang out as the pillar of golden light split apart into around a dozen smaller beams of light, each of which shot forth toward one of the Azure Luan Bird projections.

These beams of light were extremely fast, while the Azure Luan Bird projections had been slowed down significantly, so the former was able to catch up to the latter in an instant.

A string of thunderous explosions rang out as the beams of golden light were detonated in unison, transforming into radiant golden suns that released devastating auras of destruction, creating countless spatial rifts in the surrounding area.

All of the Azure Luan Bird projections were instantly destroyed amid the explosions of golden light, with the exception of a single one.

This was the true Azure Luan Bird, and its feathers were in a state of complete disarray, while the wound stretching from its chest to its lower abdomen had been split open and was once again bleeding profusely.

Jin Tong was standing on the Azure Luan Bird's back, and she was also riddled with injuries, with countless thin cracks lining her entire exoskeleton.

As for Xiao Bai and Daoist Xie, they were nowhere to be seen, but numerous white and golden fragments could be seen littered throughout the nearby space.

The Azure Luan Bird threw up a mouthful of blood, but the defiance in its eyes didn't waver as it summoned its Mantra Treasured Axis once again.

However, before it had a chance to do anything else, several dozen translucent golden threads suddenly appeared directly beneath it, then pierced through its body and emerged from its back before it had a chance to react.

The Azure Luan Bird's entire body instantly stiffened, while the Mantra Treasured Axis also abruptly ceased in its rotation.

Immediately thereafter, the translucent golden threads converged forcefully, slicing the Azure Luan Bird's body into countless pieces, all of which began raining down toward the ground below.

Jin Tong wasn't struck by these translucent threads, but her expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and she immediately fled into the distance as a ball of golden light.

However, before she was able to get very far, the translucent golden threads intertwined with one another to form a huge golden net, trapping her within it.

Immediately thereafter, the Gold Devouring Immortal appeared directly before her, then opened its mouth to release a burst of golden light that encompassed her entire body.

A horrified look appeared on Jin Tong's face as she struggled with all her might, and golden light erupted out of her body, frantically attempting to keep the golden net at bay, but her efforts proved to be completely futile.

A derisive sneer appeared on the Gold Devouring Immortal's face, and it opened its mouth up wide, releasing a burst of golden light that sucked in Jin Tong in a flash.

Trapped within the golden light, Jin Tong's body shrank down rapidly before vanishing into the Gold Devouring Immortal's mouth.

The Gold Devouring Immortal hovered in mid-air with its eyes tightly shut, and the golden spirit domain around it rippled momentarily before vanishing into its body.

Moments later, radiant golden light erupted out of its body, forming waves of golden light that swept forth in all directions alongside its tremendous aura, which was slowly elevating bit by bit.

"I've finally found another one... Someday, I will return to my full power..." the Gold Devouring Immortal murmured to itself, then closed its eyes once again.

......

On the edge of a vast forest.

There was a small mountain here that was lined with jagged rocks, and a green jade flying carriage was rapidly approaching from afar before crashing heavily down onto the ground like a shooting star.

The entire mountain shuddered violently as countless rocks came tumbling down, raising an enormous cloud of dust.

On the flying carriage, Han Li gave a muffled groan as he forcibly swallowed the mouthful of blood that had already gushed to the base of his throat.

"Uncle! Are you alright?" Jin Tong exclaimed in a concerned voice.

Han Li waved a hand to indicate that he was fine.

He then released his spiritual sense to scour the surrounding area momentarily, following which his brows furrowed slightly as he asked, "Jin Tong, can you sense where the Gold Devouring Immortal is right now?"

Jin Tong hurriedly closed her eyes to focus on her spiritual connection with the Gold Devouring Immortal upon hearing this, and moments later, she reopened her eyes as a perplexed look appeared on her face.

"For some reason, it's not moving... It's still in the same place that it was originally at, and it doesn't appear to have moved at all."

"It's not chasing after us?" Han Li asked as he swallowed a pill.

"No, but..."

"But what?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Its spiritual sense and immortal spiritual power are all fluctuating violently in a very abnormal fashion. It's almost as if it's locked in a fierce battle, but that's clearly not the case. Why is that?" Jin Tong mused with a puzzled expression.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li said, "According to your description, I think it must've fallen into some type of powerful illusion."

"Illusion? How did it suddenly fall into an illusion?" Jin Tong exclaimed.

"I don't know, but in any case, this is good news for us. Let's keep going, we can't afford to delay here any longer," Han Li replied.

Jin Tong immediately nodded in response.

The flying carriage lit up once again, yet right as it was about to rise up into the sky, Han Li was suddenly struck by a rush of dizziness, following which a voice rang out within his consciousness.

"I've temporarily trapped that Gold Devouring Immortal for now, but the illusion will only last 20 years. At your current cultivation base, continuing onward will be no different from committing suicide, so I suggest that you turn back and go back to where you came from."

Han Li was very alarmed to hear this voice, and he immediately channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique to protect his own consciousness while asking internally, "Who are you, and why did you help me?"

However, there was no response to his question, and the dizzy sensation clouding his mind also faded.

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly as he released his spiritual sense to scour the surrounding area, but he was unable to find anything amiss.

Jin Tong was rather perplexed by Han Li's strange actions, and she asked, "What's wrong, Uncle?"

Han Li offered no reply as he stood rooted to the spot in a daze, seemingly contemplating something in silence.

Moments later, he heaved a faint sigh and shook his head, and the flying carriage sped away into the distance at his behest.

......

There was an enormous peach blossom forest countless kilometers away.

Under an enormous ancient peach blossom tree in the forest was a massive bed chariot, reclined on top of which was a huge white fox. The fox had a shock of golden fur on its glabella, resembling a heavenly eye.

Its eyes were slightly narrowed, making it appear as if it were half-asleep, and its entire body was enshrouded in a faint glow, making it appear as if it were a fox deity.

Not far away from the giant white fox was a gorgeous young girl in a short white dress. There was a slightly seductive quality to her stunning beautiful features, which were currently displaying a concerned expression, and after some hesitation, she asked, "Esteemed patriarch, if you could trap that Gold Devouring Immortal, then why didn't you help him a bit more and kill it altogether?"

"You know that I don't have any fondness for humans, Le'er. If it isn't for the fact that he looked after you in the Spirit Domain Realm, I would've already killed him for encroaching upon the territory of our Spirit Fox Tribe!" The white fox replied with a cold harrumph.

The girl that it had just referred to as Le'er was none other than Liu Le'er, who had spent much of her formative years with Han Li back in the Spirit Domain Realm.

"But esteemed patriarch..."

"That's enough!" the white fox snapped as its eyes abruptly sprang open. "I helped him this time not just to repay him for looking after you in the past, but also to sever the karma between you and him. This matter concerns your future cultivation, and while I do spoil you in other things, this is non-negotiable! If you refuse to accept this outcome, then I'll go and kill him right now to sever the karma at its roots!"

"No, don't do that! I'm sorry, esteemed patriarch," Liu Le'er hurriedly said in an alarmed manner.

A hint of sympathy appeared on the white fox's face upon seeing her panicked reaction, and he sighed, "Killing that Gold Devouring Immortal will incur severe consequences, even for me. I have no idea how that man made an enemy out of that Gold Devouring Immortal, but there's no need to worry.

“As long as he knows what's good for him and turns back, it won't be impossible for him to make it back to the nearest immortal region in 20 years."

Liu Le'er wasn't relieved at all to hear this, and the concern in her eyes only grew more pronounced.

......

Close to a year passed by in a flash.

During this time, Han Li had continued to venture even deeper into the primordial land without pause.

However, as they advanced in their journey, the primordial beasts that they encountered became more and more powerful. As a result, they had no choice but to slow down and proceed with caution.

Even so, they had still in advertently incurred the wrath of extremely formidable primordial beasts on several occasions, thereby forcing them to flee for their lives.

Thankfully, none of these primordial beasts were anywhere near as persistent as the Gold Devouring Immortal, and at the very most, they would only pursue the flying carriage for a few days before giving up.

Half a month ago, Han Li had flown the carriage into a valley in order to escape from a High Zenith Stage primordial beast.

The valley was quite large, and there was a peaceful ancient forest inside.

However, only after entering the valley did Han Li realize that it was littered with primordial beast carcasses.

This was clearly a terrible sign, but before he had a chance to back out of the valley, countless vines converged from all directions to form a massive cage around the flying carriage.

As it turned out, this forest was actually an incredibly powerful tree demon.

In the end, Han Li was only able to escape from that ordeal after drawing upon the Divine Devilbane Lightning in his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword to conjure up a lightning teleportation array.

Chapter 577: Stuck Between a Rock and a Hard Place

It was a bright and sunny day, and gusts of fierce wind were howling incessantly over a mountain with sparse vegetation, but a thin layer of mist remained lingering in the air despite the ferocity of the wind.

Right at this moment, a streak of green light appeared in the distance, then rapidly approached the mountain before fading to reveal a green jade flying carriage.

Han Li leaped down from the carriage, then inspected his surroundings briefly before making his way over to a large tree that was completely devoid of leaves. He sat down with his back against the tree, then took a pill before closing his eyes to rest.

Jin Tong and Xiao Bai also descended from the flying carriage before arriving by his side.

Both Han Li and Jin Tong appeared to be exhausted, and even Xiao Bai was hanging its head in a lethargic manner as it laid down onto the ground.

Some time later, Han Li exhaled as he opened his eyes, and he was looking a lot more energized than before, but there was still a hint of concern in his eyes.

After a brief hesitation, Jin Tong said, "It's already been over half a year, yet that thing still hasn't moved at all."

"It looks like whoever communicated with me back then had to have been an extremely powerful being. This is a late-High Zenith Stage spirit insect, and even though its spiritual sense is its weakness, it's still an extraordinary feat to trap it in an illusion for so long. It appears the Gold Devouring Immortal really will be trapped in that illusion for 20 years," Han Li mused.

"Is that person really helping us?" Jin Tong asked.

"That's hard to say for now, but given that this is the primordial land, anything is possible," Han Li replied in an ambiguous fashion.

"Even in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, there was so much treachery going on, I don't think anyone in the primordial land would be so kind as to help us for no reason," Jin Tong sighed.

"I wouldn't say that's entirely accurate," Xiao Bai suddenly interjected. "Many of the immortals of the immortal regions appear to be wise and benevolent on the surface, but behind the scenes, they're constantly engaging in treacherous dealings. In contrast, even though the primordial land is constantly ravaged by conflict, everyone is much more forthcoming here."

"Shut your mouth!" Jin Tong snapped as she slapped Xiao Bai on the top of its head. "Have you forgotten what the Beast Race did to us after we helped them?"

"You can't just focus on a single example! The Beast Race is only a tiny race on the outskirts of the primordial land. In contrast, the major primordial races are far more honorable!" Xiao Bai countered.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing mention of the major primordial races, and Jin Tong just so happened to spot the change in his expression, upon which she hurriedly asked, "Have you thought of something, Uncle?"

"Seeing as that person is able to trap the Gold Devouring Immortal for 20 years and was able to communicate directly into my consciousness without my detection, they have to at least be at the late-High Zenith Stage, and they could even be a Great Encompassment Stage being. I've never met anyone of such a lofty cultivation base, but there's a chance that they could be from one of the major primordial races mentioned by Xiao Bai just now," Han Li replied.

"Does it really matter? As long as they're helping us, who cares if they come from a major primordial race or a smaller one? It would be great if they could trap the Gold Devouring Immortal for 200 years, even 2,000 years!" Jin Tong said.

Han Li was rather amused to hear this, and he jibed, "Why 2,000 years and not for the rest of eternity?"

"If I can spend 2,000 years traveling and eating with you, there's a good chance I'll become even more powerful than that thing. Once that time comes, I'll wait for it to deliver itself to me so I can eat it. That would save me the trouble of having to search for it!" Jin Tong replied in a confident manner.

"Are you sure you're not the one who's going to be eaten?" Han Li asked in an exasperated voice.

"For some reason, ever since I could remember, I've always had an innate urge to devour all of the other Gold Devouring Beetles that I encounter, and this urge became even stronger as that thing was pursuing us," Jin Tong replied with a serious expression.

"Perhaps that's simply a mission that all Gold Devouring Beetles share," Han Li mused in a contemplative fashion.

Jin Tong didn't really understand what that meant, but she didn't ponder it, either, as she asked, "What should we do from here, Uncle? Maybe we should listen to whoever helped us and return to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region."

"That's not an option. I'm definitely already a wanted a fugitive in the entire immortal region, so going back would be no different from suicide," Han Li said with a wry smile.

"Then should we keep going forward?" Jin Tong asked.

"After being chased by that Gold Devouring Immortal for so long, we've already completely diverged from the route that we were supposed to take. At our current cultivation bases, if we keep forging ahead blindly, we'll land ourselves in hot water sooner or later. We can't just ignore the advice of someone capable of trapping a late-High Zenith Stage being in an illusion for 20 years," Han Li said.

"Well, what can we do then? Surely you're not planning to just stay here and cultivate!"

"That's exactly what I intend to do!" Han Li declared, much to the astonishment of both Jin Tong and Xiao Bai.

"We're just going to stay here in the middle of nowhere? Is that supposed to be a joke? Besides, we won't be able to make any significant progress in our cultivation in 20 years anyway," Jin Tong said in a concerned manner.

"There are no other feasible options. At this point, we're stuck between a rock and a hard place, and we can't retreat or advance, so we may as well take our chances here. At the very least, I think this is the best way to proceed," Han Li said.

"In that case, I'll place my trust in you, Uncle. You can go into seclusion and focus on your cultivation, I'll make sure you don't get disturbed," Jin Tong vowed as she puffed out her chest in a display of confidence, while Xiao Bai buried its own head under its two front paws, seemingly resigning itself to its fate.

"There's no hurry. We haven't just been traveling aimlessly for the past half a year. During this time, I've been searching for a suitable place to go into seclusion, and I've made my choice, but it's not here," Han Li said with a smile.

"Why not? There aren't any primordial beasts nearby. Isn't this a good place to cultivate in seclusion?" Jin Tong asked with a perplexed expression.

"Do you still remember that ravine that we recently passed by?" Han Li asked.

"I do, it's not far away from the valley where that tree demon was. It was so dark, and even from really far away, it reeked of blood and baleful qi. Surely you're not planning to go into seclusion in there," Jin Tong exclaimed.

"That's right. Here in the primordial land, all of the formidable primordial beasts have their own territories, and generally speaking, they won't encroach upon the territories of others. That tree demon was extremely powerful, and that's why that other primordial beast stopped pursuing us as soon as we entered the tree demon's territory. As long as we stay in its territory, we won't be disturbed by other primordial beasts," Han Li explained.

"That sounds correct, but the tree demon isn't just going to allow us to cultivate on its territory!" Jin Tong countered in a puzzled manner.

"I'm not sure if you noticed, but the tree demon's roots were spread out over the entire valley and even a large area outside the valley, but they didn't extend into that ravine. Do you know why that is?" Han Li asked.

Jin Tong hadn't noticed this at all, and she could only shake her head with an inquisitive expression.

"Water and sunlight are mandatory for the nourishment of all plant life, so plants generally prefer warm and humid environments. That applies even to plant demons. That ravine is extremely dark and completely devoid of sunlight, and that's why the tree demon wasn't willing to extend its roots there," Han Li explained.

"I see," Jin Tong replied with an enlightened expresion.

"More importantly, the ravine is extremely abundant in baleful qi, and that's exactly what I need. Alright, we've taken some time to rest, let's set off for that ravine right away," Han Li declared.

With that, the three of them flew onto the flying carriage, which sped away as a streak of green light.

Around half a month later, the flying carriage drew to a halt in the sky above a ravine that was several dozen kilometers in length and several thousand feet wide.

Han Li was standing at the front of the carriage, looking at the ravine down below with a hesitant expression.

While he had already decided that this was going to be where he went into seclusion, there was still a major element of risk associated with this plan.

The primordial land was rife with formidable beasts, and there was no guarantee that there weren't creatures even more powerful than the tree demon lurking in the ravine. Perhaps it wasn't the lack of sunlight that made the tree demon unwilling to spread its roots here. Instead, perhaps it was wary of some other formidable being inside the ravine.

Han Li shook his head to rid himself of those meddling thoughts. At this point, it was already too late to turn back.

In the next instant, he swooped down into the ravine, and as soon as he entered its depths, he was immediately plunged into darkness.

A nauseating bloody odor permeated throughout the entire ravine alongside an extremely fearsome baleful aura.

Han Li remained completely unfazed as he conjured up an azure light barrier around himself, and only after descending to a depth of close to 10,000 feet did he release his spiritual sense to scour the ravine.

In doing so, he discovered that the ravine was far deeper than he imagined, and not only was it impossible to determine where its bottom laid, Han Li couldn't sense any living beings inside at all.

He continued to descend rapidly along a sheer cliff face of the ravine, and the more he descended the more alarmed he became.

The cliff faces on either side of the ravine were riddled with jagged and uneven rocks, interspersed among which were slightly flatter and more even stone platforms that varied in size.

Littered all over these jagged rocks and stone platforms were piles of skeletons that were burning with fluorescent green flames. There was a huge number of these skeletons, and just like the stone platforms, they also varied drastically in size.

Han Li was rather confused to see this.

Could it be that the baleful qi here was so abundant because this was where the tree demon had been discarding the skeletal remains of its victims?

Chapter 578: Descent

Around 15 minutes later, Han Li descended onto one of the stone platforms protruding out of the cliff face, and he swept a sleeve through the air to scatter the dozens of skeletons on the platform, sending them plunging down deeper into the ravine.

Han Li briefly inspected his surroundings, then swept a sleeve through the air to summon Daoist Xie, Jin Tong, and Xiao Bai amid three streaks of light, two golden and one white.

As soon as Jin Tong appeared, she was immediately struck by a sense of discomfort, and she hurriedly asked, "Where are we, Uncle?"

"There's an extreme abundance of baleful qi here," Daoist Xie remarked with tightly furrowed brows.

"We're already deep within the ravine right now. This amount of baleful qi should still be tolerable for all of you, but if we go any deeper, you run the risk of suffering baleful qi contamination, so I'll leave all of you to stay here for now while I continue my descent," Han Li said.

"Just focus on your cultivation and don't worry about anything else, Uncle," Jin Tong declared with a reassuring nod.

Han Li patted Jin Tong on the head, then turned to Daoist Xie as he said, "Brother Xie, as a safety precaution, I'll have to trouble you to set up an array with me."

Daoist Xie nodded in response.

"Master, this feels like such an eerie place... Is it really alright to stay here?" Xiao Bai suddenly asked in a concerned manner.

"Just as the baleful qi in here is unbearable for all of you, I'm sure the same applies to other primordial beasts as well. On top of that, my spiritual sense wasn't able to detect any living beings in here, so there shouldn't be any problems," Han Li replied.

Xiao Bai nodded silently in response.

"Jin Tong, even though that person told us that the Gold Devouring Immortal will be trapped for 20 years, we can't just take their word for it. Make sure to keep constant tabs on the Gold Devouring Immortal, and if it begins moving, notify me right away," Han Li instructed.

"You can count on me, Uncle," Jin Tong replied with a serious look on her little face.

After that, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce an array plate, following which he and Daoist Xie sprang into action, flying over the cliff faces of the ravine to set up an array.

"Back when I was with Qu Ling, I was always the one doing the hunting, but now that I'm back with Uncle, I've suddenly become the one being hunted," Jin Tong suddenly remarked.

"Are you regretting returning to Master's side?" Xiao Bai asked.

Jin Tong slapped it on the head as she smiled and said, "How could I possibly regret it when being with Uncle is so exciting? Besides, Uncle will definitely find a way out of this predicament, I'm sure of it!"

A faint smile appeared on Xiao Bai's face upon hearing this.

......

A few minutes later, Han Li parted ways with Daoist Xie and Jin Tong, then continued his descent deeper into the ravine.

As he did so, the gusts of wind were sweeping through the air beside him, picking up specks of fluorescent flames from the nearby skeletons before blowing them in different directions.

These specks of green flames resembled stars in the night sky, except they were far more eerie and unsettling to behold.

The deeper Han Li descended into the ravine, the more perplexed he became.

He had thought that there would be an even distribution of baleful qi throughout the entire ravine, but as it turned out, the deeper he went, the denser the surrounding baleful qi became, and strangely enough, the number of skeletal carcasses on the cliff faces on either side were also becoming fewer and fewer.

After descending for about 30 kilometers, all traces of light ceased to exist, and the baleful qi in the surrounding area was so dense that it felt like a suffocating blanket.

At this point, even Han Li was beginning to feel very uncomfortable, despite the fact that he had previously used baleful qi to open up some of his immortal acupoints.

His brows furrowed slightly as he fought through the discomfort and continued his descent.

As he descended, the surrounding baleful qi only continued to grow denser and denser, and even the protective spiritual light around him wasn't able to completely keep it at bay.

As he neared the 50-kilometer mark, the surrounding baleful qi suddenly began to churn violently, and gusts of howling yin wind swept through the air.

The nearby air temperature also plummeted drastically, and a layer of black ice crystals appeared over the cliff faces, while some sections had been so badly frozen that the rock had cracked and split apart.

Han Li was caught completely off guard, and a thick layer of black ice emerged over his body, while all types of violent and aggressive thoughts forced their way into his mind.

All of a sudden, he found himself seeing red, and he felt as if he had been transported to a battlefield riddled with vast mountains of demon beast carcasses and rivers of blood.

At the same time, a chorus of ghostly howls rang out beside his ears.

Before he had a chance to do anything, countless crimson ghostly hands extended out of the mountains of carcasses and rivers of blood, attempting to tear away his sanity.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he remained in a state of lucidity.

He was aware of the detrimental effects that baleful qi contamination could have on one's spiritual sense, and he had already channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique to protect his own mind.

He closed his eyes while focusing on channeling the Spirit Refinement Technique, and a cool and refreshing sensation welled up in his mind, while the horrific illusion of the battlefield began to fade.

However, gusts of yin wind were still sweeping incessantly through the area, and while the illusion was fading, it refused to disappear altogether.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph as he channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique several more times, and the illusion was finally completely dispeled.

With that, he gently exhaled, following which the layer of black ice crystals around him was shattered amid a flash of azure light. However, instead of continuing his descent from there, he peered down into the ravine with a wary look in his eyes.

The baleful qi here was far more formidable than he had anticipated, and if any other mid-Golden Immortal cultivator who hadn't cultivated the Spirit Refinement Technique had been in his place, they would've most likely already been driven insane by the illusion from just now.

Gusts of yin wind were howling incessantly down below alongside clouds of churning black mist, and it was clear that he was far from reaching the bottom of the ravine.

On top of that, the boundless baleful qi and yin wind here severely obstructed his spiritual sense, thereby restricting his spiritual sensory range.

He was originally planning to reach the bottom of the ravine to take advantage of the more abundant baleful qi there to assist in his cultivation, but at this point, he had already reached his limits, and descending any further could result in a complete loss of his sanity.

If the same illusion from before were to present itself to him again in an even stronger form, then he wasn't confident that he would be able to overcome it.

Right as he was hesitating about how to proceed, he suddenly raised an eyebrow as a hint of elation appeared in his eyes.

He had discovered that by overcoming the earlier illusion through channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique, he had made some significant progress in his Spirit Refinement Technique, equivalent to the progress that he had made over the past few years of cultivation!

In this environment, his spiritual sense was constantly on the verge of collapse, and it seemed that this was greatly beneficial for the cultivation of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

His original plan was only to take advantage of the baleful qi in this place to open up more immortal acupoints, so this discovery was certainly a pleasant surprise.

It was extremely rare to see such a vast abundance of baleful qi in any place, and this only made him even more curious about what was at the bottom.

Moments later, Han Li decided to continue in his descent.

This time, he was only able to descend a few more kilometers before the effects of baleful qi contamination began to rear their ugly heads again, and he immediately drew to a halt while simultaneously channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique.

The same illusion of the horrific battlefield had surfaced in his mind, and this one was even stronger than the one from before.

Han Li was channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might to withstand the illusion, and only after close to an entire day had passed did he finally exhale before opening his eyes.

Just as he had anticipated, he had made significant progress in the Spirit Refinement Technique once again.

A hint of elation surfaced in his eyes, and at this rate, it wasn't going to take long before he fully mastered the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

After taking a brief rest, he continued his descent.

The more he descended, the more formidable the surrounding baleful qi and yin wind became, and it was as if this ravine were connected directly to the depths of hell.

Just like before, Han Li would periodically stop at certain points, using the yin wind and baleful qi to assist him in his cultivation of the Spirit Refinement Technique, and using this method, he was able to make rapid progress.

Several months later, Han Li had already reached the pinnacle of the fourth level of the cultivation art, he was only one step away from full mastery.

At this moment, he was standing on a giant rock protruding out of the cliff face, looking down into the ravine below.

By his estimates, he had already descended close to 500 kilometers into the ravine, yet he still didn't appear to be close to the bottom.

He briefly inspected his surroundings, and after some contemplation, he began to descend again.

A short while later, he stopped in his tracks with a surprised expression.

At this point, the ravine had become very narrow, and gusts of yin wind were sweeping through the area, stirring up the nearby baleful qi to form a series of vortexes of different sizes.

The baleful qi here was several times more formidable than before, and the gusts of yin wind were also blowing with increased ferocity.

Bursts of violent intent forced their way into Han Li's mind, and even though he was constantly channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique, he was struggling to retain his sanity.

Before he had a chance to do anything else, an incredibly thick pillar of yin wind suddenly erupted out of the ravine down below before sweeping up his entire body.

A burst of extremely formidable baleful qi surged out of the pillar of yin wind, instantly shattering the defenses of the Spirit Refinement Technique in his mind.

Chapter 579: Succumbing to Depravity

A burst of fierce killing intent instantly flooded into Han Li's mind.

His eyes quickly turned bloodshot, while his vision blurred, and he was once again thrust into another illusion.

All around him was a sea of blood with countless demon beast skeletons and carcasses submerged within, and the entire surrounding area was filled with the nauseating stench of blood and gore.

Han Li immediately bit down onto the tip of his own tongue, using the pain to help him recover some of his lucidity. At the same time, he was channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique to protect his own mind as much as possible, but as he swept his gaze over his surroundings, his pupils instantly contracted slightly.

The previous illusions had been able to affect his mind, but they were still tolerable, and he was able to free himself from them by channeling the Spirit Refinement Technique.

However, this illusion was different. He seemed to have fallen completely into it, and it wasn't going to be so easy to break free.

Even though he was doing everything in his power to cling to his sanity, he could feel all of the blood in his entire body churning violently, and a wave of irrepressible fury rose up in his heart with such ferocity that it felt as if it were about to tear his chest apart.

He had experienced something like this before, back when he had been struck by that abrupt onset of Spirit Refinement Technique backlash in the Black Wind Sea. However, that problem should've already been ironed out through his cultivation of the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, at least on a temporary basis.

Could it be that this illusion was forcibly triggering premature backlash from his Spirit Refinement Technique?

With that in mind, Han Li hurriedly channeled the Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might, and a cool and refreshing sensation coursed through his mind to slowly snuff out the fury in his heart.

After that, he began to ponder how he could break free from this illusion.

Right at this moment, a burst of splashing rang out nearby, and Han Li turned to discover that a demonic wolf carcass that was over 100 feet in length had slowly stood up within the sea of blood not far away.

Two specks of eerie red light appeared in its eye sockets, and it let loose a ferocious roar before pouncing at Han Li, who flicked a finger through the air, releasing a streak of azure light to slice the demonic wolf carcass in half.

Immediately thereafter, two more demon beast carcasses rose to their haunches before launching themselves at Han Li, and they were also promptly slain.

However, before Han Li had a chance to do anything else, more and more carcasses came pouncing at him from all directions, and he was forced to retaliate, striking them down one after another.

Initially, these carcasses weren't all that powerful, but as more and more of them sprang to life, they also became progressively more formidable, and before long, there were even some True Immortal and Golden Immortal Stage demon beast carcasses among their ranks.

At this point, Han Li had already adopted his Giant Mountain Ape form, and he was swinging his enormous golden fists through the sea of blood around him, eradicating all of the surrounding carcasses.

However, there seemed to be no end to these carcasses, and it didn't take long before he was completely surrounded.

Right at this moment, a green tail that was over 1,000 feet in length abruptly emerged from the sea of blood down below, then swept toward him with tremendous force.

Han Li was busy warding off other attacks, so he could only launch a hurried punch at the sweeping tail to release a golden fist projection, and a resounding boom rang out as the fist projection clashed against the giant tail, upon which the former was instantly shattered like an egg.

As for the massive tail, it wasn't even slowed down in the slightest as it crashed straight into Han Li's side, sending him flying like a ragdoll into the throngs of demon beast carcasses in that direction.

The nearby carcasses immediately began roaring with excitement as they piled onto all at once, completely inundating him before tearing at his flesh in a frenzy.

The Giant Mountain Ape was normally renowned for its incredible physical constitution, yet in this moment, its defenses had become extremely frail, and almost in the blink of an eye, most of its flesh had been torn away, revealing the bone underneath.

Han Li was furious, and his arms glowed with radiant golden light as he lashed out in all directions.

A burst of tremendous power erupted out of the golden light, causing the surrounding space to warp and rumble violently.

All of the nearby carcasses were sent flying, while the giant golden ape sprang up to a higher elevation, allowing it temporarily free itself from the encirclement.

Han Li looked down at his own severely ravaged body, and the fury in his eyes gradually faded.

Even though half of his body had gone missing, he didn't feel as if he had suffered any severe injuries, and his body instantly reverted back to normal amid a flash of golden light.

He immediately realized that he had been swept up in the heat of the moment, and as a result, he had forgotten that he was in an illusion.

Of course, the main reason why he had almost fallen prey to the illusion was the mental disturbance that had been caused by the premature onset of Spirit Refinement Technique backlash.

If he were to allow himself to get lost in this illusion, then he would never be able to break free from it.

Before he had a chance to ponder the subject any further, all of the demon beast carcasses came springing up at him once again from down below.

Han Li exhaled as he closed his eyes while channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might, paying no heed to all of the converging carcasses.

A glimmer of translucent light emerged on his glabella, then quickly expanded and grew brighter until it was as radiant and blinding as the sun.

The group of demon beast carcasses that were charging at the forefront were only around 10 feet away from Han Li at this point, and as soon as the translucent light shone upon them, they immediately began screeching with agony before being reduced to dust in the blink of an eye.

The rest of the demon beast carcasses hurriedly shot back in retreat upon seeing this, flying deep into the sea of blood, not daring to show themselves again.

All of a sudden, not a single carcass could be seen, and all that remained was the sea of blood peacefully rippling around him.

Moments later, Han Li's eyes abruptly sprang open, and there was radiant golden light glowing within them. His gaze quickly roamed over the surrounding area, following which a thick beam of translucent light erupted out of his glabella, forming a giant translucent blade that was over 1,000 feet in length before striking the space directly up ahead.

The crimson space in the path of the translucent blade rippled momentarily, but then instantly returned to normal.

Even though Han Li was unable to tear the space open, he was very much encouraged to see this, and his glabella lit up once again, but right at this moment, the sea of blood down below suddenly began to churn and bubble violently.

Immediately thereafter, a mountainous green carcass slowly began to emerge from the depths.

The carcass belonged to an enormous green rat with an almost entirely decomposed body. There were two balls of green and red flames burning within its eye sockets, presenting a very peculiar sight to behold, and there was a massive green tail that was just as long as the rat itself trailing along behind it.

The giant green rat was giving off an enormous aura that caused the nearby space to tremble and groan incessantly, as if the very space itself were unable to bear the enormity of its aura.

The aura of the green rat was far more formidable than that of the High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal, and among all of the powerful beings that Han Li had seen, perhaps only Immortal Lord Miro could compare with it.

Despite his alarm, Han Li didn't panic.

Regardless of how formidable this giant green rat was, it was nothing but an illusion.

Upon spotting the tail trailing along behind the rat, he immediately realized that this was the very same tail that had sent him flying earlier.

Right at this moment, the giant rat's eyes lit up, and it pounced at Han Li as an enormous green shadow.

Han Li immediately made a hand seal, and a thick pillar of translucent light shot out of his glabella before striking the green rat directly on the head.

However, the giant rat merely opened its mouth to swallow the pillar of light, and it wasn't slowed down in the slightest as it crashed straight into Han Li like an enormous meteorite.

Han Li's glabella lit up once again, and a huge shield of translucent light was conjured up in front of him.

However, as soon as the translucent shield took shape, it was instantly shattered, following which a burst of tremendous force crashed into Han Li's body, sending him flying for close to 10 kilometers before he was finally able to steady himself.

Before he had a chance to retaliate, a long green shadow shot forth like lightning before piercing straight through his body. The green shadow had come out of the giant rat's mouth and, and it appeared to be the rat's tongue, but there was a layer of green flames burning over it.

Han Li instantly felt a burst of scorching pain flare up in his mind, as if his entire soul were being incinerated, and he couldn't help but give a muffled groan. However, he was able to suppress the pain as he reached out with both hands to grab onto the green tongue, but before he could rip the tongue into two, it wrapped itself around his hands like a spirit snake, then rapidly wrapped itself around the rest of his body as well.

Immediately thereafter, the green rat opened its mouth to produce a burst of immense suction force that acted upon Han Li, while its tongue was also rapidly retracted.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li was sucked into the giant rat's mouth.

His vision blurred momentarily, following which he found himself in a dark space, surrounded by decomposing chunks of dark purple flesh, which were constantly exuding putrid and nauseating pus.

Bursts of tremendous force were also compressing toward him from all directions, and he remained firmly tied up by the green tongue.

Han Li fought back his disgust as he struggled with all his might, but to no avail, and his heart immediately sank.

However, he then suddenly ceased all struggles and closed his eyes, seemingly resigning himself to his fate.

All of a sudden, bursts of green flames appeared all around him, and they landed upon his body, setting him alight.

The green flames were giving off incredible heat that directly scorched Han Li's soul, and the pain was so unbearable that he couldn't help but give a muffled groan.

Chapter 580: From Crisis to Fortune

Han Li gritted his teeth in agony before abruptly letting loose a thunderous roar, and a shimmering golden nascent soul suddenly emerged from the top of his head.

The nascent soul had a grim look on its face, and it rubbed its hands together, following which a burst of golden light flashed through its eyes before it vanished into Han Li's body again.

In the next instant, Han Li felt a cool and refreshing sensation spreading through his spiritual sense, slightly counteracting the scorching pain that was ravaging his soul.

However, the heat radiating from the green flames was only becoming more and more intense, and it was impossible to alleviate, even as Han Li channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might.

At this point, Han Li had already conjured up his True Extreme Film to help him withstand the tremendous compressive force that was acting upon him from all directions, but he was still trembling uncontrollably, while cracks and pops were ringing out incessantly from within his body, as if all of his bone were about to be shattered.

Time passed by in an agonizingly slow fashion.

All of a sudden, Han Li shuddered as a twisted look appeared on his face.

The heat in his spiritual sense had risen to a terrifying degree, and he felt as if his entire soul were slowly shrinking amid the unbearable heat.

His consciousness slowly began to blur, as if it were slowly leaving his body, but right at this moment, what appeared to be the sound of something shattering rang out deep within his soul.

A speck of translucent light then abruptly emerged somewhere in his spiritual sense, and it began to release a burst of suction force.

The scorching heat that permeated throughout his spiritual sense seemed to have suddenly found an outlet, and it surged toward the speck of translucent light in a frenzy to form a scorching vortex.

In the span of just a few seconds, all of the scorching heat in Han Li's mind had faded, and the twisted look on his face also disappeared.

Immediately thereafter, a resounding boom rang out from within his soul, and it was rapidly being enhanced and elevated to a whole new level.

Only after around 15 minutes had passed did these changes gradually subside, and everything returned to normal.

Han Li slowly opened his eyes, and he was ecstatic to discover that not only had his consciousness returned to normal, his spiritual sense had become two to three times more powerful than before.

It was as if there were countless glittering and translucent streams flowing through his mind, giving off tremendous spiritual sense fluctuations.

Never had he anticipated that he would achieve full mastery of the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique while on the brink of disaster.

Perhaps the reason why he hadn't been able to reach this step up to this point was because his spiritual sense was too powerful, so he had never been in a situation where his soul had been on the verge of collapse.

In his desperation to attain more power in order to stand a chance against the Gold Devouring Immortal, he had ventured deep into this mysterious ravine, and in an enormous stroke of luck, it had allowed him to achieve full mastery of the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Han Li swept his gaze over his surroundings, following which his glabella began to glow brightly, and bursts of radiant translucent light shot out from within like sharp swords in all directions.

All of a sudden, bursts of blinding translucent light erupted out of the giant green rat's body, following which it exploded violently into streams of green light that flew away in all directions.

Before long, Han Li was revealed, having already reverted back to his human form.

Piercing translucent light was radiating from his body, illuminating the surrounding crimson space.

All of a sudden, he made a hand seal, and the translucent light converged to form an enormous sword that was able to instantly slice the crimson space apart.

Han Li's vision blurred momentarily, and in the next instant, he found himself back in the dark ravine.

He gently exhaled as he inspected his surroundings momentarily, then descended onto a nearby protruding cliff before sitting down with his legs crossed.

With his current drastically enhanced spiritual sense, the surrounding yin wind and baleful qi were no longer able to affect him.

He closed his eyes to carefully experience the enormous spiritual sense in his mind, and he was ecstatic with what he saw.

Moments later, his eyes abruptly sprang open, and a burst of translucent light flashed over his glabella, following which a radiant translucent sword projection shot forth, vanishing into the black mist in a flash before racing up the ravine.

High up in the sky above the ravine, a True Immortal Stage azure eagle was flying past when the translucent sword projection suddenly pierced straight into its head, and it was only able to muster up a cry of shock and agony before the light in its eyes completely faded.

At the same time, its aura also vanished, and its lifeless body tumbled down into the forest that was actually the body of the tree demon.

The vines and branches in the forest immediately awakened, and they converged to ensnare the body of the azure eagle in a cocoon, following which a string of grotesque crunching sounds rang out.

Inside the ravine, a hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes.

With his significantly enhanced spiritual sense, his Sword Observation Art had become several times more powerful, making it an even more effective weapon against the Gold Devouring Immortal.

After that, he tested out a few more spiritual attacks, all of which had also become immensely more powerful.

Following his experimentation, he closed his eyes once again, and moments later, several translucent chains shot out of his glabella, then quickly intertwined with one another to form a rectangular cage.

The chains were riddled with barely distinguishable black runes that were giving off a faint black glow, which intertwined with the translucent light emanating from the chains, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the cage of chains, which was hovering in mid-air, then pointed a finger in its direction, and the cage instantly split back up into several translucent chains before vanishing into thin air.

Deep within the forest outside the ravine was a huge tree that stood at several thousand feet tall. The tree had an extremely dense canopy, and the trunk was as green as jade, as were all of its branches and leaves. Furthermore, there was an enormous face on the trunk of the tree.

At this moment, the eyes of the face were tightly shut, and a snoring sound was coming out of its half-agape mouth, indicating that it seemed to be sleeping.

Right at this moment, several translucent chains emerged beside the tree amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, then vanished into the tree in a flash.

The giant face on the tree instantly opened its eyes as it let loose a roar of alarm and fury, and its thick branches began to flail around violently like arms.

At the same time, an immense High Zenith Stage aura erupted out of its body, and bursts of green light shot out of the tree's trunk in a frenzy before landing in the nearby valley.

Everything that came into contact with this green light was instantly destroyed, and the earth in a radius of several hundred kilometers rumbled and quaked violently, sending huge clouds of dust rising up into the air.

However, in the next instant, the flailing branches of the giant tree suddenly stopped moving, and the expression on its face also abruptly stiffened, but the radiant green light glowing from the tree and its immense aura still remained.

Deep within the giant tree was a green space that was filled with dense green mist, and hovering at the center of the mist was a green soul in the form of a humanoid tree.

However, at this moment, the soul was trapped in a cage formed by translucent chains, and the cage was giving off a layer of translucent light that isolated the green soul from the sea of mist outside.

The green soul was struggling frantically within the cage, taking on all types of different forms to try and break free, but no matter what it tried, its efforts proved to be completely futile.

After briefly trapping the soul for some time, the cage suddenly split back up into several translucent chains that vanished into thin air.

The tree demon was instantly able to move again, and a confused look appeared in its eyes as it scoured its surroundings in a perplexed fashion.

......

Deep within the ravine.

The translucent chains appeared beside Han Li in a flash, then immediately vanished into his body.

His complexion was rather pale, but there was a hint of elation on his face.

That cage just now was a secret technique called the Spiritual Sense Cage, which could only be unleashed after mastering the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique. It was capable of trapping enemy souls to temporarily sever the connection between their body and their soul.

While it was true that the tree demon had been caught completely off guard, the fact that this secret technique was able to temporarily seal away the soul of a High Zenith Stage being was still a testament to its immense power.

After taking a brief moment to catch his breath, Han Li's complexion gradually began to recover, and a contemplative look appeared in his eyes.

The secret technique was very powerful, but it was also extremely taxing on his spiritual sense. Even though he had only unleashed it for a very short time, only 30% of his spiritual sense remained, and it was going to take at least a month for him to recover.

However, this was still very much a worthy trade.

After sitting in silence for a moment, Han Li summoned a black jade slip before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

This jade slip contained the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

The Spirit Refinement Technique was far more powerful than Han Li had anticipated. Originally, he had been planning to take advantage of the vast abundance of baleful qi here to open up more immortal acupoints, but it seemed like cultivating the Spirit Refinement Technique was actually the better option.

After reading through the entire fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly with concern.

The contents of the fifth level were far deeper and more difficult to grasp than the fourth level. Having said that, Han Li had seen countless profound cultivation arts in the past, and no matter how difficult the fifth level was to grasp, it had to be a continuation of the fourth level, so it shouldn't be a problem for him to interpret it as long as he was willing to spend the time.

With that in mind, he injected his spiritual sense into the jade slip once again.

Chapter 581: Gathering of Immortals

Around an hour ago, right when Han Li achieved full mastery of the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Countless kilometers away from the ravine that Han Li was in, there stood a white mountain that reached all the way up into the clouds.

On the mountain summit was an azure platform that had been constructed out of stone blocks, and at the center of the platform was a square stone table, around which were placed four stone chairs of the same style, but in different colors.

At this moment, three of the stone chairs were occupied.

One of them was occupied by a black-robed young man with a dark complexion. He had a pair of silver horns on his head, and there was a very cold and inhospitable air about him.

The second chair was occupied by a white-robed man who appeared to be 30 to 40 years of age. He was extremely handsome, with a head of flowing white hair, down the middle of which was a lock of eye-catching golden hair.

The final person to complete the trio was a hunch-backed elderly man with red hair and a red beard, holding a crimson cane in one hand.

Hovering above the stone table in front of the trio was a white mirror of water, within which was a swirling expanse of white light.

A dark ravine could just barely be made out beneath the white light, and there were wisps of black qi drifting out of the ravine.

"Those are some very powerful spiritual sense fluctuations... Could it be that someone on Old Man Gu's territory made a breakthrough to the Great Encompassment Stage?" the black-robed young man mused.

"A breakthrough to the Great Encompassment Stage would've triggered far more significant phenomena. If you ask me, this looks like something that would arise from someone cultivating some type of spiritual secret technique," the white-robed man said.

The black-robed man's brows furrowed slightly as he took a glance at the white-robed, then gave a cold harrumph.

The white-robed man paid no heed to him as he turned to the red-haired elderly man and asked, "What do you think, Brother Yu?"

"I'm not too sure what to make of this, but seeing as this is happening on Fellow Daoist Gu's territory, we're in no position to intervene," the red-haired man replied in an ambiguous fashion.

"Today is our once-in-a-million-year gathering, yet Fellow Daoist Gu has already been absent several times in succession, and now, something strange seems to be happening on his territory. I really do wonder what he's up to," the white-robed man sighed as he shook his head with a resigned smile.

"Don't mind him, Fellow Daoist Gu has always been a very mysterious man," the red-haired elderly man chuckled.

"Maybe you should mind your own business instead of prying into Old Man Gu's matters, Brother Liu. Recently, one of your subsidiary branches in the Dark Star Mountain Range suddenly attacked and took over the entire Insect Race territory in that area. How do you explain that, Brother Liu?" the black-robed young man asked.

"So that's what's on your mind! I was wondering why you were being so hostile to me. Both of us have countless descendants spread across the vast primordial land, and they've always lived and died by the laws of natural selection, so why concern yourself with these matters? If you're truly bothered by this, then just send some of your people to recover the territory," the white-robed man replied with a nonchalant smile.

"In that case, I don't believe there's any need for this gathering to drag on any longer. I'll be going ahead now," the black-robed man declared as he suddenly rose to his feet, then abruptly vanished into thin air.

"Looks like Brother Zuo's temper is still as fiery as ever. Brother Liu, I'll also be taking my leave now. See you in a million years," the red-haired elderly man said as he also rose to his feet, then waved his cane through the air, and a white spatial rift appeared in front of him, then slowly widened to form a spatial passageway.

After that, the red-haired elderly man calmly stepped into the spatial passageway and departed as well.

Meanwhile, a faint smile appeared on the white-robed man's face as he mused, "That human brat is quite brave. He's neither advancing or retreating, instead choosing to remain where he is to cultivate. Let's see if he has what it takes to dig himself out of this hole."

As soon as his voice trailed off, the white mirror hovering above the platform abruptly vanished, and the white-robed man was also nowhere to be seen.

......

It took Han Li around half a month to fully comprehend the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

His spiritual sense was far superior to that of the average Golden Immortal to begin with, and now that he had mastered the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, he naturally fulfilled the spiritual sense prerequisites to cultivate the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

However, the fifth level of the cultivation art was extremely complex, and it seemed that many risks also had to be taken during its cultivation, and that left him a little hesitant about how to proceed.

However, given the impact that the baleful qi in the ravine had on his spiritual sense, it occurred to Han Li that perhaps he could further enhance his own spiritual sense by descending deeper into the ravine.

With that in mind, he stowed the jade slip away, then rose to his feet and recommenced his descent.

However, it didn't take long before Han Li's brows began to furrow slightly, and as he continued his descent, the concern on his face only grew more pronounced.

Contrary to his expectations, the yin winds deeper in the ravine had only become weaker instead of stronger.

Even though the baleful qi was only becoming denser the deeper he went, without those yin winds to complement it, the baleful qi alone wasn't sufficient to conjure up those illusions in his mind.

A disappointed look appeared on Han Li's face, and after a brief pause, he returned to the depth where the yin wind was strongest before sitting down with his legs crossed to try and cultivate the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Half a year flew by in a flash.

As Han Li opened his eyes, a rather frustrated look appeared on his face.

During the past six months, he had been cultivating constantly without rest, but progress had been extremely slow. Not only was progress far slower than when he was able to take advantage of those baleful qi illusions to cultivate the Spirit Refinement Technique, it was significantly slower than even under normal circumstances.

Han Li took a deep breath to compose himself.

Back when he was cultivating the third level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, he had encountered the same problem, but eventually, he was able to master the third level with enough time. However, in this situation, he simply didn't have time to make slow and steady progress.

After some contemplation, he made a hand seal, and his body shuddered slightly, following which all of the surrounding baleful qi abruptly converged toward him, inundating him in the blink of an eye.

All of a sudden, he felt as if he could hear the blood-hurdling howls of countless demon beasts ringing out beside his ears, and at the same time, bursts of sinister and violent intent began infiltrating all parts of his body.

He took a deep breath and didn't channel any of his cultivation arts to defend himself.

Bursts of dense baleful qi surged erratically throughout his body, and it felt as if there were countless tiny daggers twisting in his meridians.

His brows furrowed slightly, but then quickly unfurrowed again, and he promptly devoured a cultivation enhancement pill before channeling his Profound Baleful Spirit Arts.

All of the baleful qi that had accumulated in his body instantly erupted forth, manifesting itself as a vast expanse of black light that resembled a cloud of dense mist.

The black light instantly fused as one with the surrounding baleful qi, stirring up the nearby baleful qi into a frenzy, causing them to form a series of vortexes around him before surging into his body at an even faster rate than before.

All of a sudden, Han Li was completely inundated by a dense black cloud, and he felt as if there were countless needles piercing into his skin.

As he continued to channel the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts, the bursts of erratic baleful qi in his body began to converge toward a single point, forming a vast wave of baleful qi.

He couldn't help but give a muffled groan, and his brows became tightly furrowed with agony.

Earlier, the bursts of baleful qi had been spread out all over his body, and they had caused him some pain, but it wasn't all that severe. However, now that all of the baleful qi had converged to one place, the pain was far more unbearable than before.

Thankfully, there didn't seem to be any other detrimental effects aside from the excruciating pain for now, and Han Li was able to grit his teeth and persevere as he directed the baleful qi toward his 62nd immortal acupoint.

He was well aware of the fact that because this was extraneous baleful qi that he hadn't accumulated in his body, he would instinctively reject it. On top of that, this extraneous baleful qi was only going to be even more ferocious and untamed than the baleful qi that was already in his body.

Similarly, the sinister and violent intent imbued in this baleful qi was only going to be even more ferocious, and if he wasn't careful, it could easily overwhelm his immortal acupoints and completely destroy his consciousness.

However, time was of the essence here, and extreme measures had to be taken, so despite the severe degree of risk involved, he was still planning to use this extraneous baleful qi to help him open up his immortal acupoints.

"It's... still... not enough..." Han Li spat through gritted teeth with tightly furrowed brows.

He made a rapid string of hand seals, and the black light around him brightened significantly, while the rate of influx of baleful qi sped up by twofold, but at the same time, the pain also became twice as unbearable.

Han Li forcibly suppressed the excruciating pain as he continued to absorb more baleful qi into his own body before channeling it toward his immortal acupoint.

The baleful qi within the ravine began to churn violently, causing the demon beast carcasses on the cliff faces on either side of the ravine to tumble down before shattering into powdered bone and specks of fluorescent flames in mid-air.

As time slowly passed, the baleful qi in the surrounding area began to thin out, while the baleful qi directly around Han Li became denser and denser.

Over three months passed by in a flash.

On this day, a resounding boom suddenly rang out within the ravine.

Deep within the ravine, Han Li was hovering in mid-air, and a small vortex was taking shape on his back beneath his shoulder blades. The vortex was voraciously absorbing the world's origin qi that was surging down from above the ravine, and only after close to 20 seconds had passed did the influx of the world's origin qi slowly subside.

At this point, the vortex had been replaced by a speck of golden light, and it was none other than Han Li's 62nd immortal acupoint!

Han Li took a moment to inspect the immortal acupoint, and he discovered that aside from the vast amount of immortal spiritual power within it, there was a large quantity of baleful qi as well, far more than what was present in his previous immortal acupoints.

It was clear that opening acupoints using extraneous baleful qi was different from doing so using one's innate baleful qi.

Chapter 582: No Turning Back

Han Li shook his head and set aside his concerns for now, then summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, upon which he discovered that two more Time Dao Runes had appeared on its surface.

He then gently exhaled before casting his gaze down into the dark ravine below.

Due to the fact that the baleful qi at this altitude had virtually been completely absorbed by Han Li, the baleful qi down below was quickly rising up to fill the void left behind. Despite this, Han Li was still unable to see the bottom of the ravine from where he was.

After devouring a pill and taking some time to rest, Han Li rose to his feet, then plunged rapidly down into the depths of the ravine, instantly sinking into the boundless baleful qi down below.

Just as he had anticipated, the deeper he descended, the more viscous the surrounding baleful qi became.

After descending for only around 30 kilometers, he could already sense that the yin winds and baleful qi swirling around him had become several times more powerful than before, and all types of horrific illusions began to surface in his mind again.

However, with his current spiritual sense, he had become significantly more impervious to these illusions, and he continued descending without pause.

After descending for close to another 20 kilometers, the surrounding yin winds subsided somewhat once again, but the baleful qi in the area had become even denser, to the point that Han Li felt as if he were encountering physical resistance in his descent.

Right at this moment, numerous specks of green light suddenly appeared directly in front of him, and they quickly converged to form the same giant green rat from before.

However, this time, it was several times more massive than before, and its body was so severely charred and ravaged that it looked as if hot oil had been poured all over it. The skin and fur on its face had been completely stripped away, and its two massive eyeballs looked as if they could fall out of its eye sockets at any moment.

A sharp screeching sound rang out as the giant rat came charging directly at Han Li, bringing along with it an indescribable odor of blood and gore, an odor so intense that Han Li felt as if there were a boundless wave of blood crashing toward him.

However, Han Li was already mentally prepared, and he remained completely unfazed as he channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique while letting loose a thunderous roar.

A burst of tremendous spiritual sense instantly swept through his consciousness, cleansing his mind like a storm on a hot summer's day.

The giant rat illusion was instantly dispeled before it could reach Han Li, and he took only a brief moment to compose himself before continuing his descent.

He knew that the purer and denser the baleful qi he had access to, the quicker he would be able to open his immortal acupoints and elevate his own cultivation base.

Time was quickly ticking down, and he had to make the most of every single moment. The more power that he could attain, the greater his chances of surviving this ordeal.

However, he was forced to draw to a halt after descending for only several thousand more feet.

This time, what had stopped him wasn't an illusion. Instead, it was the baleful qi, which had become dense to the extreme.

The baleful qi that was currently beneath him wasn't even present in the form of mist anymore. Instead, it resembled an unmoving black wall that was formed by solidified ink.

Han Li could clearly sense that the baleful qi within this wall was different from the baleful qi that was currently swirling around him, but he couldn't put his finger on exactly what was different.

After a brief moment of hesitation, he leaned down before attempting to plunge one of his hands into the wall.

However, as soon as he reached into the wall of baleful qi, his wrist and hand were instantly struck by a burst of sharp, bone-chilling pain as the surrounding baleful qi morphed themselves into sharp needles as if they were living creatures, then pierced themselves into his skin.

Han Li shuddered as he hurriedly attempted to withdraw his hand, only to discover that he was unable to do so as his hand had somehow been locked into place.

He immediately activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, upon which he discovered that those needles of baleful qi were anchoring his hand firmly into place, rendering it completely immobilized.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as a bolt of golden lightning shot out of the palm of his hand, and the intrusive needles of baleful qi immediately sprang back in the face of his Divine Devilbane Lightning, but they were still circling around his hand like a pack of predators stalking their prey.

Han Li took advantage of this opportunity to pull back his hand, and his pupils immediately contracted slightly in response to what he saw.

At this moment, the palm of his hand was riddled with countless tiny red spots, all of which were tiny holes as thin as strands of hair. As it turned out, the needles of baleful qi had pierced all the way through his hand, and there were wisps of black qi permeating throughout these tiny holes.

Another burst of Divine Devilbane Lightning erupted out of his hand, and the residual wisps of baleful qi were instantly eradicated, while the tiny holes on his hand also quickly healed, but there was still a hint of lingering fear in Han Li's eyes.

If he hadn't reacted as quickly as he did, then this hand would've been completely destroyed.

It seemed that the deeper he went, the more aggressive the baleful qi became, and at this point, the baleful qi was actively invading his body without requiring any guidance. With that in mind, it most likely wasn't going to be a simple task to control the baleful qi here and guide it toward his immortal acupoints.

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face as he stared at the black wall down below.

If he were to allow the baleful qi within the black wall to infiltrate his body, then he would be taking a huge risk, and he could easily fall to his demise. However, if he could control the baleful qi here, then he would undoubtedly be able to make rapid progress in opening further immortal acupoints.

After grappling with this dilemma for some time, Han Li finally made up his mind.

At this point, there really was no turning back. He had already chosen to place all of his eggs in one basket, so he could only continue down the path of no return.

With his mind made up, Han Li plunged straight into the black wall without any further hesitation.

As soon as he entered the black wall, he immediately felt as if an enormous weight had crashed down onto his consciousness. A sharp screeching sound was reverberating incessantly in his mind, and he felt as if he had been robbed of all of his senses.

His entire body was enveloped in viscous baleful qi, which formed countless sharp needles that pierced through his skin and flesh, all the way until they reached his bones.

The physical and spiritual pain from the experience was so immense that Han Li immediately began to tremble uncontrollably, and his consciousness was on the verge of fading away.

He gritted his teeth with all his mind, and with his final shred of lucidity, he began to channel his Spirit Refinement Technique.

As soon as he did this, he immediately felt as if a gust of wind were sweeping through his consciousness, instantly silencing the sharp ringing sound while also restoring his spiritual sense to its normal state.

With his spiritual sense recovered, he was able to protect his own mind while simultaneously channeling the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts, guiding the immense baleful qi in his body toward his 63rd immortal acupoint.

However, to his alarm and horror, only a part of the baleful qi in his body was successfully guided toward his immortal acupoint, while the rest continued to surge toward all parts of his body in a completely unrestrained fashion.

A string of loud cracks and pops instantly rang out from within Han Li's body, and a series of massive bulges began to appear beneath his skin.

As a result, his body began to inflate rapidly like a balloon, and it looked as if he were about to explode at any moment.

Despite his alarm, Han Li was able to remain composed, and he began to make a rapid string of hand seals in an attempt to control the baleful qi that was continuing to surge into his body, but at this moment, his body was like a broken dam that was impossible to seal.

His body continued to swell further and further, but at the same time, a small vortex had appeared on his shoulder, and it was absorbing a portion of the incoming baleful qi.

That vortex was actually another one of Han Li's immortal acupoints. Due to the excessive influx of baleful qi, that immortal acupoint had opened up on its own, and it was absorbing baleful qi as quickly as it could alongside Han Li's 63rd immortal acupoint.

Han Li gritted his teeth tightly as he persevered through the excruciating pain. At the same time, he was channeling his Profound Baleful Spirit Arts with all his might, trying to guide as much of the baleful qi in his body toward the two immortal acupoints as possible.

......

Over 10 years flew by in a flash.

Jin Tong was seated with her legs crossed on the cliff at the entrance of the ravine, and in a rare display of discipline, she was cultivating through seated meditation.

Xiao Bai was laying on the ground not far away from her with its front paws resting beneath its chin, and it seemed to have fallen asleep.

Right at this moment, a burst of golden light descended from above before landing on the cliff.

Xiao Bai took a glance to discover that it was Daoist Xie, who had returned from examining the array, then closed its eyes again. Meanwhile, Jin Tong's eyes remained closed the entire time.

Right at this moment, a burst of rumbling akin to resounding thunderclaps rang out from deep within the ravine, immediately following which a cloud of baleful qi rose up from down below, all the way until it spilled over the edge of the cliff.

Only then did Jin Tong's eyes spring open, and she jumped to her feet, then rushed over to the edge of the cliff before peering down into the ravine with an anxious expression.

Xiao Bai had also gotten up from the ground, and it jogged over to her side before casting its gaze into the ravine as well.

"Uncle..." Jin Tong murmured to herself with a complex look on her face, one that was a combination of anticipation, concern, excitement, and unease.

Chapter 583: Bottom of the Ravine

A resounding boom rang out as the sky above the ravine shuddered, and wisps of the world's origin qi that were visible to the naked eye converged from all directions, forming an enormous funnel in the sky, directing a vast quantity of the world's origin qi into the ravine.

In the valley not far away from the ravine, a giant human face appeared on a huge tree, then cast its gaze toward the ravine. The root system beneath it also began to rustle violently as the entire tree moved toward the ravine.

The ground within the valley split open as the trees on either side moved back to clear a wide path, allowing the giant tree demon free passage.

There was a perplexed look on the tree demon's faces as it rushed through the valley, but it suddenly stopped cold in its tracks as it discovered that the vast funnel of the world's origin qi was hovering directly above the ravine that was filled with baleful qi.

A wary look appeared on its face upon seeing this, and after a brief hesitation, it suddenly turned around before rushing back into the valley.

Meanwhile, hundreds of kilometers deep in the ravine, Han Li was standing in mid-air, glowing as brightly as the sun, and the golden light radiating from his body was keeping all of the surrounding baleful qi over 100 feet away from him.

The radiant golden light formed countless threads that intertwined with one another to create a golden cocoon that enveloped his entire body, and only a faint silhouette was visible through it.

The vast world's origin qi that had been funneled into the area came cascading down like an enormous golden waterfall, forming a massive rippling vortex around the golden cocoon.

No light had reached this point in the ravine for countless years, yet the entire area was suddenly illuminated by the radiant golden light, and even though it was unable to completely shine through the dense baleful qi, it was still a stunning sight to behold.

The golden waterfall continued to cascade down for three whole days before finally fading, following which a roar of exaltation suddenly rang out from within the ravine.

A burst of scorching golden light rose up within the giant golden cocoon, and it swept through the cocoon like a sword to slice it into two.

Han Li flew out of the cocoon with golden light flashing in his eyes, then opened his mouth to release a burst of tremendous suction force, drawing all of the golden light in the ravine into his belly, and the golden cocoon also disintegrated into specks of golden light before surging into his mouth.

At the same time, a speck of golden light appeared on his back, and it was flashing incessantly while absorbing the residual world's origin qi in the air.

With that, his 84th immortal acupoint had finally been opened!

Just like his previous immortal acupoints, this one also had some hints of black baleful qi within it, and it was actually even more apparent in this particular immortal acupoint.

Han Li swept a hand through the air with a calm expression, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared in front of him amid a flash of golden light, then began to revolve on the spot while releasing waves of golden ripples.

At this point, there were over 400 Time Dao Runes on the axis, and all of them lit up in unison. At the same time, there were also now as many as 18 time law threads wrapped around the Mantra Treasured Axis.

Han Li raised a hand to make a beckoning motion, and the 18 time law threads immediately turned as straight as arrows before flying toward him, only to curl around his fingers upon reaching him.

Sensing the energy fluctuations emanating from the time law threads, Han Li murmured to himself, "I didn't think that I would attain so many additional time law threads by mastering the fourth level of the Mantra Axis Scripture. Now that the Mantra Treasured Axis has become even more powerful, I'll stand a better chance against the Gold Devouring Immortal."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he swept a sleeve through the air to stow the Mantra Treasured Axis away again.

As all of the golden light around him faded, the surrounding baleful qi converged once again to inundate him.

Han Li had absorbed much of the baleful qi in this area, so it wasn't as dense as it had originally been, but down below was still a vast expanse of impenetrable darkness, and it seemed that the density of the baleful qi deeper in the ravine hadn't changed at all.

Han Li took a deep breath, then sat down with his legs crossed and swallowed a cultivation base consolidation pill before closing his eyes to meditate.

......

Three days and three nights later, Han Li reopened his eyes, then rose to his feet.

There's not much time left until the 20 years are up, so it's about time that I discussed some strategy with Brother Xie and the others...

With that in mind, Han Li cast his gaze upward, yet right as he was about to ascend out of the ravine, a familiar voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Fellow Daoist Han, we've already made it to this point, don't you want to go to the bottom of the ravine to see what's down there?"

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, following which he asked with furrowed brows, "Didn't I already cut off your perception of the outside world? How do you know where I am right now?"

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Han, I'm not to blame for this. It's just that the sudden drastic increase of the baleful qi in your body has strengthened my connection to the outside world slightly," Mo Guang hurriedly explained.

"Aren't you a Heavenly Devilish Monarch? I never knew that you could make use of baleful qi," Han Li mused as he raised an eyebrow.

"Baleful qi is not something that only humans and demon beasts possess. Instead, it arises within all living beings who have taken the lives of others. On top of that, our Heavenly Devils are even more sensitive to these types of negative energies than humans," Mo Guang explained.

While conversing with Mo Guang, Han Li covertly examined the connection between himself and Mo Guang, and he was relieved to find that there was indeed nothing amiss.

"Why have you suddenly proposed for me to go to the bottom of the ravine, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang? Have you discovered something?"

"Not exactly, I only have a vague feeling that there seems to be something very special down there. This is only a suggestion from me. If you feel like it's not worth the trip, then don't worry about it," Mo Guang replied.

After a brief silence, Han Li decided, "It can't hurt to go down and have a look."

With that, he continued to descend deeper into the ravine.

After descending for several hundred kilometers, the surrounding baleful qi had become so dense that even Han Li was feeling rather uncomfortable, despite his current cultivation base and spiritual sense.

By drawing upon the baleful qi in the ravine to open up his immortal acupoints for such an extended period of time, both his body and soul had undergone some slight changes, allowing him to gradually integrate himself into this environment.

However, the 20-year time limit was fast approaching, and there wasn't enough time left to make any further significant progress, so he had decided that he was immediately going to turn back if the baleful qi were to become too dense to bear.

However, right at this moment, an enormous green skeleton suddenly appeared in his field of view.

The skeleton was long and sleek, with a spine that resembled a winding ridge. On either side of the spine were racks of ribs, beneath which the bones of the creature's four limbs were still intact. On top of that, the limbs were all standing straight, supporting the skeleton in an upright position, as if it had died standing and remained that way, even in death.

Han Li flew down until he landed beside the skeleton, and by his estimates, he was currently at least 1,000 kilometers away from the entrance of the ravine up above.

He walked around the mountainous skeleton until he was standing directly in front of it, and he discovered that the skull of the skeleton was resting on the ground, while bursts of baleful qi were rising up incessantly out of its massive eye sockets before spreading into the surrounding space.

The head was quite wide up top, but then tapered to a point, and there was a pair of massive front teeth protruding out of front of its long mouth, giving it the appearance of a massive rat.

Han Li immediately recalled the giant green rat that he had seen in the baleful qi illusions earlier, and it occurred to him that this seemed to be the rat's carcass.

At the very center of the giant rat's glabella was a hole with smooth and even edges that pierced all the way through the back of its head, and it seemed that had been the killing blow.

The skeleton was already completely devoid of spiritual power fluctuations, but as Han Li stood in its presence, he was still struck by a sense of insignificance and inferiority, as if he were standing before a vast mountain.

What was particularly noteworthy about the giant rat were its two front teeth, which were of a slightly darker green color than the rest of its body, and there were bursts of clear law power fluctuations emanating from them.

Han Li was rather curious to see this, and he was just about to take a closer look when he suddenly noticed that the body of a purple-robed man was laying behind the giant rat's head.

A hint of surprise appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

The body of the man was largely quite well preserved, but it was looking extremely wizened, and its skin was a purplish-green color. On top of that, its clothes were in complete tatters, and there was a layer of black dust-like granular substance all over the entire body.

Han Li skirted around the giant rat's head to approach the body, and he was immediately struck by a wave of incredibly fierce baleful qi, causing him to stop in his tracks as his brows became tightly furrowed.

He cast his gaze toward the body's face to find that its features didn't actually appear very old, and it was only due to its severely sunken cheeks and eyes that it had initially appeared like a wizened elderly man.

Within its sunken eye sockets, the body's eyes were still open, and what was particularly harrowing was that its pupils were a completely dull and lifeless gray color.

Chapter 584: Two Bodies

This is a Gray Immortal... No wonder I felt a slightly familiar aura just now...

Just like Mo Yu from the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, this purple-robed body had also belonged to a Gray Immortal.

His gaze roamed back and forth between the two bodies, following which he turned his attention to the baleful qi in the surrounding area, and he immediately realized that these two bodies were the source of the terrifying baleful qi in the ravine.

Han Li didn't get too close, keeping his distance as he made a lap around the Gray Immortal's body, and he didn't spot many injuries on the body. In fact, the only one he could see was an uneven wound on its right temple, and that wound seemed to have been somewhat corroded as there was a dark green coloration on its jagged edges.

Judging from what he could see, it appeared that the giant rat and this Gray Immortal had fought in a battle countless years ago, ultimately leading to their mutual demise.

Perhaps this enormous ravine had been created during the course of their battle.

Han Li withdrew his gaze from the Gray Immortal as he returned his attention to the giant rat carcass, and a contemplative look appeared on his face.

Even though it's already been dead for countless years, its body is still giving off such formidable spiritual power fluctuations. If I can get Jin Tong to devour it, perhaps she'll be able to advance further in her cultivation base...

With that in mind, Han Li cast his gaze toward the rat's two massive front teeth, then raised a hand, and an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword appeared in his grasp.

He injected his immortal spiritual power into the sword before lashing out at the base of the pair of front teeth, and a sharp clang rang out as a burst of dark green light erupted out of the base of the teeth.

A wave of formidable sword qi surged through the air alongside the eruption of dark green light, and a burst of intensely corrosive energy fluctuations surged forth from within the teeth.

A burst of azure light rose up around Han Li's body, and only then was he able to keep this corrosive aura at bay.

Close to 20 seconds later, the corrosive aura fluctuations gradually subsided, and an elated look had appeared on Han Li's face.

Even though he hadn't gone all-out in that attack just now, it was still quite extraordinary that the rat's teeth had managed to remain completely unscathed.

After a brief pause, Han Li summoned three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at once, then combined the three into a single sword. Arcs of electricity surged over the sword alongside bursts of formidable sword qi as he lashed out once again at the base of the teeth, and only then did the pair of teeth fall out of the giant rat's mouth.

Han Li gently exhaled as he stowed the swords and the pair of front teeth away, then made his way over to the body of the Gray Immortal to conduct a closer inspection.

The purple robe on the body appeared to be made from quite an exceptional material, but unfortunately, it was already ruined.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light to flip the body over, and a gray cloth pouch fell out.

An elated look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he hurriedly picked up the cloth pouch before injecting his spiritual sense into it, and sure enough, it was a storage pouch!

He emptied the contents of the storage pouch onto the ground, and to his slight dismay, it only amounted to an unexpectedly small pile of items, most of which were materials that were either gray or black in color.

Han Li swept his gaze over the pile of items, and several fist-sized black crystals suddenly caught his interest.

The crystals were giving off a faint black glow that seemed to be capable of devouring all of the surrounding light, and they were also releasing formidable law power fluctuations. These were none other than Black Marrow Crystal, the primary ingredient for refining Origin Void Pills.

Furthermore, these Black Marrow Crystals were clearly of a far superior quality to the ones that Wyrm 3 had given him.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light that picked up one of the Black Marrow Crystals for a closer inspection, then stowed all of the Black Marrow Crystals away.

Outside of the Black Marrow Crystals, most of the materials on the ground were unfamiliar to Han Li, but many of them were giving off powerful energy fluctuations that weren't inferior to those of the Black Marrow Crystals.

In particular, there were three items that were giving off energy fluctuations that set them apart from everything else.

One of these items was a gray bone that was around a foot in length. It was extremely hard, and if it weren't for the gray patterns present on its surface, it would appear no different from a normal rock. It was clear that this was a very ancient artifact, but Han Li had no idea what type of creature the bone belonged to.

The second item was a large black spirit flower with crimson spirit patterns on all of its flower petals, and they connected together to form the design of an unsettling smiling face.

The final one of the three items was a vial of gray liquid. A layer of gray flames could be seen on the surface of the liquid, but it was somehow giving off an intense chill that could be felt even through the vial.

The auras of these materials were completely different from those of normal spirit materials, so Han Li could only presume that these things could only be found in the Gray Realm.

After conducting a brief inspection, he stowed all of these materials away, and the only things that remained on the ground were a pair of immortal treasures and a black jade box.

One of the immortal treasures was a black spear with an antiquated shaft and a gleaming black spearhead, within which a red mark could be seen, giving off formidable killing intent.

The other immortal treasure was a gray veil that was as thin as a cicada's wing, and it was etched with numerous star designs that were giving off a faint gray glow.

Han Li bent down to pick up the black spear, but to his surprise, it was extraordinarily heavy, almost comparable in weight to his Heavy Water True Axis.

He mustered up some more strength to pick up the black spear, then thrust it forward thrice in rapid succession, and three vibrant spear projections instantly emerged before exploding one after the other, causing the nearby space to tremble violently.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, and he began injecting his immortal spiritual power into the spear, but the influx of immortal spiritual power didn't draw any reaction out of the spear.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, but it then occurred to him that the energy in a Gray Immortal's body had to have been completely different from immortal spiritual power, so this was most likely a weapon that could only be used by a Gray Immortal.

With that in mind, a disappointed look appeared in his eyes, and he was just about to stow the spear away when he suddenly noticed that a thin layer of black light had appeared on its surface.

As it turned out, while injecting immortal spiritual power into the spear, some of the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints had also surged into it, and that had drawn a slight reaction out of the spear.

Could it be that this weapon can be powered by baleful qi?

With that in mind, Han Li released the pent-up baleful qi in his body, and it began to swirl around him as a cloud of black mist.

He then slowly guided the baleful qi into the spear, and the black light emanating from it instantly brightened significantly.

At the same time, the red mark in the spearhead also began to glow radiantly while releasing strands of crimson light that circled around the tip of the spear incessantly.

To Han Li's surprise, this weapon really could be powered using his baleful qi.

However, he could tell that this was a weapon of an extremely high caliber, and that he was only able to tap into a small portion of its power.

After stowing the black spear away, he picked up the gray veil, which was as soft and insubstantial as a cloud and as light as a feather.

Han Li inspected the veil briefly, then injected his baleful qi into it, and a layer of gray light instantly emerged over the veil, which had also become several times thicker than before.

At the same time, a series of antiquated patterns appeared on its surface, and in contrast with normal spirit patterns, these ones seemed to be far more haphazard, but also somehow more profound.

In this thicker form, the veil was still very soft and pliable, but also extremely resilient, indicating that it was an exceptional defensive material.

Right at this moment, a curious look appeared in his eyes as his gaze settled upon the patterns on the veil's surface.

These patterns were somewhat familiar to him, and he felt as if he had seen them before somewhere.

It didn't take long before he recalled exactly where he had seen something like this before, and he immediately summoned a silver jade box, within which was a piece of soft material. This was none other than the mysterious gray cloth that he had obtained from Xiong Shan.

He spread the gray cloth open, and there were some enigmatic patterns etched on its surface. These patterns were slightly different from the ones on the veil, but it was clear that they were of the same style.

Looks like this gray cloth is also from the Gray Realm...

With that in mind, Han Li injected his baleful qi into the cloth, but it displayed no response.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and he began to wonder if he was mistaken.

However, he continued to persevere, injecting more and more baleful qi into the gray cloth, but even after a full 15 minutes had passed by, the cloth still wasn't displaying any reaction.

Han Li grew a little disheartened upon seeing this, and he was just about to withdraw his baleful qi when a layer of faint gray light suddenly appeared over the cloth's surface, a layer of light so faint that it was barely detectable at all.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, and he took a deep breath before redoubling his efforts, further increasing the outflow of baleful qi.

The light emanating from the gray cloth gradually became brighter and brighter, and the antiquated patterns on its surface also slowly lit up while becoming clearer and clearer.

However, even as Han Li continued to inject more baleful qi into the gray cloth beyond this point, the light emanating from it didn't become any brighter, nor did the antiquated patterns on its surface become any clearer.

It looks like I don't possess sufficient baleful qi to fully reveal what's on the cloth, Han Li thought to himself, then stopped what he was doing and inspected the gray cloth for a while longer before stowing it away again.

The cloth was something that Han Li had obtained by chance anyway, so it would naturally be great if he could uncover its secrets, but even if he couldn't, it wasn't going to weigh on his mind.

After that, he stowed the gray veil away as well, then picked up the black jade box, which was sealed by a gray talisman.

Chapter 585: Split Soul

Han Li's gaze rested on the gray talisman for a moment, and he discovered that the runes on it were drastically different from normal runes, but the patterns on the gray cloth and the gray veil were rather similar.

After some contemplation, he cast an incantation seal onto the talisman, and a layer of gray light instantly appeared over its surface to repel the incantation seal.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as a burst of golden light that was giving off faint time law power fluctuations emerged from his hand, yet that was also repelled upon making contact with the gray talisman.

His expression remained unchanged, and this time, he channeled the baleful qi in his body before attempting to make contact with the gray talisman again.

This time, the gray light on the talisman flashed momentarily before fading away, and it didn't' reject the baleful qi.

Han Li was very encouraged to see this, and he immediately began injecting baleful qi into the talisman.

The seal within the talisman wasn't actually all that complex, and he was quickly able to undo it.

Around 15 minutes later, the gray talisman flew off the black jade box on its own, following which the box sprang open to reveal a crimson mask inside.

Han Li picked up the mask, and a surprised look appeared on his face.

This was a crimson mask assigned to the Reincarnation Disciples of the Reincarnation Palace. It was quite similar in appearance to his dragon mask, and the words "Dragon 4" were inscribed upon it.

"Dragon 4... Could it be that this Gray Immortal was from the Reincarnation Palace?" Han Li murmured to himself.

The Reincarnation Palace mask given to him by Wyrm 3 bore the words "Dragon 5".

Han Li didn't think much of this as he stowed both the mask and the jade box away, then turned his attention back to the body of the Gray Immortal.

Right at this moment, Mo Guang's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Looks like we're in luck, Fellow Daoist Han. This is a very well-preserved Gray Immortal body, and this Gray Immortal was most likely at the High Zenith Stage back when they were alive."

"So what? No matter how powerful they were, they're nothing but a corpse now. Why do you sound so excited, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang?" Han Li asked.

"Back when I was with Ma Liang, I came across a scripture in a set of ruins that contained some information pertaining to Gray Immortals. That scripture contained a secret technique that can be used to refine the body of a Gray Immortal into an avatar. After obtaining this scripture, Ma Liang had always wanted to find a Gray Immortal body, but wasn't able to do so. I certainly wasn't expecting to find one here," Mo Guang explained.

"Is that right?"

Han Li was quite intrigued to hear this.

Back in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, he had witnessed just how powerful the High Zenith Stage Mo Yu was, and if he could come into possession of a High Zenith Stage Gray Immortal avatar, then he would stand a much better chance against the Gold Devouring Immortal.

"I wouldn't dare to lie to you, Fellow Daoist Han. Gray Immortals are different from normal cultivators in that following their demise, the energy in their bodies won't quickly dissipate. Instead, most of it remains in their body, thereby making it possible to refine their bodies into avatars. You're truly in luck, Fellow Daoist Han. If you can successfully refine this body into an avatar, then you'll be able to use it against that Gold Devouring Immortal," Mo Guang said.

"Show me the refinement method," Han Li requested.

Mo Guang immediately emerged from the shadow beneath his feet, following which Han Li handed a white jade slip to him, and Mo Guang accepted the jade jade slip, then made a copy of the refinement method before handing it back to Han Li.

After briefly inspecting the refinement method in the jade slip, Han Li's brows began to furrow slightly.

The refinement method was quite different from normal avatar refinement methods, and many prerequisites had to be satisfied, one of which was that the user had to possess tremendous baleful qi.

During the refinement process, the user had to inject their baleful qi into several important points in the Gray Immortal's body in order to be able to control it.

Secondly, the user had to split their own soul using a special secret technique, then use another secret technique to fuse their baleful qi and a split portion of their soul, converting it into a baleful soul that could possess the Gray Immortal's body.

Only with both conditions met could one ensure complete control over the avatar.

"The first condition is easy to meet, but the second condition, the one that requires splitting one's soul before creating a baleful soul, is that detrimental to the user in any way?" Han Li asked.

"There will inevitably be some detrimental effects that arise from splitting one's soul, and following the conversion into a baleful soul, it'll regularly transmit negative emotions of violence and bloodlust into the user's mind. However, that's only to be expected. The energy in a Gray Immortal's body is directly contrary to that of a cultivator, so the two will conflict with each other.

“If a normal soul were to enter a Gray Immortal's body, it would quickly be destroyed. Only after a conversion into a baleful soul would it be able to reside long-term in a Gray Immortal's body," Mo Guang replied.

The excitement in Han Li's heart slowly faded upon hearing this.

If he could refine this Gray Immortal body into an avatar at only a minor cost, then he would be happy to pursue this option, but not only was this soul splitting technique going to be very harmful to his soul, it would also affect him on an emotional level, and those consequences were simply unacceptably severe.

"If you feel like the detrimental effects are too much, there's actually another solution," Mo Guang suddenly said.

"What is it?" Han Li asked.

"It's very simple: you can allow me to enter the Gray Immortal's body in the place of your split soul," Mo Guang replied.

Han Li was very surprised to hear this.

"I am a Heavenly Devilish Monarch," Mo Guang continued. "I possess no form or substance, which makes me very similar to a soul. On top of that, I possess a very high level of natural resistance to the energy in the bodies of Gray Immortals, so I should be able to enter the body just fine."

Han Li was silent for a moment upon hearing this, then asked, "Fellow Daoist Mo Guang, how long has it been since we signed our contract back in the Spirit Realm?"

"I'm always in a state of slumber, so I don't have much of a concept of the passage of time, but it should've been at least 10,000 years by now. Why do you ask, Fellow Daiost Han?" Mo Guang asked.

"Given how many years we've been together, I'm sure you're very familiar with my personality, and I'm sure you would've known that I wouldn't have agreed to using the soul splitting technique. From the very beginning, your plan was to possess this body yourself, right?" Han Li asked.

Mo Guang's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this, following which a wry smile appeared on his face as he sighed, "Looks like I can't hide anything from you. My intention was indeed to possess this Gray Immortal body myself, but I don't harbor any ill will toward you. All I want is to be able to help you in the upcoming battle against the Gold Devouring Immortal. If you're killed by the Gold Devouring Immortal, I'll also be in a terrible situation."

"That's the extent of your intentions?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Of course, I also want to attain more power for myself. You've already reached the late-Golden Immortal Stage, while Jin Tong and Daoist Xie have both reached the Golden Immortal Stage as well, leaving me as the only one still stuck at the True Immortal Stage, and it's not a good feeling to be left behind like this," Mo Guang sighed with a hint of dejection on his face.

Han Li remained silent as he stared at Mo Guang with a contemplative look in his eyes.

Moments later, he suddenly raised a hand to release a burst of azure light that enveloped the Gray Immortal's body.

Strands of translucent azure light emerged before wrapping themselves around the body, quickly forming a cocoon around it.

As a result, the immense baleful qi being released by the body was sealed in and unable to spread through the surrounding area.

"We'll discuss this matter some other time," Han Li said as he stowed the cocoon away.

Mo Guang nodded in response, then vanished into Han Li's shadow again.

After that, Han Li returned to the giant rat carcass with slightly furrowed brows.

The giant rat carcass contained immense spiritual power, but as one of the sources of baleful qi in this place, it also contained tremendous baleful qi, so it was definitely inedible to Jin Tong and Xiao Bai.

However, there was a solution to this.

After some contemplation, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to summon a stack of array plates and array flags, then set them up near the rat carcass.

A day and a night later, a gourd-shaped array had taken shape around the carcass, and within the array were four black rings the size of round tables.

The lines in the array were particularly concentrated near these rings, indicating that they were the four most important points in the array.

Han Li began to chant an incantation while making a hand seal, and specks of black spiritual light emerged all over the gourd-shaped array.

In particular, four pillars of black light had erupted out of the four rings, and they were swaying back and forth like the tentacles of a living creature.

All of a sudden, Han Li switched to a different hand seal, and the four pillars of black light instantly shot into the giant rat's carcass in unison.

The immense baleful qi surging out of the carcass instantly subsided, following which countless black runes abruptly appeared within it.

Immediately thereafter, a dull thump rang out, and the baleful qi flowing out of the giant rat carcass became even denser, and the rate of outflow had also sped up by severalfold.

Countless waves of incredibly dense baleful qi were spreading through the surrounding area, plunging the bottom of the ravine into complete darkness, and Han Li was quite pleased to see this.

This array was something that he had created on the spot using several other different arrays as a foundation, and he wasn't sure if it was going to work, but thankfully, it was working exactly as planned.

Han Li began to make a rapid string of hand seals to operate the array, but right at this moment, the giant rat carcass abruptly shuddered, following which a string of loud cracks began to ring out.

At the same time, two specks of green light emerged within its eye sockets, and they resembled a pair of eyes that were directed at Han Li.

Han Li immediately felt as if he had been plunged into a glacial pit at the sight of its scrutiny, and his back instantly became drenched in cold sweat.

If the giant rat carcass had somehow sprung back to life, then he was in an enormous amount of danger! With that in mind, he hurriedly sprang back in retreat as a streak of azure light.

Almost at the exact same moment, the giant rat carcass opened its mouth to release a green shadow that hurtled directly toward Han Li.

The green shadow was moving far faster than Han Li, and it reached him in the blink of an eye before attempting to pierce into his body.

Right at this moment, countless arcs of bright golden lightning suddenly emerged over Han Li's body amid a rumbling thunderclap, and they rapidly converged to form a single thick bolt of light to oppose the green shadow.

Chapter 586: Averting a Crisis

A resounding boom rang out as the bolt of golden lightning exploded violently upon making contact with the green shadow. The entire surrounding area was instantly illuminated a bright golden color, while the nearby space shuddered violently.

The green shadow that had shot out of the rat carcass's mouth was also sent flying back by over 100 feet.

However, it remained completely unscathed, and after steadying itself, it launched itself at Han Li once again, this time even faster than before.

Han Li immediately let loose a loud roar as he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which began releasing countless waves of golden ripples around him.

Everything in the surrounding area instantly fell still, including the churning baleful qi and the trembling space, and at this point, the green shadow was only about 10 feet away from Han Li.

A faint sheen of cold sweat had appeared on his head, and he heaved a faint sigh of relief.

The green shadow was extraordinarily fast, and if it weren't for his lightning-fast reactions and his time law powers, it would've definitely already pierced into his body.

He wiped the cold sweat from his forehead, then began to inspect the green shadow with a hint of intrigue in his eyes.

Right at this moment, the green shadow suddenly trembled slightly, then released a burst of bright green light that stained the surrounding golden ripples green as well.

Han Li was very alarmed to see this, yet before he had a chance to do anything, a burst of formidable law powers suddenly erupted out of the green shadow.

A green line then shot out of the green shadow, hurtling directly toward Han Li at a terrifying speed, and it was slicing straight through the golden ripples in its path.

However, slicing through the golden rippled was clearly very arduous for the green line, as evidenced by the fact that the light emanating from it was rapidly dimming, but in the end, it was still able to reach Han Li.

All of a sudden, the green shadow trembled once again before abruptly becoming extremely thin, resembling a sheet of green paper, and it also flew toward Han Li behind the green line, covering a distance of around 10 feet in the blink of an eye.

Before Han Li had a chance to react, the green shadow had already vanished into his body, immediately following which it transformed into a burst of tremendous baleful qi that spread rapidly throughout his entire body.

As the baleful qi flowed through Han Li's body, all of his meridians instantly became numb and as cold as ice, rendering him completely immobilized and unable to muster up any immortal spiritual power.

The golden light radiating from his body rapidly faded away, as did the surrounding golden ripples, and he found himself completely enveloped within a layer of faint green light.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, giving him no time to react.

His heart immediately sank, but he remained calm as his mind began racing to find a way out of this predicament.

Right at this moment, a burst of sinister cackling suddenly rang out within his mind, and a glowing green rat suddenly appeared in his consciousness, then immediately pounced at his nascent soul.

The golden nascent soul's eyes sprang open, and a furious look appeared on its face as it rubbed its hands together before thrusting them forward, instantly releasing a translucent sword projection to strike the green rat.

Even though Han Li's immortal spiritual power had become completely stagnant, his spiritual sense remained uninhibited, and the green rat was instantly sliced into two.

However, the green rat was completely unfazed, and it wasn't even slowed down in the slightest as it continued to pounce at Han Li's nascent soul, this time as two balls of green light.

The nascent soul's brows furrowed tightly upon seeing this, and it raised its hands again to release a pair of translucent chains, which ensnared the two balls of green light in the blink of an eye, but didn't constrict any further for fear of splitting the green rat's body up into additional segments.

The two balls of green light immediately began to struggle frantically within the translucent chains, and even though they weren't very bright, they were imbued with immense spiritual power.

As they struggled, the pair of chains around them began trembling incessantly, and they were displaying signs of loosening.

The nascent soul made a hand seal, and the two chains instantly intertwined with each other. At the same time, several more translucent chains emerged before also quickly intertwining with one another.

A cage of chains quickly took shape, and it was none other than Han Li's Spiritual Sense Cage, which had trapped both of the balls of green light inside.

The two balls of green light fused as one to form a single green rat again, and there was an alarmed and furious look on its face as it struggled against the Spiritual Sense Cage with all its might while also tearing viciously at it with its teeth.

The Spiritual Sense Cage was trembling incessantly, but it was able to hold firm.

However, before Han Li even had a chance to catch his breath, the immense baleful qi that had been brought into his body by the green shadow suddenly became extremely erratic.

With the green rat trapped in the Spiritual Sense Cage, there was no one to control the baleful qi, and it had erupted into a chaotic frenzy.

Han Li was still unable to channel his immortal spiritual power, but the baleful qi in his body had emerged on its own upon sensing the extraneous baleful qi.

As a result, a cloud of dense black mist appeared over his entire body.

The baleful qi released by the green shadow immediately fused into the black mist surrounding Han Li, and the cloud of mist began to swell drastically in size, as if it were receiving tremendous sustenance.

At the same time, Han Li's Profound Baleful Spirit Arts was activated on its own, and it was rapidly absorbing the extraneous baleful qi.

All of a sudden, a horrified look appeared on the face of the green rat that was trapped in the Spiritual Sense Cage, and it began to screech frantically in a state of panic.

The green light emanating from its body was flashing erratically, and with the absorption of this extraneous baleful qi, the rat's body began to shrink at a very slow rate, much like a deflating balloon.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, but a thought then suddenly seemed to have occurred to him, and a complex look flashed through his eyes.

Inside his spiritual sense, his nascent soul continued to focus on keeping the green rat contained in the Spiritual Sense Cage.

As the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts continued to operate, the surrounding baleful qi also began to churn violently before flooding into Han Li's body. Furthermore, the immense baleful qi emanating from the giant rat carcass had formed a thick pillar of baleful qi, which was also surging incessantly into his body.

All of a sudden, Han Li was experiencing a completely unprecedented rate of baleful qi influx.

As the vast volumes of baleful qi surged into his body, it formed an enormous wave that crashed toward his closed immortal acupoints.

Han Li was astonished by what he was seeing, but at this moment, he was still completely immobilized, so he could only look on helplessly as the situation continued to unfold.

The immortal acupoints in his body were quickly beginning to loosen in the face of this overpowering wave of baleful qi, and they were forced open one after another.

Within mere moments, three of his immortal acupoints had been opened in rapid succession!

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, but his elation quickly turned to concern as his face suddenly turned a dark crimson color.

With his immortal acupoints being opened so forcefully and aggressively, his meridians were trembling violently, and the resulting pain was countless times more severe than when he had previously been channeling baleful toward his immortal acupoints.

However, there was nothing that he could do aside from grit his teeth and fight back the pain.

As time passed, Han Li's Profound Baleful Spirit Arts began to operate in overdrive, and all of the baleful qi released by the green shadow was quickly integrated into his own baleful qi.

At this point, the green rat in the Spiritual Sense Cage had shrunk down to nothing more than a tiny speck, and with one final screech of despair, it disintegrated into nothingness.

Han Li was quite relieved to see this, and he withdrew his Spiritual Sense Cage.

With all of the extraneous baleful qi absorbed, he was able to regain control over his own body, but the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts were still completely out of his control, continuing to rapidly channel the surrounding baleful qi toward his immortal acupoints.

Two dull thumps rang out in rapid succession as two more immortal acupoints were opened.

Han Li shuddered as the crimson coloration of his complexion deepened even further. A trail of blood began to trickle down from the corner of his lips, which his chest heaved violently, and his aura was becoming very erratic.

He hurriedly channeled his immortal spiritual power to protect his own body and meridians, but he ultimately decided not to attempt to arrest the frenzied operation of the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts.

After what seemed like an eternity, the density of the baleful qi around Han Li had reached a terrifying level, and it looked as if there were balls of black flames dancing all over his body.

His face had turned such a dark shade of crimson that it was virtually black, and blood continued to flow down from the corners of his lips, but his eyes were filled with elation.

At this point, 106 immortal acupoints had already been opened in his body, yet the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts was still operating in overdrive, frantically devouring the surrounding baleful qi.

A dull thump rang out within Han Li's body as yet another immortal acupoint was opened, and he shuddered as he involuntarily threw up a mouthful of blood, but the elation in his eyes only became more pronounced.

With 107 immortal acupoints opened, he had reached the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage, and just a single step further would take him to the High Zenith Stage.

Right at this moment, all 107 of the immortal acupoints suddenly began to tremble in unison as if they were resonating with one another, and the surrounding world's origin qi began to surge rapidly into them.

Upon entering Han Li's body, the world's origin qi was converted into bursts of pure immortal spiritual power that flowed through his meridians like a turbulent river.

It seemed that the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts had finally run its course, and it slowly ceased its operation before stopping entirely.

Han Li slumped to the ground in an utterly exhausted fashion, looking as if he didn't have a single ounce of strength left in his body.

After laying still for a while, he summoned a restorative pill before devouring it, then sat up straight and closed his eyes to meditate.

A long while later, he opened his eyes, and the crimson coloration of his complexion had largely faded, clearly indicating that he had mostly recovered from his injuries.

After taking a deep breath, he rose to his feet, and as he felt the immense immortal spiritual powers coursing through his body, he couldn't help but clench his fists in excitement.

The sequence of events that had unfolded just now had been extremely perilous. It seemed that there had been a residual soul fragment left in the giant rat carcass, or perhaps the skeleton had developed its own sentient will over the course of countless years. In any case, it had attempted to use its vast baleful qi to infiltrate Han Li's spiritual sense.

In the face of such an enormous influx of baleful qi, he had been completely immobilized, and even if the average High Zenith cultivator had been in his place, their soul would've been destroyed long ago, forcing them to surrender their body to the green rat.

It was only thanks to the combination of his Profound Baleful Spirit Arts and his tremendous spiritual sense that Han Li was just barely able to weather the storm, and he had reaped some significant rewards during the process.

With 107 immortal acupoints opened, he was now only a single step away from reaching the High Zenith Stage.

However, the obvious downside to all of this was that there was now an enormous amount of baleful qi deposited in his body, and that was rather concerning to him.

Chapter 587: Shared

After taking a moment to compose himself, Han Li turned his attention back to the giant rat carcass nearby.

At this point, the baleful qi emanating from it was far sparser than before.

Instead of immediately approaching the carcass, Han Li made a hand seal to reactivate the array around it, speeding up the process of baleful qi dissipation.

Close to an hour later, all of the baleful qi in the carcass had finally been expelled.

At this moment, the skeleton was looking even more translucent than before, to the point that Han Li could almost see the spiritual power flowing through it.

Han Li inspected his surroundings momentarily before sweeping a sleeve through the air to stow away the carcass and the array tools around it, then began flying back up the ravine as a streak of azure light.

On the stone cliff at the top of the ravine, Jin Tong was pacing back and forth with an anxious expression while occasionally peering down into the ravine.

"Settle down, Jin Tong. I'm sure Master is fine," Xiao Bai said as it laid on the ground with a bored look on its face.

"I can't just sit around and do nothing! There's not much time left until the 20 years run out, yet Uncle still hasn't come out yet. Something must've happened to him! I have to go down there!" Jin Tong decided with a grim expression.

Daoist Xie drifted over to her side to stop her, then said, "I'll go. I'm a puppet, so I'll be less affected by the baleful qi in the ravine."

A grateful look appeared on Jin Tong's face upon hearing this, and she was just about to say something when she suddenly turned her gaze back to the ravine.

A streak of azure light was racing up from down below, and it broke through the dense baleful qi before quickly arriving atop the cliff.

The azure light faded to reveal none other than Han Li, and a displeased look immediately appeared on Jin Tong's face, but before she had a chance to complain to Han Li for his belated return, her expression suddenly changed drastically as she exclaimed, "Uncle! Your cultivation base..."

Xiao Bai and Daoist Xie also approached Han Li, and a stunned look appeared on the former's face as it exclaimed in elation, "Master, you've reached the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage! How?"

"You're certainly never one to disappoint, Fellow Daoist Han," Daoist Xie praised.

"Did you find some treasure down there and eat it without telling me? Is that why your cultivation base suddenly went up by so much?" Jin Tong yelled in an accusatory voice.

However, she then noticed that there was something different about Han Li's physical appearance, and she asked, "Also, why have your eyes suddenly turned gray? They look so cool!"

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he raised a hand to conjure up a mirror formed by water vapor.

Sure enough, his pupils had indeed turned gray, giving him a rather similar appearance to Mo Yu.

It looks like Mo Yu wasn't telling me the full truth about the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts, after all, Han Li thought to himself as he heaved a internal sigh.

Jin Tong was a little concerned by Han Li's silence, and she hurriedly asked, "What's wrong, Uncle? Did something happen?"

"I'll tell you about what happened in the ravine another time. For now, come with me, I found some things that should be of help to you in the ravine," Han Li replied.

"So there really is a treasure down there?" Jin Tong exclaimed as her eyes lit up with excitement.

"But I didn't sense anything..." Xiao Bai mused with a puzzled expression.

"You'll see what it is once we get there. Brother Xie, I'll have to trouble you to keep overseeing the array up here in our absence," Han Li said as he turned to Daoist Xie.

After that, he took another glance at his own reflection in the mirror that he had conjured up, only to discover that his pupils had returned to their original color.

Daoist Xie nodded in response, and Han Li cupped his fist toward it in a grateful salute, then flew back down into the ravine as a streak of azure light, taking Jin Tong and Xiao Bai with him.

Before long, the three of them had all vanished into the baleful qi down below.

After absorbing all of the baleful qi in the giant rat carcass, Han Li had become far more sensitive to baleful qi, and his body's rejection of baleful qi had also diminished significantly.

At the same time, the effect that the surrounding baleful qi had on him had become virtually negligible, and he was even able to control the baleful qi on a very rudimentary level.

Upon returning to the bottom of the ravine, Han Li made his way over to the giant rat carcass, then began making a quick string of hand seals.

A burst of invisible force erupted out of his body to force back the surrounding baleful qi, creating a space that was completely devoid of baleful qi.

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air to release two streaks of light, one golden and one white, and they transformed into Jin Tong and Xiao Bai.

As soon as she appeared, Jin Tong's brows immediately furrowed slightly as she complained, "There's so much baleful qi here..."

In contrast, Xiao Bai's gaze was immediately drawn to the giant rat carcass.

Upon noticing the object of Xiao Bai's fixation, Jin Tong's gaze also fell upon the mountainous green skeleton, and an ecstatic look appeared on her face as she rushed toward it as a streak of golden light.

However, she had only just begun flying toward the carcass when she was pulled back by Han Li.

"Hold on a second! This carcass previously contained a vast amount of baleful qi. Even though the baleful qi has since been eradicated, there's still no guarantee that it won't have a detrimental effect on you, so you should conduct a careful examination before you begin eating," Han Li advised.

"Don't worry about it, this amount of baleful qi isn't enough to hurt me! Let me go, I'll die if I don't eat this thing! After I'm done with it, maybe my cultivation base will go up by a lot as well!" Jin Tong urged in an insistent voice as she wiped away the drool that was flowing down the corner of her lips.

"Can I have some as well, Master?" Xiao Bai asked with a hopeful expression.

"The circumstances are a bit special right now. If eating this skeleton can help Jin Tong make a breakthrough, then we'll stand a better chance against the Gold Devouring Immortal, so I'm afraid we'll have to prioritize Jin Tong for now," Han Li replied.

"Alright..." Xiao Bai sighed in a dejected manner.

"If we can survive this ordeal, I'll make sure to think of some other way to compensate you," Han Li consoled as he patted Xiao Bai on the head.

Jin Tong's attention had been focused on the skeleton this entire time, and her impatience had been mounting by the second. She turned to Han Li with an eager expression as she asked, "Can I begin eating now, Uncle?"

Han Li could only give a resigned nod in response.

Jin Tong was ecstatic, and she immediately sprang forward as a giant golden beetle, digging into the delectable feast that was laid out before her, while Xiao Bai could only watch with an envious expression.

However, not long after Jin Tong began her feast, she suddenly reverted back to her human form, then flew down from the giant rat skeleton, holding a long green bone around the same thickness as a human arm in her hand.

She then flew over to Han Li with a perplexed expression as she said, "Take a look at this bone, Uncle. I almost chipped my tooth when I tried to eat it!"

Han Li accepted the bone from Jin Tong upon hearing this, then began to inspect it closely, upon which a surprised look appeared on his face.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of azure light emerged over his hand as he injected a wisp of immortal spiritual power into the bone, and it immediately began to glow brightly as a rune that Han Li had never seen before appeared on its surface, giving off bursts of powerful spatial fluctuations.

"This is a spatial treasure... Could this be its storage tool?"

Han Li attempted to inject more of his immortal spiritual power into the bone, but all that did was make the bone glow brighter and brighter, and it became as radiant and translucent as a piece of flawless jade, but it displayed no other reaction.

No matter what Han Li tried, all the bone did was glow, and Han Li was unable to refine it, nor figure out what it was meant to be used for.

At this point, Jin Tong had already flown back onto the giant rat skeleton in her golden beetle form.

Some time later, a streak of golden light flew down from the skeleton, then reverted back to Jin Tong's human form, and she wiped the back of her hand over her own lips, then patted her bulging belly as she gave a content burp.

"I'm full. You can have the rest, Xiao Bai," she declared in a generous manner as she pointed at what remained of the skeleton.

Xiao Bai was completely caught off guard by the offer, and Jin Tong gave it a slap on the head as she urged, "What are you waiting for? Hurry up before I change my mind!"

Xiao Bai naturally wanted to take up the offer, but it was still a little hesitant.

"You're one of us, so I can't just have the entire skeleton for myself and leave nothing for you. Besides, this skeleton really is quite filling. Even at the halfway mark, I was already starting to feel a little stuffed.

“It's definitely going to take me a while to digest what I've eaten. On top of that, I ate quite a few of your immortal treasures while I was inside your stomach, so this makes up for that," Jin Tong said.

Xiao Bai was very touched to hear this, but it still didn't immediately take Jin Tong up on her offer. Instead, it turned to Han Li for approval first.

"We'll do as she says," Han Li said with a nod, and Xiao Bai was certainly more than happy to oblige, swelling drastically in size before devouring the rest of the skeleton in a single bite.

After that, it reverted back to its original size, while Jin Tong praised, "I have to admit, your ability to swallow anything in one go is really impressive. Even I can't help but feel envious!"

"Alright, focus on digesting the skeleton now," Han Li said with a smile.

"Now that you mention it, I'm starting to feel a little sleepy..."

Jin Tong gave an involuntary yawn as she spoke, then quickly transformed into a tiny golden beetle before drifting down toward the ground.

Han Li reached out to catch her, then stowed her away into a spirit beast pouch.

"Master, that skeleton contained an enormous amount of energy, so I'll have to go into seclusion for a while as well," Xiao Bai.

Han Li nodded in response, then flipped a hand over to produce another spirit beast pouch before stowing Xiao Bai away as well.

Chapter 588: Final Stand

After the giant rat skeleton was gobbled up by Jin Tong and Xiao Bai, the bottom of the ravine had suddenly become a lot more spacious.

Han Li swept his gaze over his surroundings, and he suddenly noticed that there were some specks of flashing green light at the foot of the cliff face that had previously been concealed by the skeleton.

He approached the area, then leaned down to take a look, and he discovered that there were around a dozen semi-transparent plants growing there, each of which was around a foot in height.

Their leaves were as thin and transparent as ice crystals, and the veins inside were very clearly visible and giving off faint green light.

Han Li swept his spiritual sense over the strange plants briefly, but wasn't unable to detect any special aura from them.

Even though he was unable to identify these plants, it was clear that they were no ordinary plants, considering they had been able to grow at the bottom of a ravine with such immense baleful qi around.

However, he didn't have the time to be pondering such matters.

Thus, he flipped a hand over to produce around a dozen white jade boxes, then uprooted all of the green plants before carefully placing them into the boxes, then adhered a silver talisman onto each of the boxes.

After that, he remained still on the spot for a moment, seemingly in deep thought, then suddenly said, "Come out, Mo Guang."

As soon as his voice trailed off, his shadow suddenly became as black as ink, then gradually elongated to around twice its original length, following which Mo Guang emerged from it.

"Have you made a decision on my proposal, Fellow Daoist Han?" Mo Guang asked with a smile.

"I am aware of the value of a Gray Immortal's body. We're in the midst of a major crisis right now, so if you can maximize the body's value, then I have no reason to turn down your proposal," Han Li replied.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist, a Heavenly Devil Contract has been signed between us, so there's a relationship of codependence between us. The more powerful I become, the more powerful you become, so ultimately, it'll still be beneficial to you," Mo Guang said as a hint of elation flashed through his eyes.

"That's true. However, my understanding of Gray Immortals is very limited, so as a safety precaution, I'll have to plant a few restrictions in your body. Will that be acceptable?" Han Li asked.

Mo Guang faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded in response. "Of course."

Han Li wasted no further time with words as he joined his middle and index fingers before pointing them at his own glabella, releasing a burst of spiritual sense that fell upon Mo Guang.

After that, he made a hand seal and channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, upon which several translucent threads shot out of his glabella before flying into Mo Guang's glabella, chest, dantian, and several other vital regions.

Mo Guang gave a muffled groan as his face became slightly twisted with pain, but he merely suffered in silence.

Some time later, the pain etched on his face faded, and Han Li removed his fingers from his own glabella as he declared, "These restrictions won't affect you in any way under normal circumstances, but once you enter the Gray Immortal's body, if you inadvertently fall under the control of its residual soul or something like that and try to do something out of line, then those restrictions will activate on their own.

“If that happens, even I may not be able to react in time to stop the restrictions from taking effect."

"Rest assured, Fellow Daiost Han, these restrictions will never have to take effect," Mo Guang said with a smile.

"That would naturally be best. Before you begin refining the Gray Immortal's body into an avatar, I'll have to trouble you to give me a detailed rundown of the refinement process," Han Li said with a serious expression.

Mo Guang nodded in response and did as he was told.

Han Li listened to the refinement process that was being described while comparing it against the contents of the jade slip that he had been given by Mo Guang earlier, raising questions whenever there was something that he didn't understand.

Three days later, a triangular array with Black Marrow Crystals embedded onto it had taken shape at the bottom of the ravine. Han Li and Mo Guang were standing on either side of the array, while the Gray Immortal's body was placed at its center.

The two of them exchanged a glance, then sat down with their legs crossed in unison, making a hand seal while chanting a collective incantation.

As the Black Marrow Crystals in the array began to lit up, a black flame that wasn't giving off any heat rose up at the center of the array, enveloping the Gray Immortal's body to commence the refinement process.

Close to a year passed by in the blink of an eye.

The bottom of the ravine was teeming with baleful qi, and the triangular array was completely enshrouded in a cloud of dense black mist.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed around 30 feet away from the array with a layer of azure light shimmering over his body, and waves of golden ripples were also spreading from his body, giving off peculiar energy fluctuations.

Moments later, a burst of black baleful qi suddenly drifted out of his face, then flashed momentarily before vanishing again.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li opened his eyes, and his pupils were glowing a bright silver color.

Recently, his eyes had been periodically taking on this gray color, and the timing and duration fo these bouts of eye color changes were seemingly completely haphazard.

Furthermore, with each successive onset, Han Li could sense a burst of baleful qi deep in his consciousness becoming stronger and stronger, while an unreasonable sense of aggression rose up in his heart.

If it weren't for his tremendous spiritual sense, he would've most likely already fallen prey to this aggressive intent.

Han Li exhaled as the layer of baleful qi over his face gradually faded, and his pupils also returned to normal, following which he closed his eyes to meditate once again.

......

Two months later.

A burst of loud rumbling suddenly rang out from the bottom of the ravine, and the dense baleful qi there began to churn violently.

The baleful qi rose up until it had almost spilled out of the entrance of the ravine, and a perplexed look appeared in the eyes of Daoist Xie as it observed the unfolding scene from above.

At this moment, there was an enormous vortex of baleful qi that was swirling violently as it converged toward the center of the triangular array.

Outside the array, Han Li and Mo Guang were standing with their hands clapsed behind their backs, and both of them were looking rather weary.

"My sincerest apologies, Fellow Daoist Han. I thought that the refinement process would be complete in just 64 days, never did I think that it would take this long," Mo Guang said while intently scrutinizing the enormous baleful qi vortex at the center of the array.

"It's fine, we still have enough time. How confident are you in your ability to complete the fusion process?" Han Li asked as his gaze fell upon the Gray Immortal body at the center of the array.

Compared with when it was first discovered, the body had grown significantly in stature, and it was also looking more supple and full of vitality. Its wizened and sinsiter features had also become a lot softer, and it was finally beginning to resemble a living person.

"Truth be told, my chances of success are only at around 50%. If I can successfully take over this body, my cultivation base will rise all the way to the Golden Immortal Stage, and I could even progress straight to the late-Golden Immortal Stage. However, if I fail, then I'll be trapped in this body, doomed to become sustenance for it," Mo Guang replied with a wry simle.

"Why did you propose this method if there's such a major element of risk involved?" Han Li asked.

"I had no choice! Your cultivation base has been progressing at an extraordinary rate, and all of your spirit pets and puppets are also far more powerful than I am. Right now, I'm nothing more than a piece of redundant baggage for you. If I don't take such this leap of faith, I'll eventually just be completely forgotten or abandoned altogether," Mo Guang sighed.

"That's a very interesting way of looking at things," Han Li replied in an ambiguous fashion.

"Alright, here I go. Wish me luck, Fellow Daoist Han," Mo Guang said, then flew into the swirling vortex as a black shadow.

A resounding boom rang out, and the Gray Immortal's body at the center of the triangular array suddenly sprang bolt upright.

Its eyes were still a completely lifeless gray color, but its mouth had gaped open to an extreme extent.

Han Li watched as Mo Guang flew headfirst into the body's mouth, quickly entering its belly as a stream of black mist.

Immediately thereafter, the Gray Immortal's body began to tremble in an uncontrollable fashion while moving its own limbs around erratically in a jerky and uncoordinated fashion.

Furthermore, holes that resembled countless immortal acupoints had emerged all over its body, and they were devouring the black baleful qi in the ravine in a frenzy.

This spectacle lasted an entire month before the vortex of baleful qi in the ravine finally disappeared, and at this point, the Gray Immortal's body had already returned to normal, but it was still hovering in mid-air in a completely still manner.

Han Li was standing nearby, and he swept his spiritual sense over the body, only to find that it wasn't giving off any energy fluctuations.

If it weren't for his connnection to Mo Guang through their Heavenly Devil Contract, he would've already been led to believe that Mo Guang had already been devoured by the Gray Immortal's body as sustenance.

Han Li shook his head as he heaved a faint sigh.

All of a sudden, he raised an eyebrow before sweeping a sleeve through the air to summon Jin Tong, then asked, "How did it go? Have you consolidated your cultivation base?"

"After eating the two pills you gave me, I've consolidated by current cultivation base, but I haven't been able to go any further beyond that," Jin Tong replied with a slightly disappointed expression.

Han Li was rather amused by Jin Tong's disappointed expression, and he said, "The High Zenith Stage is a major hurdle that's extremely difficult to overcome. Just look at how those guys were fighting tooth and nail for High Zenith Pills back in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor! All you had to do to reach the High Zenith Stage was eat half a skeleton, how could you still be unsatisfied?"

Seven days ago, Jin Tong had suddenly awakened and reached the early-High Zenith Stage.

Furthermore, it seemed that she hadn't been afflicted by any of the five decays, much to Han Li's amazement.

Chapter 589: Awakening

"If only I could've reached the mid-High Zenith Stage. That way, we'd have a much easier time against that guy," Jin Tong sighed.

A pang of sympathy welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this. It seemed that Jin Tong had been forced to mature a lot during the time that they had been pursued by the Gold Devouring Immortal.

However, what Jin Tong said next immediately made him realize that she was still just the same greedy little girl as before.

"This body looks really good, Uncle! Should I eat it as well? Maybe that'll allow me to get to the mid-High Zenith Stage!"

"This is the body of a Gray Immortal, and it's filled with baleful qi. Are you sure you want to eat it?" Han Li asked with an exasperated expression.

Jin Tong immediately began shaking her head vigorously upon hearing this. "On second thoughts, I still haven't completely digested what I ate earlier. Xiao Bai has a much better appetite than I do, so it can have this body..."

Right at this moment, the sound of breathing suddenly rang out from the body, and Han Li hurriedly approached it to discover that its chest was heaving slightly as if it had begun breathing.

Furthermore, its eyes had fallen shut, and its eyeballs were frantically darting around beneath its eyelids, as if it had fallen into some type of nightmare and was desperately trying to wake up, but to no avail.

Jin Tong was very startled to see this, and she asked, "Why is this thing suddenly alive again? And by the looks of it... Is it having a nightmare?"

Han Li offered no response, and he suddenly recalled what he had seen back in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor. At the time, Mo Yu's body had also been a living corpse, but it had been unable to awaken due to the lack of a soul.

The fact that this body had been successfully resurrected meant that the refinement process and the integration of Mo Guang had been successful, but why was it still unconscious? What was the problem?

After a prolonged period of deep thought, an enlightened look suddenly appeared in Han Li's eyes.

Aside from the restoration of Mo Yu's soul, there had been one more vital contributing factor to the awakening of the body in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, and that was the Origin Void Pill!

Back then, Wyrm 3 had gone to great lengths to seek out Han Li to refine an Origin Void Pill for her, and that definitely wasn't a pointless gesture. As it turned out, the Origin Void Pill had played a pivotal role in Mo Yu's resurrection.

With that in mind, Han Li immediately flipped a hand over to produce an Origin Void Pill, then squeezed the Gray Immortal's cheeks between his fingers to force its mouth open before feeding it the pill.

After that, Han Li retreated back to around 30 feet away to continue observing in silence.

Jin Tong was rather perplexed to see this, but she didn't ask any questions as she also retreated back to a safe distance away with Han Li.

A short while later, a loud burp rang out, and a plume of dense black smoke billowed out of the Gray Immortal's mouth.

An apprehensive look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he immediately dragged Jin Tong behind himself while channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique.

Right at this moment, Mo Guang's voice suddenly rang out from the Gray Immortal's body. "Don't attack, Fellow Daoist Han! It's me!"

After that, the Gray Immortal's body began to move, shaking out its own limbs as if it were growing accustomed to itself.

"Prove it!" Han Li demanded in a cold voice, not letting down his guard in the slightest.

"Mo Guang" hesitated momentarily, then made a hand seal before opening his mouth, releasing a cloud of inky black baleful qi, which transformed into a black scroll that slowly unfurled itself in front of Han Li.

Han Li swept his spiritual sense over the scroll to discover that it was the Heavenly Devil Contract that they had signed, but even so, he remained wary and vigilant.

Mo Guang could sense the restrictions that had been planted in his body by Han Li's Spirit Refinement Technique, and he opened his mouth to swallow the black scroll again, then sighed in a resigned manner, "Your cautious nature really will never change, will it, Fellow Daoist Han?"

"If I wasn't this cautious, Ma Liang would still be your contractual partner right now," Han Li said in an indifferent voice.

"I didn't really think much about this in the beginning, but the more time I spend with you, the more I come to realize that the likes of Ma Liang really couldn't ever hope to hold a candle to you," Mo Guang said with a smile.

"Instead of trying to flatter me, why don't you explain your current cultivation base? Why is it different from what you told me it would be?" Han Li asked in a cold voice.

At this moment, Mo Guang was at the early-High Zenith Stage, but his cultivation was constantly fluctuating like a flame that was swaying in the wind, unable to find any semblance of stability.

Jin Tong could hear the animosity in Han Li's voice, and she didn't suppress her early-High Zenith Stage aura any longer as she began glowering at Mo Guang with an unfriendly expression.

Mo Guang hurriedly raised his hands in surrender upon seeing this, then explained, "Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Li. Only after I entered this body did I realize that it was far more powerful than I anticipated. I had been completely suppressed by it, and if you hadn't fed me that pill in a timely fashion, I would've most likely already ceased to exist by now."

"The integration process has only just been completed, yet you're already at the early-High Zenith Stage. It doesn't look to me like you were in any danger at all, Fellow Daiost Mo Guang," Han Li countered in a skeptical fashion.

"I'm only at the True Immortal Stage at the moment, so I was actually biting off far more than I could chew by trying to take over this body. As a result, my cultivation base is quite unstable at the moment. Once it stabilizes, I'll be back down to the late-Golden Immortal Stage. At the very most, I can only stay at the High Zenith Stage for a short time," Mo Guang replied with a wry smile.

Through their spiritual connection, Han Li could sense that Mo Guang's aura was indeed gradually falling back down to the late-Golden Immortal Stage, and the apprehension in his heart finally faded.

"It looks like you're telling the truth. In that case, I'll place my trust in you. Rest assured, and take some time to recuperate, I'll keep a look out for you," Han Li said.

"You have my thanks," Mo Guang replied, then immediately sat down with his legs crossed and began to meditate.

......

In the sky above an azure mountain range, a giant ball of semi-transparent white light was hovering in mid-air.

The ball of light was several dozen acres in size, and there were waves of white light constantly rippling over its surface, presenting a kaleidoscope-like effect that entranced the beholder.

The ball of light was extremely eye-catching, but none of the nearby demon beasts dared to approach it. On the contrary, all of them were frantically attempting to get as far away from it as possible.

A giant golden beetle could be seen at the center of the ball of white light, and it was none other than the High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal.

At this moment, it was completely still, as if it had been frozen in place, and its eyes were half-open in a rather dreary fashion.

Furthermore, a tiny white vortex could be seen swirling around in each of its pupils.

If these white vortexes were to be magnified by a hundredfold, one would discover that they were formed by countless specks of white light, within each of which was a flashing image.

In one of the images, the Gold Devouring Immortal had already returned to the Insect Race, and it had led the Insect Race army to eradicate all of the nearby Beast Race settlements, securing a vast amount of territory and resources in the process.

Not long after that, another Gold Devouring Immortal appeared in the primordial land in one of the other images.

After some struggle, it was able to hunt down and devour this Gold Devouring Immortal too...

In an underground cave deep below the Insect Race's territory, the Gold Devouring Immortal was curled up into a ball on a massive golden stone bed, and there was a pained look on its face.

Its entire body was giving off extremely radiant golden light alongside tremendous aura fluctuations that were undulating incessantly while steadily trending up toward a bottleneck.

Right at this moment, the aura fluctuations surging out of its body became even more violent, and they were crashing against the bottleneck like turbulent waves.

With each wave that swept through the underground cave, it would tremble violently as countless rocks shards came clattering down from above.

Resounding booms rang out one after the other, and the intervals between them were steadily shrinking.

All the while, the golden light radiating from the Gold Devouring Immortal's body was becoming brighter and brighter, until it was as radiant as the sun.

The golden light filled the entire underground cave, and it was rippling like water. Even though the walls of the cave had been reinforced by the Gold Devouring Immortal, countless cracks were still appearing on their surfaces, and these cracks were gradually widening by the second.

Right at this moment, a loud screeching sound suddenly rang out from within the golden light, following which a tremendous aura erupted forth.

The surrounding underground cave was instantly completely destroyed without being able to put any resistance, and the entire mountain also disintegrated.

Countless rocks of different sizes came plummeting out of the sky, only to instantly be repelled upon contact with the golden light.

At this moment, there was a massive golden cocoon hovering at the center of the golden light, and it was riddled with profound golden patterns that were giving off formidable law power fluctuations.

The nearby world's origin qi converged in a frenzy to form balls of radiant golden light that were constantly streaming into the golden cocoon, making it thicker and thicker. At the same time bursts of thunderous rumbling were ringing out incessantly within the cocoon, as if something terrifying were taking shape.

Within the golden cocoon, the Gold Devouring Immortal had transformed into a tall and imposing man with bushy eyebrows and a square face that was riddled with golden patterns, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

Rays of golden light were constantly surging into the man's body from the surrounding golden cocoon, and his aura was still steadily elevating.

"Finally! I've finally returned to the Great Encompassment Stage!" the man roared with excitement as he threw his head back in exaltation, but right at this moment, his surroundings suddenly shuddered violently, following which a series of cracks emerged over the surrounding scene.

In the end, the entire scene shattered like a pane of glass, then disintegrated into specks of translucent light.

The man's ecstatic expression stiffened as he stood completely rooted to the spot.

Chapter 590: Final Preparations

In the sky above the azure mountain range, the ball of white light began flashing erratically as countless white runes surged out of it.

A dull thump then rang out as the ball of light abruptly exploded, scattering into countless specks of white spiritual light.

The Gold Devouring Immortal shuddered as a hint of lucidity slowly returned to its glazed-over eyes, and the white vortexes deep within its pupils faded as it looked around with a bewildered expression.

"What happened? Haven't I already returned to the Insect Race and progressed to the Great Encompassment Stage? What am I doing here?" it roared in an alarmed and furious voice.

All of a sudden, its expression stiffened as it cast its gaze forward.

It had detected the aura of its target, the target that it was already supposed to have captured and devoured, and its aura had become significantly more powerful than before!

Could it be that I fell prey to some type of illusion?

The fury in the Gold Devouring Immortal's eyes gradually faded as it turned to inspect its surroundings.

It was a calm and pleasant day with a warm breeze blowing over the azure mountain range, and there didn't appear to be anything amiss.

The Gold Devouring Immortal quickly withdrew its gaze as a hesitant look appeared on its face.

It raised one of its front limbs before extending it forward, and the golden light radiating from its body suddenly converged in front of it to form a circular golden array.

There were countless golden runes dancing within the array, and it seemed that some type of secret technique was being used.

All of a sudden, a stunned look appeared in the Gold Devouring Immortal's eyes as it exclaimed, "I've already been here for 20 years!"

A fearful look then appeared on its face as it hurriedly began scanning its surroundings again.

The Gold Devouring Immortal had been residing in the primordial land for countless years, so it was naturally far more familiar with the primordial land than an outsider like Han Li.

The Insect Race and the Beast Race were nothing more than insignificant races situated on the outskirts of the primordial land, while the true rulers of the land were the four monarch races.

All of the four monarch races were extremely powerful and presided over enormous territories, claiming all of the regions of the primordial land with the most abundant spiritual qi.

Furthermore, there were countless powerful beings among their ranks, including a whole host of Golden Immortals and Jade Immortals, and each of the four races was led by a Great Encompassment Stage patriarch, the four of whom were collectively known as the four sages.

The Gold Devouring Immortal was already at the late-High Zenith Stage, so it didn't fear the four monarch races, but it was very much apprehensive of the four primordial sages.

At this point, it had already entered the territory of one of the four monarch races, namely the Almighty Rat Race.

The Gold Devouring Immortal had come all this way in pursuit of Han Li and Jin Tong, but it had been inexplicably trapped here in an illusion for 20 years.

20 years was not a very long time, but the Gold Devouring Immortal knew that the only ones in the primordial land capable of trapping it in an illusion for this duration were the four sages.

With that in mind, a contemplative look appeared in its eyes.

It was said that Patriarch Gu of the Almighty Rat Race was a mysterious figure who was barely ever in the primordial land, and he wasn't supposed to be particularly adept in illusions, either. Instead, the Heavenly Fox Race, which directly neighbored the Almighty Rat Race, was far more skilled in casting illusions.

Could it be that the Great Encompassment Stage patriarch of the Heavenly Fox Race did this to me? But why? Is he trying to warn me not to set foot in the territory of the four monarch races?

Countless thoughts were racing through the Gold Devouring Immortal's mind, but in the end, its greed won out over its caution, and it continued onward as a giant ball of golden light.

......

Above the sheer cliff at the entrance of the dark ravine, two balls of light, one golden and one white, were hovering in mid-air, giving off tremendous auras.

The balls of light contained none other than Jin Tong and Xiao Bai.

Even though both of them had become significantly more powerful than before, they were still unable to acclimate themselves to the baleful qi at the bottom of the ravine, so they had come up to the surface to cultivate.

Right at this moment, the ball of golden light suddenly faded to reveal Jin Tong, and she turned to a certain direction with a grim look on her face.

Deep within the ravine, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed on a large rock, channeling his immortal spiritual power while assessing the state of the baleful qi in his own body.

Mo Guang was also seated with his legs crossed nearby, and black light was flashing over his body as he continued to absorb the baleful qi in the surrounding area.

Even though he had successfully taken over this body, further consolidation was still required to complete the integration process.

At this moment, the body was looking even more supple than before. Its skin had become clean and smooth, while its previously wizened muscles had been completely filled out. Dressed in a black robe, it appeared no different from a normal person.

All of a sudden, Han Li's eyes sprang open, and Jin Tong's voice rang out within his mind.

"We've got trouble, Uncle! That guy must've woken up and is coming after us right now!"

Han Li immediately rose to his feet upon hearing this, then took a moment to calculate the time, following which he murmured to himself, "It's been 20 years on the dot... Looks like that voice wasn't lying to me."

He then turned to take a glance at Mo Guang, and he decided not to disturb Mo Guang from his cultivation as he began to ascend up the ravine as a streak of azure light.

Mere moments following Han Li's departure, Mo Guang opened his eyes as he cast his gaze upward with a contemplative look in his eyes.

It didn't take long before Han Li arrived on the cliff where Jin Tong was, and both Jin Tong and Xiao Bai were standing before him.

"Uncle..." Jin Tong began in a nervous voice, but didn't seem to know what to say.

"Jin Tong, are you Gold Devouring Immortals fearful of baleful qi?" Han Li suddenly asked as he glanced at the dense baleful qi in the ravine.

"Not really, but we definitely don't like baleful qi, either," Jin Tong replied.

"If it was possible for us to get away, we would've escaped from that Gold Devouring Immortal long ago. Seeing as we can't get away, we may as well just wait here for it and spare it the trouble of having to keep chasing after us!" Han Li said with an amused smile.

"My thoughts exactly! Both of us have become way more powerful than before, and we've got that phony, Mo Guang, as well! With all of our powers combined, I'm sure we'll be able to win!" Jin Tong replied as her eyes lit up with excitement.

"Don't forget about me!" Xiao Bai protested in an unconvincing voice.

"Oh yeah, we've got Xiao Bai as well... You should be able to withstand at least one attack..." Jin Tong said as she patted Xiao Bai on the head.

"While it's true that all of us have become a lot more powerful, we can't afford to grow complacent in the face of a late-High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal. Jin Tong, how much longer will it take to get here?" Han Li asked with a grim expression.

"At its current speed, it should be able to get here in about a month," Jin Tong replied.

"That should be enough time," Han Li murmured to himself upon hearing this.

Jin Tong and Xiao Bai could tell that Han Li had a plan, and both of them were feeling much more reassured.

"Continue cultivating here in the meantime. Jin Tong, make sure to keep constant tabs on the Gold Devouring Immortal, and tell me right away if anything changes," Han Li instructed.

"You can count on me, Uncle!" Jin Tong replied.

After that, Han Li flew back into the ravine, and he quickly reached the bottom.

Mo Guang had already gotten up from his cultivation, and upon spotting Han Li, he immediately rose to his feet before cupping his fist in a salute.

Han Li briefly relayed what he had been told by Jin Tong to Mo Guang, then added, "We'll be requiring your power to oppose the Gold Devouring Immortal, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang."

"I'm happy to help. I'll begin preparing right away. I can't promise too much, but at the very least, I should be able to maintain my High Zenith Stage powers for 15 minutes when it comes time to battle," Mo Guang replied.

"That's good to hear," Han Li said with a smile, while Mo Guang returned to his seated cultivation.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face, and swept a sleeve through the air to summon a large stack of array tools of different colors, while Daoist Xie also appeared beside him amid a flash of golden light.

"Daoist Xie, please help me set up these arrays here," Han Li said.

Daoist Xie nodded in response, then took some of the array tools from Han Li, and the two of them immediately sprang into action.

The two of them were busy at work for close to half a month before completing the arrays.

At this moment, Han Li was hovering in mid-air while chanting an incantation, and specks of light were flashing incessantly throughout the entire ravine.

Bursts of tremendous power were also surging through the area, some of which were extremely hard and strong, while others were more soft and resilient, and they were all working together to stir up the surrounding baleful qi.

All of a sudden, all of the specks of light and the bursts of power faded, leaving no trace behind, and the unrest in the baleful qi also quickly subsided.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, then descended to the bottom of the ravine, where he sat down with his legs crossed before sweeping a sleeve through the air, summoning a series of immortal treasures, all of which were glowing radiantly while giving off bursts of law power fluctuations.

Han Li picked up these immortal treasures before examining them one by one, making some final preparations for the upcoming battle.

He had already done everything that he could to brace himself for the imminent storm, but the opponent was going to be a late-High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal, so he had to be extra meticulous.

After carefully examining all of the immortal treasures, he stowed them away again, and all that was left on the ground at this moment was the Profound Heavenly Gourd.

Han Li observed the gourd for a moment, then picked it up and began to examine its opening.

That part was still lighter in coloration than the rest of the gourd, but it had become a lot darker than before, and the green light emanating from the gourd had also become brighter.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

Even though he had been fleeing from the Gold Devouring Immortal this entire time, he had made sure to consistently water the gourd using the spirit liquid from the Heaven Controlling Vial, and it was clearly working.

At this rate, it should be able to reach full maturity in no more than a century.

Han Li examined the gourd for a moment longer, then opened his mouth to release a burst of azure light that vanished into it.

A layer of countless tiny runes instantly emerged over its surface, and the runes were constantly flowing like water while releasing bursts of law power fluctuations that kept all of the baleful qi within a radius of several dozen feet at bay.

Chapter 591: Swords in the Gourd

Han Li took a deep breath before closing his eyes, then injected his spiritual sense into the glowing green gourd, arriving in the green space within.

The green space didn't appear to be any different from before. It was still filled with countless wisps of green light, which were slowly revolving to form a green vortex.

However, these wisps of green light were clearly a bit brighter than before, and they were also giving off a very peculiar aura. This was most likely the result of the nourishing effect of the Heaven Controlling Vial's spirit liquid.

Hovering at the center of the green vortex were several Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, as well as that miniature pagoda immortal treasure that he had obtained from the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor.

After so many years of refinement, the spiritual power of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had become completely self-contained, and they were giving off faint azure spiritual light, seemingly no different in appearance from normal spirit treasures.

As for the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword that had been placed into the gourd first, its spiritual power had become restrained to the extreme, to the point that it wasn't even glowing with spiritual light anymore, making it resemble an ordinary mortal sword.

However, through his spiritual connection with the sword, Han Li could sense that it contained tremendous spiritual power that could be unleashed at any moment at his behest.

After withdrawing his spiritual sense from the gourd, Han Li opened his eyes before sweeping a sleeve through the air, and one of the flying swords emerged from the gourd, then landed in his grasp.

After catching the flying sword, Han Li injected some of his immortal spiritual power into it, and an earth-shattering thunderclap instantly rang out as a vast expanse of radiant golden lightning erupted forth.

Countless thin arcs of lightning also sprang out of the sword in all directions, instantly encompassing the entire surrounding area.

These arcs of lightning were extremely bright, and all of the nearby baleful qi instantly surged back in retreat to avoid them.

A pleased look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

Sure enough, following this period of refinement in the Profound Heavenly Gourd, all of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had become significantly more powerful than before.

Immediately thereafter, eight more Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew out of the gourd at Han Li's behest, and they rose up into the air along with the one that was already in his hand.

The nine swords circled around in mid-air as thick arcs of golden lightning emerged over them amid rumbling thunderclaps, and the space in the wake of the nine flying swords was also trembling and rippling violently.

Ever since Han Li reached the late-Golden Immortal Stage, he had become able to control as many as nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at once, and that was undoubtedly a massive boost to his power.

The nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords circled around in mid-air momentarily, then returned to the gourd at Han Li's behest.

As for the miniature pavilion immortal treasure, its spiritual power had also become more self-contained, but it hadn't changed to anywhere near as significant an extent as the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, perhaps because it was simply a treasure of an inferior caliber.

After directing the nine flying swords back into the gourd, Han Li rose to his feet as he observed the gourd with a hint of excitement in his eyes.

In the next instant, he raised a hand to toss the gourd up into the air, then cast a rapid string of incantation seals into it, and the green light emanating from the gourd instantly brightened, while the green runes began to revolve at a blinding speed.

All of a sudden, a thick beam of translucent light shot out of his glabella before vanishing into the gourd in a flash.

With his recent cultivation base progression and his mastery of the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, his spiritual sense had become far more powerful than before, and he wanted to try and refine this treasure to see if he could make some progress.

This gourd was an extraordinarily rare and powerful Profound Heavenly Treasure, and Han Li was confident that it was definitely capable of more than just purifying the spiritual power of treasures stored within it.

With that in mind, Han Li continued cycling through a string of hand seals, injecting more and more immortal spiritual power into the gourd.

At the same time, he released his spiritual sense deep into the internal space within the gourd, but it didn't take long before he encountered some resistance in the form of a gentle yet resilient barrier that kept his spiritual sense at bay.

This was the same resistance that he had encountered during his previous attempt to explore the internal space of the gourd with his spiritual sense, but the resistance was significantly weaker than before.

This was naturally very encouraging to Han Li, and he hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, extending his spiritual sense deeper and deeper into the gourd.

Even though progress was very slow, his spiritual sense was still constantly advancing.

With every single inch of progress that was made, a huge amount of spiritual sense had to be expended, but Han Li was determined to persevere.

All of a sudden, the green light emanating from the gourd began to flash erratically, and bursts of formidable law power fluctuations surged forth, stirring up the nearby baleful qi into a frenzy once again.

Han Li paid no heed to this as he focused wholeheartedly on advancing his spiritual sense further and further into the green vortex, and two whole hours passed by in a flash.

Right as Han Li's spiritual sense was whittled down to past the halfway mark, a faint yet clearly audible cracking sound rang out from within the green gourd, as if some type of bottleneck had been broken.

The resistance that Han Li's spiritual sense was encountering instantly fell away, and it entered another green space.

At the same time, the resistance in the path of his immortal spiritual power also faded, allowing it to flow effortlessly into the gourd.

At the same time, the flashing green light around the gourd suddenly settled down again, but it had become brighter than before, as was the case with the green runes on the surface of the gourd.

Han Li didn't dare to let his guard down as he carefully advanced his immortal spiritual power deeper and deeper into the gourd, but most of his attention was still focused on his spiritual sense.

The green space that his spiritual sense had entered appeared to be very similar to the space from before, but this space was larger than the previous one.

However, this space was completely empty with the exception of a ball of green light hovering in mid-air.

The ball of green light was flashing occasionally, and it seemed to be very mysterious.

A hint of curiosity welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, and he immediately began inspecting this green space with his spiritual sense.

It didn't take long before his spiritual sense explored the entire space, but there was nothing special in it aside from the ball of green light.

Han Li turned his attention back to the ball of green light, and after a brief hesitation, he extended his spiritual sense toward it.

However, as soon as his spiritual sense came into contact with the ball of green light, it immediately brightened significantly while rippling like a green fireball.

Immediately thereafter, a resounding boom rang out as a burst of tremendous power erupted out of the ball of light to forcefully repel Han Li's spiritual sense.

Han Li was instantly struck by a rush of dizziness, and he hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique to steady himself as a surprised look appeared on his face.

After taking a moment to compose himself, he increased his spiritual sense output as he attempted to examine the ball of green light again, but just like last time, his spiritual sense was repelled once again.

However, he was mentally prepared on this occasion, so he wasn't struck by the same rush of dizziness, but he was still quite astonished, nonetheless.

Unwilling to give up, Han Li continued to extend his spiritual sense toward the ball of green light, even turning to his spiritual sense chains, Spiritual Sense Cage, and Sword Observation Arts, but his efforts were thwarted every single time.

In the end, he had no choice but to withdraw his spiritual sense.

In the meantime, his immortal spiritual power had managed to make some progress, but it had once again encountered some resistance.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he observed the green gourd.

Even though he wasn't able to get to the bottom of its secrets, his control over the gourd had improved significantly.

With that in mind, he released his spiritual sense to enter the first green space within the gourd, and the green vortex instantly sped up in its revolution, releasing a burst of bright green light that struck a nearby mountain face.

A deep indentation appeared on the mountain face as the section of rock struck by the burst of green light vanished into thin air, having been sucked into the gourd.

Han Li gave a nod of approval upon seeing this.

After countless years of direct contact with the immense baleful qi in the ravine, the rock face had become extremely hard, so it was quite remarkable that the green light had been able to tear through it so easily.

It seemed that as the green vortex sped up in its revolution, its ability to suck in objects had become significantly enhanced.

The chunk of rock that was sucked into the gourd appeared at the center of the green vortex, and as soon as it was encompassed within the green light, it immediately folded together like putty into a ball of black rock.

As the vortex continued to speed up in its revolution at Han Li's behest, the green light it was releasing became brighter and brighter.

The green light swept over the bottom of the ravine, and everything that it came into contact with was torn apart before being sucked into the gourd.

At this point, Han Li's complexion had paled slightly, and he withdrew his spiritual sense from the gourd.

Using a Profound Heavenly Treasure was extremely taxing, and most of his immortal spiritual power had been exhausted in this brief span of time.

Only after taking a pill did his complexion gradually begin to improve, upon which he immediately extended his spiritual sense into the first green space within the gourd once again.

At this point, the green vortex had already returned to its normal slow and languid speed of revolution.

Previously, Han Li had been unable to control the vortex at all, but now, he was able to speed up and slow down its rate of revolution at will.

As he continued to observe the vortex, a thought suddenly occurred to him, and he decided to see what would happen if he made the vortex spin in reverse.

Chapter 592: Inevitable Clash

As the green vortex began to revolve in reverse, its bright green coloration abruptly turned into a shade of dark green, and the suction force surging out of the vortex also transformed into a burst of powerful repulsion force that enveloped the black stone ball at the center of the vortex.

A layer of bright green light instantly appeared over the surface of the stone ball, only to vanish an instant later.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of blurry green light flew out of the gourd before striking the mountain face.

The entire mountain face shuddered violently along with the ground beneath it, as if an earthquake were unfolding, but the tremors instantly subsided, and Han Li cast his gaze forward to discover that a millstone-sized hole had appeared on the mountain face.

The edge of the hole was extraordinarily smooth, and it was so deep that there was no end in sight.

He injected his spiritual sense into the hole, and a stunned look appeared on his face.

As it turned out, the hole extended several hundred kilometers!

Han Li looked down at the green gourd in his hand with an ecstatic look on his face.

The repulsion force released by the gourd had imparted incredible destructive power upon that ordinary stone ball.

If he had shot a spirit treasure or even an immortal treasure out of the gourd as opposed to an ordinary stone ball, how powerful would that blow have been?

A hint of excitement welled up in Han Li's heart at the thought, and after taking some time to recover through the use of pills and Immortal Origin Stones, he injected his spiritual sense into the green gourd once again.

Just now, it had blasted out his spiritual sense along with that stone ball.

Inside the green space, the green vortex had already reverted back to its former state, and it was slowly revolving in its original direction.

Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and that miniature pavilion were still hovering at the center of the vortex.

At Han Li's behest, most of the flying swords and the miniature pavilion flew away to the side, leaving only a single Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword at the center of the vortex.

After that, the vortex began revolving in reverse again while also turning a darker shade of green, and the same burst of repulsion force re-emerged, this time acting upon the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

The sword was instantly enveloped in a ball of piercing green light, and it was trembling violently, on the verge of being blasted out of the gourd, but instead of allowing the burst of repulsion force to be released, Han Li was suppressing it with all his might.

As time passed, his complexion began to pale, and his body also began to tremble, clearly indicating that he was nearing his limits.

All the while, the repulsion force in the gourd was continuing to build, and bursts of dull rumbling were ringing out within the gourd as if it were a volcano on the brink of eruption.

By suppressing the release of the repulsion force, the vortex would continue to revolve faster and faster, but at a certain point, Han Li wouldn't be able to suppress it any longer.

Instead of persevering beyond this point, Han Li released the repulsion force, and the green gourd shuddered slightly, as did the space in front of it.

Han Li activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes to their full capacity, and only then was he just barely able to catch a glimpse of a green shadow.

The green shadow was only visible for an instant before it pierced into the rock face up ahead and vanished.

Almost at the exact same moment, the same green shadow flew out of the earth several thousand kilometers away.

Even after piercing through the earth for thousands of kilometers, the sword was still as fast as lightning, and it rose straight up into the sky, vanishing out of sight in a flash.

An extremely thin spatial rift was left in its wake, while Han Li looked on in astonishment from the bottom of the ravine.

Only after a long while did he gently exhale, and even though he had turned as pale as a sheet, there was an ecstatic look in his eyes.

The Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword blasted forth by the gourd had been so powerful that it had been able to instantly pierce through thousands of kilometers of earth while also slicing through the very space itself.

Some of his most powerful attacks were able to shake the space around him, but never had been able to tear through the space outright, so this was truly an extraordinary sight.

On top of that, the attack was far faster than any of Han Li's other attacks, and he was confident that even a High Zenith cultivator wouldn't be able to evade it from close range.

With that in mind, Han Li summoned an Immortal Origin Stone to aid in his own recovery, then swept his other hand through the air to release an incantation seal.

Shortly thereafter, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew down from above before landing in his grasp.

Only after conducting a careful examination to ensure that the sword hadn't been harmed did Han Li return it to the gourd.

......

Around half a month passed by in the blink of an eye.

On this day, a ball of golden light shot forth from afar, then appeared near the ravine in the bilnk of an eye.

The golden light faded to reveal none other than the Gold Devouring Immortal, and a tremendous aura erupted out of its body, causing all of the demon beasts within a radius of thousand of kilometers to flee in a panic.

The High Zenith Stage tree demon was also awakened, and it looked up at the Gold Devouring Immortal with an apprehensive expression.

"Piss off if you don't want to die!" the Gold Devouring Immortal warned, then turned its gaze to the ravine.

A furious look flashed through the tree demon's eyes, but it didn't retaliate. Instead, it lifted up all of its enormous roots out of the soil before also fleeing the scene.

The Gold Devouring Immortal paid no heed to it as it continued to scrutinize the ravine intently.

The baleful qi inside the ravine was so immense that it was left feeling a little apprehensive. Furthermore, it wasn't able to release its spiritual sense very far into the ravine at all due to the obstructive baleful qi, so it couldn't detect what was inside the ravine.

After a brief moment of contemplation, it flew down into the ravine as a ball of golden light, but as soon as it did so, a burst of thunderous rumbling abruptly rang out near the ravine, and thick pillars of black light emerged before erupting into the heavens.

This was none other than the Dawn Fall Heavenly Array, and it was giving off tremendous spiritual power fluctuations.

The pillars of black light resonated with one another to release countless black runes, which abruptly exploded to form balls of black light that collected the pillars of black light together, forming a vast sea of black light that encompassed the entire ravine and the Gold Devouring Immortal.

At the same time, Daoist Xie appeared near the sea of black light, then began to chant an incantation while making a string of hand seals.

The sea of black light instantly began to churn, and countless bands of black light that resembled giant tentacles emerged within it before sweeping toward the Gold Devouring Immortal.

All of the bands of black light were flashing with black runes that were giving off immense restrictive force, but the Gold Devouring Immortal merely harrumphed in disdain as it swept its two front limbs through the air.

Streaks of peerlessly sharp green light were instantly sent flying in all directions, severing the bands of black light that were attempting to ensnare it.

Immediately thereafter, it lashed out with its front limbs once again, sending two giant blades of golden light slicing into the surrounding sea of black light.

A string of cracks and pops instantly rang out from within the sea of black light, and it began to churn violently while rapidly dimming as if it were about to collapse.

Right at this moment, a sharp screeching sound rang out from deep within the sea of black light, followed by two thunderous dull thumps, and two explosions of golden light took place before quickly fading away.

The Gold Devouring Immortal's expression changed slightly upon seeing this. It seemed that the attacks it had just unleashed had been withstood by something.

The churning sea of black light was stabilized again, and it was rapidly becoming brighter.

At the same time, around a dozen giant black pythons suddenly shot out of the sea of black light, each of which was several thousand feet in length, and they pounced at the Gold Devouring Immortal in unison.

A cold look appeared in the Gold Devouring Immortal's eyes as it lashed out with one of its front limbs, and countless streaks of golden light instantly erupted out of its body, forming thousands of golden beetle projections that launched themselves at the oncoming black pythons.

A string of resounding booms rang out as the dozen or so black pythons were wiped out in an instant, disintegrating into countless specks of black light.

With yet another sweep of its front limb, all of the golden beetle projections converged to form an enormous golden sword projection, which swept through the surrounding sea of black light with tremendous power.

However, right at this moment, countless black runes surged out of the sea of black light, giving off burst of formidable law power fluctuations, and the remnants of the black pythons converged to form a series of giant black rings, which instantly appeared around the golden sword projection, stopping it cold in its tracks.

The Gold Devouring Immortal let loose a furious roar upon seeing this, and it raised its two front limbs up high as bright golden light erupted out of its body.

There were layers of golden runes interspersed throughout the golden light, and they revolved momentarily in mid-air before forming a ball of golden light that was several thousand feet in size.

Blinding golden radiance erupted out of the ball of golden light, and it resembled a golden sun that forced back the sea of black light to create an open area, following which the ball of golden light shot forth at the Gold Devouring Immortal's behest to strike the sea of black light with devastating power.

The ball of golden light instantly exploded with an earth-shattering boom, and ferocious gusts of golden wind swept forth in all directions, completely eradicating the surrounding sea of black light, which disintegrated into countless specks of black light.

As the sea of black light vanished, the Gold Devouring Immortal found itself back at the entrance of the ravine.

At the same time, Daoist Xie stumbled back in retreat as if it had been dealt a heavy blow.

Its complexion was quite pale, its robes were in tatters, and two large gashes had appeared on its chest and lower abdomen, clearly indicating that it had been severely wounded.

After flying back for over 10,000 feet, Daoist Xie fled the scene as a streak of golden light, making no attempt to engage the Gold Devouring Immortal in battle.

Chapter 593: Luring in the Enemy

The Gold Devouring Immortal didn't immediately give chase. Instead, it was hovering outside the ravine, observing the immense baleful qi down below with a hesitant look in its eyes.

All of a sudden, a thunderous, jeering voice rang out from deep within the ravine. "How was your 20-year-long dream?"

The Gold Devouring Immortal was infuriated by Han Li's taunt, but it remained still on the spot.

Immediately thereafter, Jin Tong also began to fan the flames as she jeered, "If you wanna eat me, then you're gonna have to come get me! I'll be waiting for you..."

The Gold Devouring Immortal was completely tipped over the edge upon hearing this, and the golden light emanating from its body began to swirl and churn like golden flames.

A layer of golden ripples emerged over its body, and it quickly shrank down to less than 1,000 feet in size. At the same time, the golden light around its body became denser than before, making it appear as if it were enshrouded in a layer of golden flames.

Immediately thereafter, the Gold Devouring Immortal swooped down into the ravine, and the fiery golden light around it acted as a protective barrier that kept the surrounding baleful qi at bay.

Even so, it was clear that the Gold Devouring Immortal was very uncomfortable in this environment.

Nevertheless, it was descending down the ravine far faster than Han Li had back when he was making his initial descent.

It didn't take long before it spotted Han Li and Jin Tong at the bottom of the ravine, and a hint of befuddlement flashed through its eyes.

It simply didn't make sense for them to have advanced so significantly in their cultivation bases in just the short span of 20 years, and even though it was still far above them at the late-High Zenith Stage, a hint of caution had welled up in its heart.

Instead of blindly continuing its descent, it hovered in mid-air to observe the area from above, and it quickly noticed that there were some things concealed within parts of the bottom of the ravine where the baleful qi was particularly dense.

Faint spiritual power fluctuations were emanating out of those areas, and it seemed that some type of array had been set up.

A hint of disdain flashed through the Gold Devouring Immortal's eyes as it suddenly opened its mouth to release a golden tornado, which swept through the bottom of the ravine, causing all of the baleful qi to recede and revealing a series of circular stone platforms and triangular black flags.

The stone platforms and black flags were blown all over the place in the face of the golden tornado, and the entire array was instantly ruined.

"This is what you had set up for me?" the Gold Devouring Immortal asked.

Han Li and Jin Tong both remained silent.

All of a sudden, a hint of self-deprecation welled up in the Gold Devouring Immortal's heart. What was it so worried about? How could an early-High Zenith Stage brat and a human at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage possibly pose any threat?

"You and I were one to begin with, you'll realize this when you become a part of me. All these years that you spent fleeing were completely pointless. As opposed to continuing your futile struggles, I suggest you give up now," the Gold Devouring Immortal said.

"By your logic, why aren't you surrendering and allowing yourself to be eaten by me? You said we were one to begin with, so what does it matter?" Jin Tong scoffed.

The Gold Devouring Immortal remained calm as it replied in a measured and patient voice, "Even though you and I were part of a single entity, there's a high level of disparity in our intelligence levels and cultivation bases, so it's far easier for me to devour you than the opposite.

“Even if you don't get devoured by me, you'll be devoured by another Gold Devouring Immortal eventually, so why not surrender yourself to me now? Perhaps I could even choose to preserve some of your memories. Honestly, I'm quite glad to see that you've reached the early-High Zenith Stage."

Han Li had been silent this entire time, but he finally interjected, "If you want to devour Jin Tong, then you'll have to ask me, her master, for permission first."

The Gold Devouring Immortal immediately burst into fury upon hearing this. "A mere Golden Immortal Stage human like you dares to proclaim himself to be the master of a Gold Devouring Immortal? Your insolence is astounding!"

At the same time, it swung both of its front limbs through the air, releasing two crescent-shaped streaks of translucent light that sped directly toward Han Li.

The streaks of translucent light appeared no different from the ones unleashed by Jin Tong, but they were several times faster, and Han Li was immediately struck by an asphyxiating sense of pressure as he stood in their path.

Fortunately, he was already prepared for this, and he unleashed his Reversal True Axis ability, darting away with Jin Tong to evade the attack.

At the same time, he swept a sleeve through the air to send two streaks of light, one black and one white, hurtling toward the Gold Devouring Immortal.

The Gold Devouring Immortal had some recollection of the white object. It was the same sheet of paper that Han Li had used during their previous battle, and it had already been severely damaged last time, so the Gold Devouring Immortal certainly wasn't expecting to see it again.

A gust of howling wind swept through the air as the sheet of paper swelled drastically in size, transforming into a white mountain that was riddled with cracks before crashing down upon the Gold Devouring Immortal.

As for the black object, that was a rectangular inkstone that descended onto the ground directly beneath the Gold Devouring Immortal, then transformed into a sea of black flames before rising up into the air.

Both of them were formidable immortal treasures that Han Li had secured from Feng Tiandu, but they were made to look quite lackluster in the face of the Gold Devouring Immortal, which lashed out with one of its front limbs, sending a streak of translucent light sweeping toward the white mountain up above.

The mountain immediately split apart down the middle with a resounding boom, then reverted back into a sheet of paper that had been sliced into two before drifting down onto the ground.

Immediately thereafter, the Gold Devouring Immortal opened its mouth to release a burst of tremendous suction force, and the sea of black flames down below was sucked into its stomach as a swirling vortex in the blink of an eye.

With the sea of black flames gone, a series of white jade pillars with all types of runes engraved upon them suddenly rose up from the ground, forming a huge white stone array that hurtled directly toward the Gold Devouring Immortal.

At the same time, the mountain faces on either side of the ravine began to glow with radiant silver light, and four enormous runes emerged upon them, then transformed into four giant runic projections that converged toward the Gold Devouring Immortal.

These four runes contained the Azure Dragon Wood Trapping Talisman, the White Tiger Radiant Metal Talisman, the Vermilion Bird Fire Raising Talisman, and the Xuanwu Water Barring Talisman, all of which Han Li had found in that treasured case that he had also obtained from Feng Tiandu.

The roars of tigers and dragons rang out in unison as an azure wyrm and a giant white tiger pounced at the Gold Devouring Immortal, and they were joined by a crimson fiery bird and a enormous turtle, trapping the Gold Devouring Immortal in the middle.

The Gold Devouring Immortal merely gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, and countless blades of translucent light that were as thin as cicada wings erupted out of its body, punching countless holes into the array down below in the blink of an eye.

The Four Symbols summoned by the array were also no match for these blades of light, and they were eradicated in the blink of an eye.

However, before the Gold Devouring Immortal had a chance to do anything else, an enormous shadow came crashing down from above, and it was a giant three-story pavilion that fell upon it like a cage.

The pavilion had a very lavish and opulent interior, and waves of strange sounds rang out within it, striking the Gold Devouring Immortal with a sense of disorientation. All of a sudden, it felt as if it had been cast back into that illusion where it had managed to capture Jin Tong and reach the Great Encompassment Stage.

A thunderous roar abruptly erupted out of its mouth, and the resulting soundwaves were so formidable that they instantly drowned out all of the strange sounds, while countless cracks appeared over the surrounding pavilion.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this. It seemed that the Gold Devouring Immortal's spiritual sense seemed to have become more formidable after being stuck in that illusion for 20 years.

He had thought that the pavilion immortal treasure that had been refined in the Profound Heavenly Gourd would be able to trap the Gold Devouring Immortal for around 10 seconds, thereby buying him enough time to unleash his Mantra Treasured Axis, but it wasn't even able to last three seconds.

A resounding boom rang out as the three-story pavilion exploded into countless fragments, and at the same time, Han Li yelled, "It's time, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, a black humanoid figure that was completely enshrouded in baleful qi abruptly appeared behind the Gold Devouring Immortal, and they were gripping an antiquated black spear that they plunged directly at the Gold Devouring Immortal's back.

The humanoid figure was naturally none other than Mo Guang, and just as he had promised, he was currently displaying early-High Zenith Stage power.

The spear in his hand began to glow radiantly with black light, while the crimson mark in the spearhead was also glowing brightly, and a lotus-flower-like spear projection had emerged from the tip of the spear.

Mo Guang was racing through the air as he plunged the spear toward the Gold Devouring Immortal with fierce killing intent, and the spear was displaying several dozen times the power compared with back when Han Li had been experimenting with it.

The Gold Devouring Immortal had already detected the attack, but it made no attempt to take evasive measures as it opposed the spear with its two front limbs.

Chapter 594: Repeated Blows

An earth-shattering boom rang out, and waves of tremendous shockwaves erupted in all directions from the point where Mo Guang and the Gold Devouring Immortal clashed, causing the nearby mountain faces to tremble violently as loose rocks came tumbling down like rain.

The black spear was bent like a bow before abruptly straightening out again, propelling itself and Mo Guang directly upward like a cannonball.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face as he watched Mo Guang flying back into the dense baleful qi. If it weren't for the fact that Mo Guang had taken over the body of an unfathomably powerful Gray Immortal, the force of that clash alone would've most likely been enough to completely pulverize his body.

As for the Gold Devouring Immortal, it was forced involuntarily downward, and right at this moment, Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis emerged amid an eruption of bright golden light.

The 18 time law threads around the axis vanished into it, and all of the Time Dao Runes on its surface, of which there were over 400, were glowing radiantly.

Waves of golden ripples surged through the air as a huge golden space instantly took shape, encompassing the Gold Devouring Immortal within it.

The Gold Devouring Immortal immediately felt as if it had fallen into a swamp, and all of its movements became extremely slow and sluggish.

It wanted to lash out and destroy the golden axis, but the circulation of its immortal spiritual power had slowed down to a crawl, making it very difficult to muster up any power.

At the same time, golden light was flashing erratically over its body, indicating that it was struggling with all its might to oppose the Mantra Treasured Axis.

Bursts of formidable law power fluctuations surged out of its body to combat the surrounding golden ripples, and the entire golden space began to tremble, but much to Han Li's relief, it wasn't displaying any signs of collapsing for now.

If he hadn't progressed to the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage, the Gold Devouring Immortal would've most likely already freed itself at this point.

With no time to waste, Han Li cycled through a rapid string of hand seals as he injected his immortal spiritual power into his Mantra Treasured Axis without any reservation, using the axis to trap the Gold Devouring Immortal.

He knew that he wouldn't be able to trap the Gold Devouring Immortal for long, and with that in mind, he immediately swept a sleeve through the air to summon the Profound Heavenly Gourd.

A circle of tiny runes around the gourd began to flash erratically as a burst of radiant green light erupted out of its opening, and there was a burst of repulsion force that was being suppressed within the gourd.

Having to simultaneously control both the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Profound Heavenly Gourd, Han Li's immortal spiritual power and spiritual sense were both being expended at an alarming rate.

All of a sudden, he let loose a low roar while making a hand seal, and the green light at the opening of the gourd instantly reached an unprecedented level of brightness, while a burst of thunderous rumbling rang out within the gourd.

Immediately thereafter, one Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword after another shot out of the gourd at an incredible speed, and there were eight of them in total, all of which were aimed directly at the Gold Devouring Immortal's heart.

......

A string of sharp clangs rang out alongside flashes of blinding golden lightning.

In order to ensure that the power of the swords wasn't compromised, Han Li was attacking with the swords themselves, rather than unleashing any sword projections.

Enhanced by his time spirit domain, the flying swords were sped up even further, and in the span of just a few seconds, several hundred blows had already been dealt upon the same spot on the Gold Devouring Immortal's body, but it remained completely unscathed.

The Gold Devouring Immortal was still struggling violently against the time spirit domain, but it was completely unconcerned as it chortled, "Struggle all you want! Once you run out of tricks, your fate will be sealed!"

All the while, Jin Tong was looking on while gritting her teeth in frustration and remorse. If she had worked harder in her cultivation during her time with Qu Ling, perhaps she wouldn't be so powerless right now.

Right as she was racking her brains to try and think of a way to break through the Gold Devouring Immortal's defenses, Han Li suddenly began to make one final push, drawing upon all of his remaining immortal spiritual power before releasing it like floodwaters through a broken dam.

At the same time, runes on the surface of the Profound Heavenly Gourd became blindingly bright, and the tip of a sword began to emerge from the opening of the gourd.

The green vortex within the gourd was revolving at an incredible speed, and it had accumulated so much power that it resembled a volcano on the brink of eruption.

All of a sudden, Han Li let loose a loud roar, and the entire gourd shuddered violently as the tip of the sword protruding out of its opening abruptly vanished.

In the same instant, a green shadow struck the Gold Devouring Immortal's chest like a bolt of lightning, and a resounding clang rang out as the Gold Devouring Immortal shuddered violently.

At the same time, a flurry of golden lightning and bursts of formidable sword qi erupted forth in all directions, completely eradicating the surrounding baleful qi.

The bottom of the ravine and the two mountain faces on either side of it were also severely ravaged in the blink of an eye, with giant gashes that were over 1,000 feet deep sliced into the solid rock.

The golden light over the Gold Devouring Immortal's chest shattered layer after layer, and a tiny crack that was as thin as a strand of hair finally appeared on its incredibly resilient exoskeleton.

The Gold Devouring Immortal's pupils contracted drastically as it felt its own defenses being breached, and it began to struggle even more violently.

As a result, the time spirit domain became extremely unstable, and it looked as if it could be overwhelmed at any moment.

A hint of disappointment flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, but he wasn't surprised by this outcome.

The final sword that had just been released was the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword that had been refined in the gourd for the longest period of time, and it had already displayed more power than Han Li had expected.

If that sword had struck any other late-High Zenith Stage being that wasn't the Gold Devouring Immortal, they definitely wouldn't have been able to get away with such a minor injury.

Han Li didn't dwell on his disappointment as he immediately switched to a different hand seal, and the nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords converged to form a single sword.

Instead of continuing to control the flying swords with his spiritual sense, Han Li grabbed onto the sword formed by the nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords before charging directly at the Gold Devouring Immortal.

At this point, the Gold Devouring Immortal had already flown into a blind rage, and it was continuing to struggle with all its might, but Han Li paid no heed to this as he plunged his sword straight at the tiny crack on the Gold Devouring Immortal's chest.

In this instant, he was releasing his immortal spiritual power, Divine Devilbane Lightning, and sword qi without any reservation.

A resounding clang rang out as Han Li swiveled around before instantly unleashing another strike, and he repeated the process over and over again in rapid succession.

Each successive blow fell faster and stronger than the previous one, and layers upon layers of Divine Devilbane Lightning and sword qi were building upon each other, all of which were accumulating at the crack on the Gold Devouring Immortal's chest like a volcano that could erupt at any moment.

At this point, Mo Guang had already returned to the ravine, but he didn't immediately re-enter the fray. Instead, he could see what Han Li's intentions were, and he knew that it was best to stay away for now.

As for the Gold Devouring Immortal, it could sense the threat that Han Li was posing, and it had already completely lost its composure as it struggled frantically against the Mantra Treasured Axis.

As Han Li's time spirit domain was steadily whittled down, the Mantra Treasured Axis was also affected, and it began to tremble violently, as did all of the Time Dao Runes on its surface.

At this point, Han Li's spiritual sense was severely overexerted, and his eyes had turned completely bloodshot, while blood was trickling out of his ears and flowing down his cheeks like a pair of tiny crimson snakes.

However, his hands remained as steadily as ever as he delivered one sword strike after another.

Despite his efforts, the crack on the Gold Devouring Immortal's chest hadn't been enlarged at all.

Finally, with the 361st sword strike that was unleashed, Han Li was unable to suppress the Divine Devilbane Lightning and sword qi that had been building up this entire time any longer, and an earth-shattering boom rang out as a vast explosion of golden lightning took place, forming a lightning vortex that completely encompassed the Gold Devouring Immortal.

At the same time, a vast sea of sword qi exploded from a single, concentrated spot on the Gold Devouring Immortal's chest.

The golden lightning and white sword qi intertwined to form a giant pillar of golden and white light that erupted directly upward, almost piercing through the entire ravine.

An agonized roar erupted out of the Gold Devouring Immortal's mouth, and its fury was elevated to an unprecedented peak.

The wings on its back abruptly exploded, releasing a burst of tremendous power. The Mantra Treasured Axis was already only just barely containing the Gold Devouring Immortal, and it was instantly sent flying back through the air with tremendous force.

The Gold Devouring Immortal took a furious glance down at the extremely deep and long gash on its chest, and it spat through gritted teeth, "You'll pay for this!"

Normally, it would've been able to recover from an injury like this in a matter of seconds, but this gash was displaying no signs of healing.

As it turned out, the residual lightning and sword qi around the gash were severely hampering the healing process.

Chapter 595: Battle of Life and Death

Han Li couldn't help but heave a forlorn internal sigh upon seeing this. All of his painstaking efforts had only managed to break the Gold Devouring Immortal's exoskeleton, but hadn't inflicted any substantial injuries.

Right at this moment, the Gold Devouring Immortal opened its mouth and a thread of translucent light roughly the size of a spear shot forth, hurtling directly toward Han Li's chest.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis back to his side to slow down the enemy attack, but as he did this, he realized that something wasn't quite right.

The Time Dao Runes on the axis were clearly glowing, but no golden ripples were released.

Before he had a chance to figure out what was happening, the translucent spear had already reached him, and it was too late for him to take evasive measures.

In this dire situation, Jin Tong suddenly sped over to him as a streak of golden light, positioning herself in front of him as a shield.

The spear pierced straight through her shoulder, then sent her body crashing heavily into Han Li, and blood splattered in all directions amid the grotesque sound of shattering bones.

The two of them crashed into the rock face behind them with so much force that it triggered an avalanche, sending huge rocks tumbling down from above.

Blood was trickling down from the corner of Han Li's lips as he flew toward Mo Guang while cradling Jin Tong in his arms, and Mo Guang immediately sprang into action as well, positioning himself in front of them.

Han Li withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis into his own body while inspecting Jin Tong's condition, and he could sense that her aura had diminished significantly, but much to his relief, her life wasn't under threat.

Having devoured that strange pill cauldron and that giant rat carcass, Jin Tong had progressed to the High Zenith Stage and attained a far superior physical constitution compared with before. Only then was she able to withstand that blow.

Otherwise, even with her acting as a meat shield, Han Li would've suffered grievous wounds from that spear strike, nonetheless.

"Are you alright?" Han Li asked as he observed the Gold Devouring Immortal intently.

"I'm fine," Jin Tong replied with a determined look in her eyes, then pulled out the translucent spear before stuffing it into her own mouth.

Meanwhile, Han Li's attention remained focused solely on the Gold Devouring Immortal.

Even though it had already detonated both of its wings, a pair of giant five-colored wings of light had emerged on its back to take their place, and with a single flap of those new wings, the Gold Devouring Immortal vanished from the spot.

Han Li's pupils contracted drastically upon seeing this, and he hurled Jin Tong away into the distance while raising his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword to defend himself.

At the same time, Mo Guang abruptly swelled to several dozen feet tall, and bright black light emerged over his body as he raised his black spear before thrusting it directly forward.

A black line shot through the air in a flash, following which a boundless expanse of black qi erupted forth in a formidable wave.

A resounding clang rang out as the Gold Devouring Immortal abruptly reappeared, having withstood Mo Guang's spear strike with its exoskeleton, and its front limbs were reaching around Mo Guang to attack Han Li.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and Han Li had only just raised his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword when the Gold Devouring Immortal's front limbs were already upon him.

"Let heaven and earth be turned on their heads!" Han Li declared in a thunderous voice, and the Gold Devouring Immortal immediately felt a burst of indescribable power sweep through the entire ravine.

Its vision blurred momentarily, and when it was able to see clearly again, it discovered that heaven and earth had indeed been flipped on their heads, and it had been hovering above the ravine just a moment ago, yet it now found itself at the bottom of the ravine.

Is this another illusion?

The Gold Devouring Immortal was quite bewildered by this, and it reflexively slowed down in its attack as a result.

"Let there be lightning!"

Another thunderous declaration rang out, and the ground at the bottom of the ravine abruptly split open as an incredibly thick pillar of golden lightning erupted out of the earth to instantly inundate the Gold Devouring Immortal.

Bursts of rumbling rang out incessantly as countless arcs of golden lightning ravaged the Gold Devouring Immortal's body, and this was clearly no illusion.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to the Gold Devouring Immortal, and it opened its cavernous mouth to send a vast expanse of translucent light sweeping toward the bottom of the ravine.

A resounding boom rang out as the ground at the bottom of the ravine exploded, but as opposed to any rocks or dust being raised by the explosion, there were only waves of baleful qi that were scattered in all directions.

As a result, it was revealed that there was a golden figure holding a black bladed weapon that was riddled with lightning cloud designs, and they quickly drifted back into the waves of baleful qi, vanishing without a trace.

As it turned out, heaven and earth hadn't actually been flipped on their heads, and that pillar of golden lightning had just been unleashed by Daoist Xie using the Thunderslash blade.

By the time the Gold Devouring Immortal came to realize this and turned its attention back to Han Li, it discovered that Han Li's eyes were tightly shut, and a speck of translucent light was glowing from his glabella.

In the next instant, a cage of black chains abruptly took shape in front of the Gold Devouring Immortal, then transformed into several translucent chains that instantly vanished into thin air.

Immediately thereafter, the Gold Devouring Immortal was completely rooted to the spot, immobilized in mid-air.

Within a golden space deep in its consciousness was a miniature golden beetle. This was its nascent soul, and it was currently trapped in a cage formed by translucent chains.

A series of black runes were engraved upon the chains, and the chains didn't appear to be particularly sturdy, but also seemed to have some type of unbreakable quality about them.

The Gold Devouring Immortal's nascent soul was furious, and it crashed repeatedly against the chain with all its might. The golden light within its consciousness was also crashing against the cage in powerful waves, but the cage remained as still as an immovable mountain.

Inside the ravine, Han Li heaved a faint sigh of relief, but he didn't dare to let his guard down at all.

Thanks to the combination of his Mantra Domain ability and that decoy from Daoist Xie, he had managed to trap the Gold Devouring Immortal's nascent soul in a Spiritual Sense Cage.

However, even though the Gold Devouring Immortal's soul was its weakness, it was still a late-High Zenith Stage being, so Han Li wouldn't be able to trap its nascent soul for long.

"Jin Tong, hurry!" he yelled in an urgent voice.

Jin Tong had been waiting for this opportunity, and she gritted her teeth to suppress the pain from her injuries as she transformed into a golden beetle the size of a water vat, then flew over to the gash on the Gold Devouring Immortal's chest before scurrying her way inside.

As soon as she entered the Gold Devouring Immortal's body, she immediately began sinking her teeth into the flesh inside.

The grotesque sounds of tearing flesh and chewing rang out incessantly, and it didn't take long before Jin Tong's entire body was drenched in blood.

With each mouthful of flesh that she devoured, more power would arise in her body, and the wound on her shoulder that had been inflicted by the translucent spear would recover a little.

Even though the Gold Devouring Immortal's nascent soul had been sealed away, its body was still trembling violently from the excruciating pain that it was experiencing.

Its nascent soul had been driven to a blind rage, and it was crashing against the Spiritual Sense Cage with reckless abandon, seemingly completely unconcerned by the possibility that it could harm itself in the process.

Han Li could feel his own spiritual sense shuddering violently, and his complexion paled slightly as he involuntarily threw up a mouthful of blood.

However, he had no time to tend to his own internal injuries as he channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might.

Maintaining the Spiritual Sense Cage was already extremely taxing on his spiritual sense, and he was having to expend even more spiritual sense in order to stabilize the cage against the Gold Devouring Immortal's frenzied assault.

Before long, his robes were completely drenched in sweat, and he was gritting his teeth so tightly that they were audibly creaking and groaning. He had even stowed his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and the Profound Heavenly Gourd away as he didn't dare to divert even the slightest modicum of attention away from the cause at hand.

As time passed, Jin Tong continued to rapidly eat her way through the Gold Devouring Immortal's body, and her aura was steadily being elevated in the process, but it was still significantly lacking compared with the Gold Devouring Immortal's tremendous aura.

15 more minutes passed by.

At this point, Han Li was so drenched with sweat that he looked as if he had just been fished out of a pond, and his face was as pale as a sheet, while his eyes were dull and dim from exhaustion.

Finally, his spiritual sense ran out, and the Spiritual Sense Cage within the Gold Devouring Immortal's consciousness immediately began to fade.

The Gold Devouring Immortal's nascent soul pounced on this opportunity to unleash one final wave of ferocious attacks, and the Spiritual Sense Cage fell away without being able to pose any further resistance.

Upon regaining control over its own body, the Gold Devouring Immortal immediately let loose an agonized screech that caused the entire ravine to tremble violently.

With its nascent soul trapped in the Spiritual Sense Cage, it had been deprived of the majority of its senses, so it hadn't been able to feel the excruciating agony of having its own body eaten away from the inside.

Now that it had returned to its senses, it was struck by a wave of indescribable pain that was almost too much for it to bear.

The golden light emanating from its body immediately began to tremble erratically, and a string of cracks and pops rang out from its bones as it flexed all of its muscles at once to compress down upon Jin Tong.

At the same time, all of the immortal spiritual power within its body also began to surge toward Jin Tong.

Chapter 596: Back Against the Wall

Up to this point, Jin Tong had been steadily eating her way toward the Gold Devouring Immortal's vital internal organs, and her entire body was covered in blood, while the gaps between her teeth were filled with bloody muscle fibers, presenting a terrifying sight to behold.

Right as she was about to bite through a layer of muscular membrane to tear hear way into the Gold Devouring Immortal's abdominal cavity, the muscles of the Gold Devouring Immortal around her suddenly began to compress toward her, while bursts of formidable immortal spiritual power were also converging toward her in an attempt to trap her.

However, having devoured so much of the Gold Devouring Immortal's flesh, Jin Tong's aura was rapidly approaching the mid-High Zenith Stage, and she was able to fight against the compressing flesh around her as she tore through the muscular membrane before forcing her way into the Gold Devouring Immortal's abdominal cavity.

The Gold Devouring Immortal was furious, but also at a loss for what to do. The problem was that Jin Tong was wreaking havoc inside its body, so it couldn't unleash any powerful attacks for fear of harming itself.

Originally, it wouldn't have been a bad thing for Jin Tong to have burrowed her way into its abdominal cavity.

Its soul was superior in power to Jin Tong's, so it should've been able to directly devour Jin Tong's soul, then digest her body, and that would've been the end of the matter.

However, its soul had been severely exerted during its escape from Han Li's Spiritual Sense Cage, whereas Jin Tong's aura had been growing steadily more powerful as she ate her way through the Gold Devouring Immortal's body.

As a result, the Gold Devouring Immortal was no longer confident in its ability to devour Jin Tong's soul, so it could only stay put for now and wait for its own soul to recover.

The helplessness of its situation made it even more infuriated, and it turned to Han Li with burning fury in its eyes.

If it weren't for this detestable human, it would've already hunted down its target long ago, and the Beast Race would've also been razed to the ground. Instead, it had been trapped in an illusion for 20 years and was now in a state of unprecedented peril.

This was all because of that human!

In this instant, Han Li became the sole object of the Gold Devouring Immortal's fixation, and it was determined to kill him.

Han Li had already anticipated this, so as soon as the Gold Devouring Immortal returned to his senses, he had already taken several pills to recover his own immortal spiritual power while also stabilizing his spiritual sense.

All of a sudden, the golden light emanating from the Gold Devouring Immortal's body faded, and a burst of scorching power was released from its body, manifesting itself as wisps of white steam.

Enshrouded within the steam, the Gold Devouring Immortal's body instantly became rather blurry and indistinct.

Han Li immediately activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, but before he had a chance to peer through the steam, a sense of foreboding welled up in his heart, and he reflexively dodged to the side.

Almost at the exact same moment, the Gold Devouring Immortal appeared right where he had been standing just a moment ago.

As soon as Han Li steadied himself, a streak of translucent light immediately came sweeping toward him.

Han Li was greatly alarmed, and he reflexively unleashed his Reversal True Axis ability, allowing him to vanish from the spot in a flash and evade the attack.

Only then did it occur to him that his Mantra Treasured Axis seemed to have recovered, and he was ecstatic.

A spherical light barrier instantly erupted out of his body, forming a giant time spirit domain that encompassed the entire bottom of the ravine.

As soon as the light barrier swept over the Gold Devouring Immortal, it immediately felt as if a layer of invisible force were acting upon it, thereby significantly slowing down its movements.

Compared with the Mantra Treasured Axis, the time spirit domain was able to encompass a larger area, but its slowing effect was far less potent. Hence, even though the Gold Devouring Immortal's speed was hampered in the time spirit domain, it could still catch up to Han Li in an instant if he weren't careful.

Furthermore, he could sense that the Mantra Treasured Axis in his body hadn't actually completely recovered, and it could suddenly become useless again at any moment, so he could only continue to take evasive measures while urging Jin Tong to speed up through their spiritual connection.

At the bottom of the ravine, two streaks of light, one azure and one golden, were flashing incessantly, with the latter pursusing the former, and even with Mo Guang's eyesight, he was struggling to keep track of the two streaks of light.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out as the Gold Devouring Immortal crashed into one of the nearby mountain faces, causing an enormous avalanche.

Han Li flew through the massive cloud of dust that had been raised by the avalanche, then propelled himself directly upward until he landed on a protruding stone platform that was jutting out of the opposite mountain face.

The Gold Devouring Immortal's patience had been completely exhausted at this point, and it let loose a feral roar of fury and frustration.

Instead of continuing to pursue Han Li, it laid down onto the ground, and its wings began to tremble violently as the light emanating from its body rapidly contracted. Even the waves of scorching heat that had been released from its body were being withdrawn, forming a layer of strange substance around it that was somewhere between gas and light.

As more and more of this substance accumulated, it began to release waves of extremely strange energy fluctuations, and a sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this.

Inside the Gold Devouring Immortal's body, Jin Tong was tearing away at its internal organs as quickly as she could when she suddenly noticed that these internal organs had begun trembling violently, and some of the tissues had begun to disintegrate into gas before seeping out of its body.

At the same time, its internal bodily temperature began to rise rapidly, and it didn't take long before Jin Tong felt as if she were in a lit furnace.

On top of that, there was a very strange burst of pressure rising up within the Gold Devouring Immortal's abdominal cavity, and the pressure was so immense that even Jin Tong was beginning to feel quite fearful and apprehensive.

Could it be that it's planning to self-detonate?

As soon as this thought occurred to her, Jin Tong immediately called out to Han Li through their spiritual connection.

"Run, Uncle! This thing's going to self-detonate!"

"Get out of there, Jin Tong!" Han Li hurriedly urged with tightly furrowed brows.

"No! I'm going to see this through to the end!" Jin Tong replied in a determined voice.

Han Li gritted his teeth momentarily, then unleashed his Reversal True Axis ability, flying directly upward as quickly as he could with Mo Guang right behind him.

The two of them had only just begun ascending up the ravine when an explosion of blinding white light erupted beneath them.

A deafening boom rang out from the bottom of the ravine, and waves of devastating shockwaves crashed against the mountain faces on either side of the ravine one after another.

In this instant, it was as if a second sun were rising up from the depths of the ravine, and all of the darkness and baleful qi was instantly replaced by blinding white radiance.

The walls of the ravine began to collapse layer after layer in the face of the explosion, causing the ravine to widen rapidly as all of the tumbling rocks were melted away within the scorching light.

At the same time, an enormous pillar of white light erupted straight into the heavens, incinerating all of the baleful qi in the ravine before rising up all the way to an altitude of close to 10,000 feet above the opening of the ravine.

A black humanoid figure emerged from within the pillar of white light in a completely spreadeagled fashion, floating in the air like a kite. The figure's entire body was severely charred and ravaged, looking as if they were on the verge of being vaporized.

On this figure's back was another humanoid figure that was curled up into a ball and encompassed within a layer of azure light, seemingly completely untouched by the explosion of white light.

After flying out of the ravine, the two figures flew several kilometers to the left to escape the explosion.

These two were naturally none other than Han Li and Mo Guang.

Han Li was hovering in mid-air as he turned to the severely disfigured Mo Guang and asked, "Are you alright?"

A smile that was more hideous than even the most horrific of grimaces appeared on Mo Guang's unrecognizable face as he chuckled, "Looks like you've made another winning gamble, Fellow Daoist Han."

His voice was extremely feeble, clearly indicating that he was severely injured, and the flesh of his cheeks had been completely stripped away, revealing two full rows of teeth that presented a harrowing sight to behold.

The explosion of white light had spread far too quickly for them to escape it.

In that dire situation, they had no choice but to take a gamble, using the Gray Immortal's body as a shield against the white light while Han Li used his time spirit domain to slow down the explosion as much as possible.

Ultimately, they were only able to fly for several hundred kilometers before Han Li's time spirit domain failed, and ultimately, the Gray Immortal's body was what had saved their lives.

Through their spiritual connection, Han Li could sense that Mo Guang's injuries were extremely severe, but he could also tell that Mo Guang was in no life-threatening danger, and he couldn't help but be amazed by the resilience of the Gray Immortal's body.

Right at this moment, a burst of thunderous rumbling rang out from down below.

Han Li looked down to find that the ground below was collapsing incessantly, and the ravine was continuing to expand, forming an enormous basin.

The nearby valley where the tree demon was residing had also collapsed before being buried into the earth and inundated by the waves of spreading baleful qi.

A string of panicked roars rang out from within the valley, only to subside a few moments later.

Mo Guang immediately flew into the waves of baleful qi that were rising up from down below, and as the baleful qi entered his body, his skin began to regrow.

His internal injuries weren't going to heal so quickly, but at the very least, he was gradually recovering from his external injuries.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly turned his gaze to a certain direction, where he spotted a giant shadow rising up out of the clouds of dust and baleful qi.

It was the Gold Devouring Immortal, and it was pouncing at Han Li once again as it roared with fury and indignation, "Why are you still not dead?!"

Han Li hurriedly cursed to himself under his breath before fleeing the scene, and right at this moment, Jin Tong's voice rang out in his mind.

"Hold on for just a bit longer, Uncle. Once I sever the arteries leading to its heart, it'll..."

For some reason, her voice abruptly cut off before she had a chance to finish.

Chapter 597: Outcome of the Battle

"What's wrong, Jin Tong?" Han Li hurriedly asked in a concerned voice through their spiritual connection, but received no response.

He activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes as he turned his gaze back to the Gold Devouring Immortal, upon which he discovered that it had descended back down onto the ground, and it was completely concealed within the vast cloud of dust and baleful qi that was hanging in the air.

Right at this moment, Daoist Xie, who had fled the scene earlier, arrived by Han Li's side, and Han Li immediately said, "Something seems to have gone wrong on Jin Tong's end, so I have to go and take a look. Please look after Fellow Daoist Mo Guang in my absence, Brother Xie."

Daoist Xie gave an affirmative response, and Han Li immediately flew down into the completely collapsed ravine.

He quickly traversed through the dust and baleful qi, and it didn't take long before he arrived at the body of the Gold Devouring Immortal.

At this moment, the Gold Devouring Immortal was laying on the ground in a completely still manner, and there was a layer of near-transparent light over its body, but Jin Tong was nowhere to be seen.

If it weren't for the faint spiritual connection that still existed between the two of them, Han Li would've been led to believe that Jin Tong had already met her demise.

After taking a moment to compose himself, Han Li immediately swept his spiritual sense over the Gold Devouring Immortal's body, upon which he discovered it was still teeming with vitality, and that its spiritual sense fluctuations were particularly strong.

It immediately occurred to Han Li that the Gold Devouring Immortal had to have forced its way into Jin Tong's consciousness in an attempt to devour her soul, seeing as she was about to sever the arteries leading to its heart.

As it turned out, this was precisely the case.

At this moment, there were two golden beetles that were tearing ferociously at each other within Jin Tong's consciousness.

One of the beetles was larger in stature, but the light emanating from its body was rather dull, clearly indicating that it was still yet to make a full recovery. In contrast, the smaller beetle was enshrouded in a layer of radiant golden light, and it held the home advantage, so it was not apparent which one of the two was going to come out on top.

There was no communication at all between the two of them, and each of them was focused solely on killing the other.

The sounds of tearing rang out incessantly as the two golden beetles tore away at each other's bodies, but no blood flowed out of the wounds. Instead, layers of misty golden light emerged in the place of blood.

The High Zenith Stage beetle lunged forward, only for Jin Tong to evade its attack, and before it had a chance to arrest its own momentum, Jin Tong bit down onto its wing before tearing off a chunk.

However, right at this moment, the High Zenith Stage beetle suddenly swiveled around, paying no heed to its injured wing as it bit down toward Jin Tong's head.

Jin Tong was unable to evade the attack, and it seemed that she was going to be decapitated, but in this dire situation, a streak of translucent white light suddenly appeared in her consciousness, then struck the High Zenith Stage beetle on the head like a bolt of white lightning, causing it to tumble down from above.

However, the streak of white light also sent a burst of sharp pain spearing through Jin Tong's soul.

After gritting her teeth momentarily to suppress the pain, Jin Tong immediately flew toward the High Zenith Stage beetle then bit down toward its head.

Outside the body of the Gold Devouring Immortal, Han Li was seated on the ground with his legs crossed and his eyes closed.

He had sensed the peril that Jin Tong was in, and he had channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique once again to forcibly send a spiritual sense thread into her consciousness, thereby saving her just in the nick of time.

......

The next day, at around noon.

A loud crack suddenly rang out, rousing Han Li from his seated meditation.

He took a glance at Mo Guang and Daoist Xie, who were seated not far away from him, then turned his gaze to the Gold Devouring Immortal's body, upon which he discovered that the layer of translucent light over it had already faded. At the same time, its vitality was seeping away at a rapid speed.

Immediately thereafter, Jin Tong flew out of the gash on the Gold Devouring Immortal's body.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he was just about to say something when Jin Tong declared in an expressionless manner, "Please keep a lookout for me, Uncle."

Han Li's brows furrowed ever so slightly at the sight of her cold demeanor, but he still nodded in response.

After that, he, Daoist Xie, and Mo Guang all retreated to several kilometers away, forming a triangle around Jin Tong and the body of the High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal.

Jin Tong took a glance at the three of them, then rose up into the air above the body before slowly closing her eyes.

With a sweep of her hand, a vast expanse of golden light surged out of her body, then began to swirl in mid-air, forming a golden vortex that was rapidly expanding, reaching several thousand feet in size in the blink of an eye.

Countless golden runes were swirling within the vortex, giving off bursts of formidable law power fluctuations that contained some type of violent aura, and the body of the Gold Devouring Immortal was slowly being sucked into the vortex.

All of a sudden, Jin Tong's eyes sprang open, and the golden light radiating from her body became even brighter while also taking on a more substantial form.

In the next instant, all of the world's origin qi within a radius of thousands of kilometers began to converge toward the golden vortex in a frenzy, and the nearby ground also split open as bursts of spiritual power surged out of the underground spirit vines and into the golden vortex.

In the blink of an eye, an enormous five-colored spirit cloud appeared in the sky above the golden vortex, and arcs of five-colored lightning were flashing incessantly within the cloud.

Inside the golden vortex, Jin Tong's body was gradually enshrouded within the surrounding golden light until she was completely out of sight, but her aura was clearly elevating and steadily growing stronger.

Han Li was standing in mid-air not far away, observing the unfolding scene in silence.

Mo Guang was also standing in silence with his hands clasped behind his back, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

As for Daoist Xie, it had sat down and closed its eyes to meditate, seemingly completely uninterested in what was happening to Jin Tong.

Xiao Bai arrived by Han Li's side, then looked up at the five-colored cloud in the sky with a hint of envy in its eyes as it exclaimed, "She's about to make another breakthrough!"

The golden vortex was revolving faster and faster, while the Gold Devouring Immortal's body continued to be sucked into it bit by bit.

All of a sudden, the golden vortex expanded drastically, and an incredibly bright ball of golden light appeared at its center, while countless golden runes of different sizes emerged around the ball of golden light.

Immediately thereafter, a series of massive bulges suddenly began to appear over the surface of the ball of the golden light, and it was also swaying and trembling incessantly.

At the same time, a string of low roars rang out from within. It was Jin Tong's voice, and she sounded both agitated and in a great deal of pain.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and a grim look appeared on his face.

Right at this moment, a projection of a giant golden beetle suddenly emerged within the golden vortex. The projection was identical to the Gold Devouring Immortal that had just been killed, and it was roaming throughout the vortex while roaring with fury, displaying intense animosity toward the ball of the golden light at the center of the vortex.

"Jin Tong has destroyed that Gold Devouring Immortal's soul, but there's still some residual resentful intent left in its body. If Jin Tong is to completely absorb the Gold Devouring Immortal, then she must defeat its resentful intent first," Mo Guang suddenly explained.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a thunderous roar rang out from within the ball of golden light, immediately following which a thick pillar of golden light erupted forth from within, then faded to reveal another giant golden beetle projection, this one representing Jin Tong.

A burst of thunderous rumbling rang out as the projection of Jin Tong pounced at the other golden beetle projection with tremendous power, and the other projection did the same, meeting Jin Tong with an equal degree of ferocity.

A battle immediately ensued between the two, and a string of resounding booms rang out as they clashed over and over again.

The beetle projection formed by Jin Tong was a little smaller in stature compared with its opponent, and it was constantly being forced back, seemingly on the back foot.

"She's in trouble, Master! We have to help her!" Xiao Bai yelled in an urgent voice upon seeing this.

"We can't help her. She has to face this battle alone," Han Li replied with a calm shake of his head.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a resounding boom rang out as Jin Tong's projection was sent flying back through the air.

The other golden beetle projection let loose a roar of excitement as it sprang forward in pursuit while lashing out with its pair of massive front limbs, preparing to tear Jin Tong's body to shreds.

Right at this moment, Jin Tong steadied herself before twisting around in mid-air, flying through the gap between her opponent's front limbs before appearing behind it in the blink of an eye.

Before the golden beetle projection had a chance to react, Jin Tong wrapped her legs tightly around it from behind, completely immobilizing it.

At the same time, she raised her front limbs and slashed them at the golden beetle projection's head.

Even though the golden beetle projection wasn't able to turn around to face her, it was still able to raise its own front limbs to withstand the attack, and a loud clang rang out as the two pairs of front limbs clashed, sending flurries of sparks flying in all directions.

A deranged look appeared in Jin Tong's eyes as she suddenly threw her head back and roared to the heavens, following which both of her front limbs began to glow with blinding golden light.

Another resounding clang rang out as Jin Tong's front limbs sliced through those of her opponent, then severed its head in one swift and violent stroke.

The decapitated body of the golden beetle projection instantly exploded into a vast expanse of golden light, and Jin Tong immediately opened her mouth to release a burst of suction force, upon which all of the golden light surged into her mouth like a golden wave.

Chapter 598: Severing Karmic Ties

A burst of spiritual light flashed over the golden beetle projection formed by Jin Tong, and it instantly took on a far more substantial form, following which it began to undergo a transformation into a tall and thin humanoid form.

An incredibly tremendous burst of pressure erupted out of the humanoid figure's body, and it was different from spiritual pressure in that it seemed to be coming from a higher life form, like the aura of a deity in the face of mere mortals.

Han Li and the others were gathered nearby, and all of them were instantly enshrouded within this burst of crushing pressure.

Xiao Bai was the one who fared the worst out of everyone, letting loose an agonized cry as blood began to flow out of all of its orifices, and it instantly reverted back into a white jade pendant that attached itself back to Han Li's waist.

As for Han Li himself, his vision turned completely dark, and he felt as if he had been dealt a heavy blow to the chest, causing him to stumble back close to 20 steps before steadying himself.

Daoist Xie had already flown back into Han Li's body for shelter, while Mo Guang remained largely unaffected despite the severe injuries that he sustained, once again putting on display the incredible physical constitution of the Gray Immortal body that he had attained.

The golden humanoid figure only lingered in mid-air for a few seconds before flying into the ball of golden light, following which the golden vortex abruptly expanded even further like a gargantuan golden mouth.

A burst of tremendous suction force then erupted out of the vortex, sucking in the five-colored spirit cloud up above.

The golden vortex was like an insatiable, bottomless pit, and it continued to slowly expand as it devoured the spirit cloud in the sky.

Around 15 minutes later, the entire spirit cloud had disappeared without a trace, and only then did the golden vortex begin to shrink.

A few seconds later, the golden vortex vanished as well, and all that remained in the sky was a golden ball that was around 10 feet in size, resembling a giant golden egg.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this, but he was still reeling from the recollection of the terrifying golden figure that he had just witnessed.

The golden ball continued to hover in mid-air as streaks of dazzling golden light occasionally flashed over its surface.

At the same time, it was giving off bursts of formidable aura fluctuations, and it seemed that there was something extremely fearsome being nurtured inside.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li flew over to the golden ball, following which a streak of white light slid out of his sleeve, then transformed into a small white flag.

This was one of the immortal treasures that he had obtained from Gongshu Jiu, and it instantly began to swell drastically at his behest, forming a giant white flag that was several hundred feet in size.

A vast expanse of white mist surged out of the flag, forming a white cloud that was several acres in size in the blink of an eye, completely concealing the golden ball within it.

The cloud seemed to have an aura concealment effect, and the astonishing aura emanating from the golden ball was instantly significantly diminished.

"Let's get out of here for now," Han Li said, and he was just about to depart with the white cloud and the golden ball when he suddenly stopped cold in his tracks.

A white-robed young man had appeared not far in front of him, completely without his detection.

The man was extremely handsome, and he appeared to be 30 to 40 years of age with a head of flowing black hair, running down the middle of which was a lock of faintly shimmering golden hair.

Even with his enormous spiritual sense, Han Li was completely oblivious to the man's arrival, and Mo Guang had clearly also been caught off guard.

It was as if the man had been conjured up out of thin air.

Even though there was no powerful aura emanating from the man's body, Han Li's instincts told him that the man possessed unfathomable power.

The white-robed man took a glance at Han Li and Mo Guang, and he made no attempt to announce his intentions.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then asked, "May I ask your name, Senior?"

Instead of answering Han Li's question, the white-robed man smiled and remarked, "You did very well. I must say, you really did surprise me."

Han Li was even more alarmed upon hearing this.

It was clear from this remark that the white-robed man had arrived on the scene long ago, and perhaps he had even witnessed the entire battle that Han Li had fought against the Gold Devouring Immortal.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he exclaimed, "Your voice! Could it be that you were the one who trapped that Gold Devouring Immortal for 20 years?"

"That's right," the white-robed man replied in a calm manner.

"Thank you for helping me in my time of need, Senior!" Han Li said in a serious manner as he extended a grateful bow.

If the Gold Devouring Immortal hadn't been trapped for those 20 years, he and Jin Tong would've most likely already met their demise at this point, so it was no exaggeration to say that this man had saved their lives.

"I only acted on the request of someone else," the white-robed man said in an indifferent voice.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this.

"I helped you to repay you for helping Le'er all those years ago. From this day forth, any connection between the two of you is severed," the white-robed man explained.

"Le'er? Liu Le'er? Is she with you right now, Senior? How is she?" Han Li immediately asked.

"Le'er is doing very well. Like I just said, the two of you shared some history back in the Spirit Domain Realm, but any ties between the two of you have already been severed, so you are not to meet her again," the white-robed man said in a cold voice.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then nodded in response.

Even though the white-robed man hadn't displayed his cultivation base, Han Li was confident that he had to be a Great Encompassment Stage being.

In the face of such a formidable being, Han Li had no choice but to comply with all of his demands. In any case, Han Li was happy as long as Liu Le'er was doing well.

The white-robed man's expression eased slightly at the sight of Han Li's compliant display, and he added, "Also, you're forbidden from telling anyone about what happened here."

Once again, Han Li was rather surprised to hear this, but he didn't display his surprise as he nodded in response once again.

After that, the white-robed man flipped a hand over to produce an azure jade slip before tossing it at Han Li, who reflexively caught it.

"This is a map, get away from this place as soon as possible, and don't come back again," the white-robed man said, then took a glance at Mo Guang as a peculiar look flashed through his eyes, following which he abruptly vanished from the spot.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which a wry smile appeared on his face.

It seemed that human cultivators really were very unpopular in the primordial land. If it weren't for his past ties with Liu Le'er, perhaps the white-robed man would've struck him down on the spot.

After a brief silence, Mo Guang turned to Han Li as he said, "That man felt even more fearsome to me than that High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal... Could it be that he's a Great Encompassment Stage being?"

Han Li offered no response, and after taking a deep breath to compose himself, he injected a wisp of his spiritual sense into the azure jade slip.

Much to his elation, the map provided by the white-robed man was quite detailed, marking out four enormous territories that belonged to four major races, and all of them were marked as forbidden areas.

The area that Han Li had passed through earlier was part of the Heavenly Fox Race's territory, and with that in mind, it occurred to him that the white-robed man from earlier was most likely the patriarch of this Heavenly Fox Race.

As for Liu Le'er, she was said to have been taken by a member of her own race, so she was most likely a member of this Heavenly Fox Race as well.

In that case, it seemed like Han Li didn't need to be concerned for her.

Outside of these four areas, there was also a relatively safe route leading to the Black Mountain Immortal Region marked out on the map.

After a brief inspection, Han Li withdrew his spiritual sense out of the jade slip.

"What do you plan to do from here, Fellow Daoist Han?" Mo Guang asked.

"We're clearly not welcome here, so let's leave this place before we're forced to leave," Han Li replied as he summoned the green jade flying carriage, then made a hand seal, and the white cloud rapidly shrank down into a ball of dense white mist that carried the golden ball that contained Jin Tong onto the carriage.

"Fellow Daoist Han, would you happen to have a yin-attribute spirit beast pouch?" Mo Guang suddenly asked.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then searched through his belongings briefly before producing a black spirit beast pouch that he handed over to Mo Guang.

This was a yin-attribute spirit beast pouch that he had obtained from Qu Ling, and it had quite a large internal space.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Han. Please wait for me for a moment," Mo Guang said, then flew down into the ravine, quickly reaching the bottom.

At this point, the ravine had already been transformed into an enormous crater that was riddled with holes, and only a tiny portion of the immense baleful qi that was originally in it remained.

Mo Guang made a hand seal, and the spirit beast pouch immediately flew forward before opening up wide to release a burst of tremendous suction force.

The remaining baleful, qi at the bottom of the ravine instantly surged forth, injecting itself into the spirit beast pouch as a pillar of black qi.

There wasn't much baleful qi left, so it didn't take long before all of it was sucked into the spirit beast pouch, which immediately swelled up, and the sound of sloshing liquid could be heard coming from inside it.

The pouch was originally as light as a feather, but it had since increased in weight to around 150 kilograms, and even through the pouch, one could sense the incredibly dense baleful qi inside.

An elated look appeared on Mo Guang's face as he stowed the spirit beast pouch away, then rose up into the sky before landing atop the flying carriage.

Han Li took a glance at Mo Guang, but didn't say anything as he swept a sleeve through the air to summon Daoist Xie.

"Please pilot the carriage along this route, Brother Xie," Han Li instructed as he handed the jade slip to Daoist Xie, who briefly examined the map that it contained before making a hand seal, and the flying carriage immediately shot forth as a streak of green light.

Meanwhile, Han Li made his way over the side of the carriage and closed his eyes as he focused his attention on the immortal acupoints in his body.

Out of his 107 opened immortal acupoints, most of them had been opened through the use of the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts, and all of those immortal acupoints had varying amounts of baleful qi within them.

In particular, the immortal acupoints that had been opened while in the ravine were especially abundant in baleful qi.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh upon seeing this. Even though he had drastically accelerated his own cultivation progress using the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts, it was most likely going to be exceedingly difficult for him to progress to the High Zenith Stage.

After all, making a breakthrough to the High Zenith Stage required one to face the fifth decay, and all of this baleful qi was going to pose a massive problem.

After a brief silence, he shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought, then closed his eyes to meditate and recover from the injuries that he had sustained during the earlier battle.

Chapter 599: The Fifth Decay

Somewhere in the True Immortal Realm.

There was a silver palace hovering in mid-air within a certain golden space, and four or five figures were seated on a raised platform in the palace, seemingly discussing something.

All of them were enshrouded in layers of spiritual light in different colors that concealed their facial features.

"Fellow Daoist Xiong, it's already been some time since you came to our Immortal Prison. How are you finding things here?" a figure enshrouded in a layer of white light asked.

The one that the question had been directed at was enshrouded in a layer of golden light, and his features were rather indistinct, but it seemed that he was a young man.

"Everything has been great," the young man replied with a smile.

"Your clan and mine have always been extremely close, and you just made a breakthrough to the late-Golden Immortal Stage, so if you need time to consolidate your cultivation base and wish to be exempt from carrying out any missions during this time, feel free to tell me, and I'll put in a word for you with our higher-ups," the man enshrouded in white light said.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Xuan. My cultivation base has already been consolidated, so no special arrangements need to be made for me," the man enshrouded in golden light replied.

"As expected of a prodigious swordsman like yourself, Fellow Daoist Xiong. Back when you first joined our Immortal Prison, you were able to slay mid-Golden Immortal Stage Reincarnation Palace cultivators on your own, even though you were only at the early-Golden Immortal Stage at the time. With the rapid progress that you've since made in your cultivation base, I'm sure you're destined for great things," another figure that was enshrouded in red light praised.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Di. I was very fortunate to have succeeded on that occasion. By the way, why isn't Fellow Daoist Gongshu here?"

The figure enshrouded in golden light didn't want the topic of discussion to linger on himself any longer, so he changed the subject.

"One of Gongshu Tian's close clansmen perished in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region some years ago, and he's always wanted to go after the culprit, but our higher-ups have never given him permission to do so.

“Not long ago, our Supervisory Heavenly Mirror detected that someone in the primordial land between the Northern Glacial Immortal Region and the Black Mountain Immortal Region seemed to have mastered the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, and Gongshu Tian volunteered to go and investigate this matter," the figure enshrouded in red light replied.

"When did this happen? I haven't heard anything about this at all. It's not all that rare to find someone who's cultivated the first three levels of the Spirit Refinement Technique, but someone who's mastered the fourth level has to be a core member of the Reincarnation Palace," the figure enshrouded in white light said in a grim voice.

"It happened not long ago. All of you were out on missions, and I was the only one here at the time," the figure enshrouded in red light explained.

"The primordial land is a very complex and sensitive place. Those primordial races are extremely resentful to us human cultivators, and even more so to cultivators of our Heavenly Court, so it most likely won't be easy to carry out an investigation there," the figure enshrouded in golden light said.

"Indeed. I presume Gongshu Tian will only be returning in futility," the figure enshrouded in red light said in an indifferent manner, while a contemplative look appeared in the eyes of the man enshrouded in golden light.

......

Close to a year flew by in the blink of an eye.

A streak of green light flashed through the sky above a certain barren region of the primordial land, vanishing into the distance in an instant.

The streak of green light contained a green flying carriage, atop which sat Han Li, who was cultivating in silence, while a white cloud was hovering in front of him.

Some time later, the golden light around his body slowly faded, and he opened his eyes.

Following this period of cultivation, all of his injuries had been healed, and his spiritual sense had also made a full recovery.

He cast his gaze toward the white cloud up ahead, and there were still no signs to suggest that Jin Tong was going to emerge from the golden ball anytime soon.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, only to quickly unfurrow again.

Having just devoured a late-High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal, it made sense that Jin Tong would go into an extended slumber, and with the map provided by the patriarch of the Heavenly Fox Race, the going had been quite smooth, so there was nothing for him to be concerned about.

With that in mind, he turned his gaze to Mo Guang and Xiao Bai, the latter of which was laying on the ground in a corner of the carriage, sleeping peacefully.

As for Mo Guang, he was seated with his legs crossed with a layer of black light around him, holding that black spirit beast pouch in his arms, and wisps of baleful qi were constantly flowing out of the pouch and into his body.

All of a sudden, a curious look appeared in Han Li's eyes at the sight of the black light around Mo Guang's body.

Even though Mo Guang was currently using baleful qi to cultivate, the baleful qi fluctuations emanating from his body were very faint.

Now that he had possessed the body of a powerful Gray Immortal, he was essentially no different from a normal Gray Immortal, so the baleful qi fluctuations emanating from his body should've been far more pronounced.

Mo Guang seemed to have detected Han Li's scrutiny, and he paused in his cultivation and opened his eyes as he asked, "What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Han?"

Han Li took a glance at Mo Guang's eyes to discover that their pupils are far closer in color to the black pupils of a human rather than the gray ones of a Gray Immortal, and he asked, "How are your baleful qi fluctuations so faint? Have you used some type of secret technique to conceal your aura?"

He had previously been pondering how he was going to conceal the immense baleful qi in Mo Guang's body so that they could enter the Black Mountain Immortal Region without attracting attention, but it seemed like this wasn't an issue.

Mo Guang faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied, "I haven't used any aura concealment secret techniques, Fellow Daoist Han."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he also detected the faint baleful qi fluctuations emanating from his own body, upon which a surprised look appeared on his face.

"How could this be?" he murmured to himself, seemingly just as perplexed.

"If you haven't done anything, then why do you appear no different from a normal person?" Han Li asked.

"Now that you mention it, I don't feel any discomfort right now. That wasn't the case back when I first left that ravine. All of this seems to be attributable to a strange vortex that's currently in my dantian, and it took shape after you fed me that pill earlier," Mo Guang explained after taking a moment to inspect his own internal condition.

"You're saying the Origin Void Pill has a baleful qi concealment effect?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. This vortex is able to conceal the aura of baleful qi. It's already been quite some time since I took the pill, but I never noticed that it had such an effect," Mo Guang replied.

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this, while Mo Guang continued, "I can sense that the vortex formed by the power of the pill isn't permanent. Instead, it's dissipating bit by bit, and it'll probably only be able to last a few years, maybe around a dozen years at most."

Han Li gave a thoughtful nod upon hearing this.

Originally, he had thought that the purpose of the Origin Void Pill was to awaken the soul of a Gray Immortal, but given what he was currently observing in Mo Guang, it seemed that the true effect of the pill was to allow a Gray Immortal to acclimate themselves with the world's origin qi of the True Immortal Realm while also suppressing the baleful qi in their body, thereby allowing them to awaken.

If he and Mo Guang intended to go to other immortal regions, this pill was going to be indispensable.

Thankfully, he had obtained a large quantity of Black Marrow Crystals, which was the main ingredient for refining Origin Void Pills, from the Gray Immortal's storage tool. He was still missing the other ingredients, but they weren't all that rare or precious, so he should be able to purchase them from the Reincarnation Palace.

With that in mind, Han Li summoned his Reincarnation Palace mask, then offered some rewards for those ingredients in the exchange section.

After that, he pulled out a Black Marrow Crystal and began to carefully inspect it.

Inside the crystal were wisps of baleful qi that were pure to the extreme.

These Black Marrow Crystals were of a far superior quality to the ones that Wyrm 3 had given him. When it came to pill refinement, balance was very important, so if he were to use these crystals to refine Origin Void Pills, then he would most likely have to adjust some steps of the process.

Right as these thoughts were running through his mind, the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints suddenly stirred before erupting into a violent frenzy.

Han Li shuddered as bursts of baleful qi that were as viscous as ink shot out of his body, then rapidly expanded outward, instantly filling the entire surrounding area within a radius of several hundred feet.

At the same time, Han Li's eyes began to glow crimson, and it was as if he had transformed into a terrifying baleful deity.

Everyone else on the flying carriage was instantly inundated by the baleful qi that had erupted out of his body, and they were naturally very startled.

The flying carriage instantly drew to a halt, while Han Li abruptly rose to his feet as he warned, "All of you, stay here and don't follow me."

After that, he flew out of the carriage and descended out of the sky.

Down below was an undulating mountain range that was quite abundant with spiritual qi, and there was a massive canyon between two mountains that a river was slowly flowing through.

There were many demon beasts residing in the mountain range, and they immediately fled for their lives upon sensing the terrifying aura that was currently emanating from Han Li's body.

Han Li flew straight into the canyon before throwing an almighty punch, blasting a huge hole into the mountain face up ahead.

He then flew into the makeshift cave that he had just created, then hurriedly set up a layer of restrictions around himself before sitting down with his legs crossed.

A layer of bright golden light emerged to envelop his entire body, but black baleful qi was still surging out incessantly, and it was becoming denser and denser.

"What's happening with Master?" Xiao Bai asked in a stunned manner as it looked down from the flying carriage.

"It looks like Fellow Daoist Han has been befallen by the fifth decay, the baleful decay," Mo Guang said.

Daoist Xie took a glance at Mo Guang, then cast an incantation seal into the flying carriage, upon which it descended into the canyon, but drew to a halt still quite far away from the cave that Han Li was in.

"Master has only just reached the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage, how could the baleful decay have befallen him so quickly?" Xiao Bai asked with a grim expression.

"Fellow Daoist Han was using baleful qi to force his own immortal acupoints open, so an enormous amount of baleful qi has accumulated in his body, thereby leading to the premature onset of baleful decay," Mo Guang explained.

"The baleful decay is the most difficult final hurdle that must be overcome in order to reach the High Zenith Stage. While I was with Gongshu Jiu, I saw countless cultivators fall at this hurdle, ultimately driven insane and killed by baleful qi backlash. Master has only just reached the pinnacle of the Gold Devouring Immortal, and he's completely unprepared..."

Xiao Bai's voice trailed off here, but the implications were very apparent.

Both Mo Guang and Daoist Xie remained silent as they observed the cave from afar.

Chapter 600: Internal Battle

Inside the cave.

Han Li was seated on the ground with his legs crossed, channeling his Mantra Axis Scripture with all his might.

His Mantra Treasured Axis had emerged, and bursts of pure time law powers were permeating throughout the rippling golden light around him, enveloping his entire body.

Han Li was well aware that the fifth decay, baleful decay, was upon him.

Due to the extreme measures that he had taken in the ravine, his cultivation base had progressed by leaps and bounds, so he most likely wasn't going to have to face the fourth decay that other Golden Immortal cultivators had to overcome. However, now that he was only one step away from the High Zenith Stage, the fifth decay was entirely unavoidable.

The main contributing factors leading to the premature onset of the baleful decay seemed to be his cultivation of the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts and his mastery of the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Even though he was already mentally prepared for such an eventuality, he was still caught off guard by this sudden crisis.

However, seeing as it was already happening, he had no choice but to face it head-on.

In contrast with the acupoint decay that he had previously endured, the onset of baleful decay was extremely violent. He could sense the baleful qi that had previously laid dormant in his body gradually being stirred up into a frenzy, constantly attacking his consciousness. At the same time, some of the baleful qi had also triggered the dozens of immortal acupoints in his body that contained baleful qi, causing the baleful qi inside to seep outward.

At this moment, Han Li could feel an unbridled sense of aggression constantly building in his body, and if it weren't for his exceptional willpower, he would've already been driven insane.

A series of dark clouds had appeared in the sky above the cave that Han Li was in, and indistinct red shadows could be seen flashing through the clouds amid the sound of ghostly wailing.

All of the plants within a radius of several hundred kilometers quickly wilted away, while the ground and the rocks slowly turned a lifeless gray color.

This was a place that had been teeming with spiritual qi just a moment ago, yet it had been transformed into an infernal hell in the blink of an eye.

Shortly thereafter, several black spots emerged over Han Li's body, and they were slowly expanding, while the pure spiritual sense in his consciousness was also gradually being contaminated by wisps of black light.

The crimson light in his eyes glowed even brighter, and waves of intense bloodlust were rising up in his mind.

All of a sudden, he let loose a low roar as he made a hand seal, and thick arcs of Divine Devilbane Lightning emerged over his body amid a dull thunderclap.

At the same time, several bursts of spiritual light released by immortal treasures had also shot out of his body.

Normally, Divine Devilbane Lightning was extremely effective at suppressing baleful qi, but in this instance, it was completely ineffective against the baleful qi surging out of Han Li's body.

On the contrary, in the face of the corrosion from the tremendous baleful qi, the arcs of Divine Devilbane Lightning were quickly snuffed out like frail candle flames.

As for the immortal treasure spiritual light that Han Li had conjured up, they quickly faded away as well, and only the innate law powers that they contained were still posing some resistance against the baleful qi.

However, the baleful qi was simply too formidable to be suppressed, and the law powers were quickly overcome as well. In the end, all that remained standing against the baleful qi was Han Li's time law powers.

Han Li wasn't surprised to see this, and he continued to make a string of hand seals, while his Mantra Treasured Axis revolved rapidly behind him, releasing bursts of time law powers to keep the baleful qi at bay.

Despite the ferocity at which the baleful qi was raging, Han Li's time law powers remained firm and resolute, much to his relief.

While it was true that he hadn't made any preparations for this baleful decay, he had studied it quite extensively, so he was aware of just how violent and ferocious it was, completely unlike the slow and subtle onset of the other four decays.

The majority of cultivators were unable to withstand the fierce eruption of baleful qi, causing them to fall insane not long after the commencement of their baleful decay, ultimately resulting in the detonation of their bodies and nascent souls.

Thankfully, he had one of the three paramount laws to protect him. Otherwise, there was a chance that he could've already fallen at the first hurdle as well.

The problem was that even though his time law powers were very formidable, the baleful qi that it was contending against wasn't from an extraneous source. Instead, it came directly from his own body and immortal acupoints, so despite the best efforts of his time law powers, some of the baleful qi was still slowly seeping into his body and mind.

The black spots on his body were rapidly expanding, and at this point, they covered close to half of his entire body. At the same time, his eyes were glowing ever more crimson with bloodlust.

Han Li was channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique to suppress the violent thoughts that were arising in his heart while sweeping a sleeve through the air to summon a white jade box, upon which was plastered a glowing silver talisman that was giving off hints of law power fluctuations.

Han Li then quickly chanted an incantation, and the silver talisman abruptly erupted into flames before burning away into nothingness.

The jade box sprang open on its own, and inside was a longan-sized silver pill that was giving off an incredible medicinal aroma. This was a High Zenith Pill.

Han Li was feeling extremely thankful that he had obtained three High Zenith Pills from the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor. Otherwise, he would truly be at a complete loss for what to do.

He swallowed the pill right away, then enveloped it with his immortal spiritual power to refine it within his own body.

The silver light emanating from the pill instantly grew brighter, and it was also giving off bursts of scorching energy that struck Han Li's lower abdomen with a sense of burning pain, as if there were a silver fireball burning inside.

Han Li took a deep breath to suppress the pain while continuing to refine the High Zenith Pill using his immortal spiritual power.

The silver light emanating from the pill lit up even further, releasing streams of warmth that quickly flowed through Han Li's body, melting away all of the baleful qi that they encountered.

However, at the same time, those streams of warmth were also constantly being whittled down.

The crimson light glowing in Han Li's eyes instantly stopped becoming brighter, then slowly began to dim, while the black spots on his body also began to recede, much to his elation.

He continued to make a string of hand seals, using the power of the High Zenith Pill to counteract the baleful qi within his body, and a layer of silver light quickly appeared around him, intertwining with the existing layer of golden light.

A peculiar medicinal aroma wafted out of the silver light, and it could be clearly smelled by Mo Guang and the others, even though they were situated very far away.

"Master's beginning to refine the baleful qi! Could it be that he already made preparations for the baleful decay in advance?" Xiao Bai exclaimed in an ecstatic voice.

A hint of surprise appeared on Mo Guang's face, but he didn't say anything.

Meanwhile, Daoist Xie began to pilot the flying carriage closer to the cave before having it draw to a halt again.

With no response coming from either Mo Guang or Daoist Xie, Xiao Bai laid down onto the carriage again.

Close to a year passed by in the blink of an eye.

Most of the baleful qi in Han Li's body had been expelled, while only some tiny black spots remained on his body, and the baleful qi in his consciousness had also been virtually completely eradicated.

However, the High Zenith Pill that he had devoured had also been completely refined.

At this point, the residual baleful qi in Han Li's body had already been forced into a corner, but as the streams of warmth released by the High Zenith Pill slowly faded, the baleful qi immediately began to stir once again.

Han Li was quite alarmed to see this, and he immediately flipped a hand over to summon another white jade box, which contained a second High Zenith Pill that he swallowed without any hesitation.

As soon as the pill was devoured, the more streams of warmth instantly began to flow through his body again, surging toward the remaining baleful qi.

Before long, all of the remaining baleful qi had been eradicated, and the black spots on Han Li's body vanished.

His skin had become as translucent as jade, to the point that his bones could be made out through his skin and flesh.

However, his expression remained grim. Even though the baleful qi in his body had been eradicated, he knew that the baleful decay hadn't been completely overcome yet.

Out of his 107 opened immortal acupoints, 71 of them had been forced open using baleful qi.

While the baleful qi within his body had been eradicated by the High Zenith Pills, the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints still remained, much to his concern and dismay.

Just as he had anticipated, the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints were posing as a major obstacle to his progression to the High Zenith Stage.

Having said that, even though the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints hadn't been cleansed, most of the medicinal power from the second High Zenith Pill was still active in his body, and he also had a third, even more potent High Zenith Pill, and that should be more than enough to eradicate the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints.

With that in mind, Han Li took a deep breath, then directed the streams of warmth in his body toward his immortal acupoints.

The baleful qi in his immortal acupoints was instantly stirred up by the streams of warmth, but unlike the baleful qi from before, this baleful qi showed no signs of receding, and it was as if they had taken root in the immortal acupoints.

Han Li's heart sank slightly upon seeing this, and he adopted a different approach, enveloping the baleful qi in the medicinal power of the High Zenith Pill before gnashing away at it.

Another few months flew by in a flash, and at this point, Han Li was no longer looking as composed and unconcerned as before.

Through these past few months of toil, he had managed to make the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints slightly dimmer than before, but that was all that he had to show for his efforts.

Not a single one of his 71 immortal acupoints had been completely cleansed of baleful qi.

A cold look flashed through Han Li's eyes as he clenched his fists tightly, and right at this moment, a faint thud rang out from within his body as the second High Zenith Pill was finally completely refined.

As a result, the streams of warmth instantly receded out of his immortal acupoints, and the baleful qi inside immediately lit up once again, threatening to make a resurgence after being repressed for so long.

Chapter 601: Temporary Fix

The immortal spiritual power within Han Li's body was instantly sucked into these immortal acupoints, and the world's origin qi outside his body also began to surge into them.

A strange bubbling sound rang out from within these immortal acupoints, and wisps of baleful qi emerged from within them, spreading throughout Han Li's body again.

These wisps of baleful qi were incredibly dark, seemingly able to devour all light, and they were even more formidable than the baleful qi that had previously been in Han Li's body.

Furthermore, some of these wisps of baleful qi were spreading through the other immortal acupoints that had no baleful qi within them.

Han Li was naturally very alarmed to see this, and he hurriedly channeled his time law powers to oppose the baleful qi.

However, this eruption of baleful qi was even more ferocious than before, and even Han Li's time law powers were struggling to withstand it.

Han Li immediately made a hand seal to inject more immortal spiritual power into his Mantra Axis Scripture, and at the same time, he summoned a white jade box, then opened it to reveal a High Zenith Pill sitting inside.

In contrast with the previous two High Zenith Pills, this one had a series of silver lines on its surface that came together to form the design of a three-legged golden crow, and it was also giving off a far more formidable aura than the other two High Zenith Pills.

Han Li carefully plucked the High Zenith Pill out of the box, but hesitated right as he was about to eat it.

The onset of baleful decay had been far more violent than he anticipated, and even though this High Zenith Pill was of a far superior caliber than the previous two, he still wasn't confident in its ability to eradicate the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints.

Given what had happened with the previous two pills, the chances of failure were quite high.

The average late-Golden Immortal cultivator would inevitably have to kill and accumulate baleful qi in their body during their cultivation, but for them, just a single normal High Zenith Pill should be enough to eradicate all of their built-up baleful qi. In contrast, Han Li had so much baleful qi in his body that he was essentially half a Gray Immortal.

Unless he could find an effective solution to the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints and restore himself to his normal state, taking more High Zenith Pills most likely wasn't going to help him.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him, and he set down the High Zenith Pill in his hand before stowing it away, then called out through voice transmission.

At this moment, Mo Guang and the others were all seated with their legs crossed in an obscure valley not far away from the cave that Han Li was in. The green flying carriage was hovering above a corner of the valley, and Jin Tong was still displaying no signs of awakening.

All of a sudden, Mo Guang's eyes sprang open as he rose to his feet.

Xiao Bai immediately sprang up onto its haunches, standing in Mo Guang's path with a wary look on its face as it asked, "What are you doing?"

"Your master has asked me to go to him," Mo Guang explained, then set off as a streak of black light, arriving in front of the cave that Han Li was in shortly thereafter.

The restrictions in the cave opened up on their own to create a passageway, and as soon as Mo Guang stepped into the cave, he was immediately struck by a wave of incredibly dense baleful qi.

His expression remained unchanged as he continued onward, and it didn't take long before he spotted an indistinct seated figure that was entirely enshrouded in black qi and golden light.

"Fellow Daoist Mo Guang, I need your help," Han Li said while channeling his time law powers with all his might, and speaking seemed to be quite a difficult task for him.

"I know what you need me to do. This will actually be quite beneficial for me," Mo Guang replied with a nod, then sat down with his legs crossed beside Han Li, who didn't waste any more time and immediately sprang into action.

With a sweep of his sleeve, hundreds of black array flags shot out in unison before landing all around the cave.

He then made a rapid string of hand seals, and black light flashed erratically over the array flags as a series of black array patterns quickly emerged to form an array that was several dozen feet in size.

After that, Han Li began to chant an incantation, then opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence into the array.

The black array immediately lit up, and several bursts of black light that were roughly the same thickness as adult human arms appeared around him, then pierced into his body.

The churning baleful qi within Han Li's body immediately stiffened, then flowed into the array long these bursts of black light.

Every single line of the array was glowing with faint black light, and dense baleful qi was rapidly flowing over those lines.

In the span of just a few seconds, the entire array was filled with baleful qi.

Right at this moment, the array patterns around Mo Guang lit up as well, and several bursts of black light emerged before piercing into his body.

The baleful qi in the array seemed to have found an outlet, and all of it surged into Mo Guang's body, causing him to shudder slightly, but an elated look then appeared on his face as he closed his eyes to absorb the incoming baleful qi.

Before long, roughly 30% of the baleful qi in Han Li's body had been transferred into Mo Guang's body through the array.

This entire time, Mo Guang's eyes remained tightly shut as he focused on refining the influx of baleful qi, while the strain on Han Li's face was steadily easing.

All of a sudden, he began to chant another incantation, then made a grabbing motion with his right hand, and a golden vial slowly took shape in his grasp.

There were six Time Dao Runes on the surface of the vial, and it was none other than his Clear Time Vial.

Inside the vial was a drop of semi-transparent golden liquid that was shimmering with faint spiritual light, and aside from the difference in coloration, it was very similar in appearance to the green spirit liquid produced by the Heaven Controlling Vial.

It wasn't entirely accurate to say that Han Li hadn't made any preparations for the baleful decay. During these past years, whenever he had some free time, he would release his Clear Time Vial so that it could absorb the light of the sun and the moon to manifest time water droplets.

After so many years of persistence, he had finally managed to produce a single droplet.

Han Li pointed a finger at the Clear Time Vial, and a beam of golden light immediately shot out of his fingertip before vanishing into the vial.

The Time Dao Runes on the vial instantly began to glow brightly while a series of golden runes emerged within it, and the time water droplet also slowly rose up from the bottom of the vial.

All of the nearby golden runes converged toward the time water droplet before fusing into it, and the golden spiritual light emanating from the droplet instantly brightened significantly.

At the same time, all of the nearby world's origin qi was also stirred up into a frenzy, and countless balls of five-colored light appeared in the surrounding area before surging into the time water droplet as well.

Han Li continued to cycle through a string of hand seals, releasing one beam of golden light into the Clear Time Vial after another, and the time water droplet glowed brighter and brighter while also gradually transitioning into a solid state before slowly spreading outward.

Three days flew by in a flash, and at this point, the time water droplet inside the Clear Water Vial had transformed into a translucent golden thread around the same length as a human finger.

Formidable time law power fluctuations were emanating from the translucent golden thread, yet it was different from the time law power fluctuations released by Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis.

At this point, most of Han Li's body had turned black, and his eyes were glowing a crimson color, but he was still able to retain his own sanity.

All of a sudden, an elated look appeared in his eyes, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which the translucent golden thread flew out of the Clear Time Vial before vanishing into his chest.

Immediately thereafter, a vast expanse of golden spiritual light erupted out of his body, and a series of golden halos appeared before spreading outward.

Bursts of time law powers were surging throughout the golden light, causing the nearby space to become rather blurry and indistinct, and Han Li's body was also becoming less and less visible.

At the same time, the black array abruptly ceased to function, and Mo Guang opened his eyes before rising to his feet before casting his gaze toward Han Li.

At this moment, his aura had become slightly more formidable than before.

The golden light around Han Li continued to flash erratically for about 15 minutes before finally fading away, upon which it was revealed that both his body and his eyes had returned to their original color, and it was as if the baleful decay had been nothing more than a distant dream.

"Congratulations, Fellow Daoist Han," Mo Guang said.

"Thank you for your help, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang, but I'm afraid this is only a temporary fix," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"There's no need to thank me, Fellow Daoist Han, I'm just glad I could help," Mo Guang said with a shake of his head.

Han Li withdrew his gaze from Mo Guang, then took a deep breath before inspecting his own internal condition, upon which a wry smile appeared on his face.

The translucent golden thread produced by the Clear Time Vial was a thread of time, and it was able to delay the onset of the five decays, so it had temporarily suppressed his baleful decay.

This was the first time that he was using a thread of time, so he didn't know how long it could delay the onset of his baleful decay for, but he felt like it should be able to delay his baleful decay for at least a few centuries.

After taking a moment to compose himself, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to recover all of the array tools in the surrounding cave before flying out into the valley as a streak of azure light, followed closely by Mo Guang.

An ecstatic look immediately appeared on Xiao Bai's face at the sight of Han Li, but the elation on its face then gradually faded as it caught sight of Han Li's rather grim expression.

Meanwhile, Daoist Xie rose to its feet, but merely cupped its fist in a salute toward Han Li without saying anything.

Han Li gave Daoist Xie a nod, then put on a reassuring smile as he patted Xiao Bai on the head.

After that, he turned his gaze to the white cloud before asking, "Has Jin Tong still not shown any signs of waking up?"

"Not at all, Master. Will she be alright?" Xiao Bai asked with a slightly concerned expression.

"Don't worry, she'll be fine," Han Li replied.

Xiao Bai was quite relieved to hear this, and it asked, "Where do we go from here, Master?"